<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<sessions xmlns="sessions.xsd">

    <div class="post">

        <h2 class="title">
            <a href="/Sessions/1131/ReBuilding-BASIC">(Re)Building BASIC</a>
        </h2>

        <div class="entry">

            <div>


                <div>
                    Speaker: <a href="/Speakers/1128/cory-smith">Cory Smith</a>
                </div>



                <div>Category: Developers</div>

                <div title="Intermediate">Level: 200</div>



            </div>

            <p>BASIC turned 47 this year and it started me thinking.  It's been a long and winding road to the age of .NET and there are times that I miss the fun factor that was &quot;hacking&quot; around in the BASIC's of old.  Sure, I could go out and find a copy of GW-BASIC and run it inside of DOSBox... but wouldn't it be cool to recreate it on a modern platform?  What would be involved in doing this?  How does one go about writing an interpreter?  What would be involved in order to compile line numbered BASIC to target .NET?  Does Silverlight offer enough capabilities to emulate a DOS type display?  These are but a few of the questions that had been running through my mind; so the project began.  It is a work in progress; however, there are plenty of thoughts and experiences to pull from.  So if you share an interest in compilers/interpreters, language design, how I hacked up Silverlight to create a UI dating 20+ years ago or to just ask me &quot;why?!?!?&quot;, feel free to join this conversation.</p>

        </div>

    </div>



    <div class="post">

        <h2 class="title">
            <a href="/Sessions/829/A-Lap-around-Orchard-The-Open-source-free-content-management-system-from-Microsoft">A Lap around Orchard: The Open source free content management system from Microsoft</a>
        </h2>

        <div class="entry">

            <div>


                <div>
                    Speaker: <a href="/Speakers/828/shawn-weisfeld">Shawn Weisfeld</a>
                </div>


                <div>Category: Developers</div>

                <div title="Beginner">Level: 100</div>



            </div>

            <p>In this talk Shawn will provide an overview of what Orchard is. We will demonstrate installing configuring and getting started with the platform. We will then look at the module eco system and how to add functionality and themes to your orchard site. We will look at the features of the package and see how the http://www.UserGroup.tv website was build atop this package.   </p>

        </div>

    </div>



    <div class="post">

        <h2 class="title">
            <a href="/Sessions/619/Architecture-and-Entity-Framework-Not-the-odd-couple">Architecture and Entity Framework - Not the odd couple</a>
        </h2>

        <div class="entry">

            <div>


                <div>
                    Speaker: <a href="/Speakers/46/devlin">Devlin</a>
                </div>


                <div>Category: Developers</div>

                <div title="Advanced">Level: 300</div>



            </div>

            <p>In this talk we will dive into the details of scalable and supportable Enterprise Solutions and how to make Entity Framework dance to that song. We will look at Entity Framework behind WCF services, using parallel processing, and how to handle explicit load scenarios for low bandwidth connections.</p>

        </div>

    </div>



    <div class="post">

        <h2 class="title">
            <a href="/Sessions/110/ASPNET-MVC-3-In-Action">ASP.NET MVC 3 In Action</a>
        </h2>

        <div class="entry">

            <div>


                <div>
                    Speaker: <a href="/Speakers/103/matt-hinze">Matt Hinze</a>
                </div>


                <div>Category: Developers</div>

                <div title="Advanced">Level: 300</div>



            </div>

            <p>This talk is for developers familiar with ASP.NET MVC that are taking their use of the framework to the next level.  In this session Matt Hinze, author of ASP.NET MVC 3 In Action, will present advanced ASP.NET MVC topics taken from real world projects, including: </p>
            <p>
                1. Understanding client side validation<br />2. Automation tools and developer productivity<br />2. Slick options for functional testing<br />
            </p>

        </div>

    </div>



    <div class="post">

        <h2 class="title">
            <a href="/Sessions/712/ASPNET-MVC-vs-Web-Forms">ASP.NET MVC vs. Web Forms</a>
        </h2>

        <div class="entry">

            <div>


                <div>
                    Speaker: <a href="/Speakers/708/thiago-silva">Thiago Silva</a>
                </div>


                <div>Category: Developers</div>

                <div title="Intermediate">Level: 200</div>



            </div>

            <p>Learn the differences between Microsoft’s current web frameworks as we compare and contrast ASP.NET Web Forms and MVC.  In this session we’ll introduce basic concepts of ASP.NET MVC, highlight pros and cons, and discuss things to consider when choosing the right technology for your project.</p>

        </div>

    </div>



    <div class="post">

        <h2 class="title">
            <a href="/Sessions/782/Attack-of-the-Cloud">Attack, of the Cloud!</a>
        </h2>

        <div class="entry">

            <div>


                <div>
                    Speaker: <a href="/Speakers/781/tom-dupont">Tom DuPont</a>
                </div>


                <div>Category: Developers</div>

                <div title="Advanced">Level: 300</div>



            </div>

            <p>Cloud computing is great, but what do we put in the cloud? The web is advancing at an incredible pace and it’s time to start building true Web Applications, not just web sites! Web Apps shake off the constraints of operating system specific frameworks, and free developers to work in open standards based environment. This session will cover a variety of topics ranging from ASP.NET MVC development, unit testing, REST APIs, JSON, JQuery, ExtJS, tips and tricks, lessons learned, and more. It will conclude with building a sample blog reader Web App, and then deploying that to Windows Azure.</p>

        </div>

    </div>



    <div class="post">

        <h2 class="title">
            <a href="/Sessions/183/Build-Secure-Database-Applications-using-SQL-Server">Build Secure Database Applications using SQL Server</a>
        </h2>

        <div class="entry">

            <div>


                <div>
                    Speaker: <a href="/Speakers/182/bryan-smith">Bryan Smith</a>
                </div>


                <div>Category: Developers</div>

                <div title="Beginner">Level: 100</div>



            </div>

            <p>In this session, you will review techniques and features used with Microsoft SQL Server to build secure database applications.</p>

        </div>

    </div>



    <div class="post">

        <h2 class="title">
            <a href="/Sessions/713/Building-a-Better-User-Experience-with-jQuery-and-WCF">Building a Better User Experience with jQuery and WCF</a>
        </h2>

        <div class="entry">

            <div>


                <div>
                    Speaker: <a href="/Speakers/711/jeff-hewitt">Jeff Hewitt</a>
                </div>


                <div>Category: Developers</div>

                <div title="Intermediate">Level: 200</div>



            </div>

            <p>Learn how to leverage jQuery and WCF in your ASP.NET applications to provide a richer, more responsive and more intuitive user experience.   In this session, we’ll discuss and demonstrate a structured approach to leveraging server side business logic and performing complex DOM manipulations using jQuery and WCF.</p>

        </div>

    </div>


    <div class="post">

        <h2 class="title">
            <a href="/Sessions/889/Connect-with-your-Kinect">Connect with your Kinect</a>
        </h2>

        <div class="entry">

            <div>


                <div>
                    Speaker: <a href="/Speakers/888/justin-weinberg">Justin Weinberg</a>
                </div>



                <div>Category: Developers</div>

                <div title="Beginner">Level: 100</div>



            </div>

            <p>The Microsoft Kinect peripheral is the fastest selling gadget of all time, selling more units in a shorter time span than the IPhone or IPad.  With the release of the Windows SDK beta for Kinect, there has never been a better time to learn about this new and innovative peripheral and exploring where your imagination takes you.</p>
            <p>
                This C# code focused session will dive into how to use the API to do some wicked cool things.  We'll start by exploring the skeletal tracking API and follow this up with some very basic speech recognition samples.  Finally we'll wrap it all together with a demo that combines a traditional WPF interface with gensture and audio queue integration.<br />
            </p>

        </div>

    </div>



    <div class="post">

        <h2 class="title">
            <a href="/Sessions/74/Correspondence-Building-Occasionally-Connected-Windows-Phone-Apps">Correspondence: Building Occasionally-Connected Windows Phone Apps</a>
        </h2>

        <div class="entry">

            <div>


                <div>
                    Speaker: <a href="/Speakers/73/michael-l-perry">Michael L Perry</a>
                </div>


                <div>Category: Developers</div>

                <div title="Advanced">Level: 300</div>


                <div class="session-status-Accepted">Status: Accepted</div>
                <div>None</div>

                <div>None</div>


            </div>

            <p>Phones are personal devices, so users expect their data to be local. But they are also collaborative devices, so users expect them to talk to each other. An occasionally connected Windows Phone application is the best of both worlds. It stores personal data locally for instant access. And it synchronizes with remote services for collaboration.</p>
            <p>Correspondence is an open source library specifically designed to make it easy to build occasionally connected applications. When you design your data model using its DSL, it generates both a local database and a network protocol. Then it gives you an object model to code against that seamlessly bridges the two worlds.</p>
            <p>Not only will I demonstrate a collaborative Windows Phone application, but I’ll teach you how to write one. You start with the data model, written in a Domain Specific Language called Factual. Then you expose that model through a View Model layer. Data bind your View Model to the UI, and your application is complete.</p>
            <p>When the user makes a change, it is both stored to the local database and published to the server. Changes made by other users are automatically pushed to the phone. Through the magic of data binding, the user is instantly notified of the change.</p>

        </div>

    </div>



    <div class="post">

        <h2 class="title">
            <a href="/Sessions/95/Cross-Platform-Development-with-jQuery-Mobile-and-PhoneGap-">Cross-Platform Development with jQuery Mobile and PhoneGap </a>
        </h2>

        <div class="entry">

            <div>


                <div>
                    Speaker: <a href="/Speakers/93/todd-stone">Todd Stone</a>
                </div>



                <div>Category: Developers</div>

                <div title="Beginner">Level: 100</div>



            </div>

            <p>jQuery Mobile is an open source touch-optimized web framework for smartphones &amp; tablets. It will allow you to design a single web application that will work on all popular smartphone and tablet platforms.  PhoneGap is an open source HTML5 app platform that supports 6 platforms.  It allows you to author native applications with web technologies and get access to APIs and app stores.  I'll show how to build a web app using jQuery Mobile with PhoneGap and share tips and tricks I've learned along the way.</p>

        </div>

    </div>



    <div class="post">

        <h2 class="title">
            <a href="/Sessions/902/Css-for-Developers">Css for Developers</a>
        </h2>

        <div class="entry">

            <div>


                <div>
                    Speaker: <a href="/Speakers/901/eric-sowell">Eric Sowell</a>
                </div>


                <div>Category: Developers</div>

                <div title="Beginner">Level: 100</div>



            </div>

            <p>Web developers often avoid digging into the topic of Css because they think that is what web designers are for and that you have be good at design to understand Css well. Neither of these is true. In this session we will jump into Css and semantic Html and see most of the skills needed to turn a design into a reality. Design is a very different skill from programming, but any programmer can learn how to take a design and turn it into a web page.</p>

        </div>

    </div>



    <div class="post">

        <h2 class="title">
            <a href="/Sessions/663/Data-in-Windows-Azure">Data in Windows Azure</a>
        </h2>

        <div class="entry">

            <div>


                <div>
                    Speaker: <a href="/Speakers/166/eric-d-boyd">Eric D. Boyd</a>
                </div>


                <div>Category: Developers</div>

                <div title="Intermediate">Level: 200</div>



            </div>

            <p>The Windows Azure Platform provides a plethora of options for data storage and trying to make sense of it all can be overwhelming. In this session we will explore the many Azure data services including SQL Azure, Azure Storage, Local Storage and AppFabric Caching. We will walk through the scenarios that each storage service addresses. Next we will dig into how to use each storage service and how they can complement each other when used together. Finally, we will explore the pricing and economic drivers that encourage one storage service over another when multiple fit into your solution.</p>

        </div>

    </div>



    <div class="post">

        <h2 class="title">
            <a href="/Sessions/947/Database-Migrations-in-Grails">Database Migrations in Grails</a>
        </h2>

        <div class="entry">

            <div>


                <div>
                    Speaker: <a href="/Speakers/946/nirav-assar">Nirav Assar</a>
                </div>


                <div>Category: Developers</div>

                <div title="Intermediate">Level: 200</div>



            </div>

            <p>Database migrations are an important facet of web development. When an application is in production and the customer requests incremental changes to the database, the development team must have a rock solid plan to preserve the existing data while seamlessly adding new functionality and tables. Without a tool to manage database migrations, teams rely on manual sql, error prone communication processes, and costly risk management to implement solutions.</p>
            <p>This presentation will cover the Grails Database Migration Plugin, the official plugin created by Spring Source which is based on the popular Liquibase framework. With live examples, we will demonstrate how database migrations can be controlled, managed, and executed.  </p>
            <p>
                Presenter: Nirav Assar<br />Audience: Grails Developers, Java Developers, Beginners to Expert
            </p>

        </div>

    </div>


    <div class="post">

        <h2 class="title">
            <a href="/Sessions/647/Developers-Are-From-Mars-Users-Are-From-Klingon">Developers Are From Mars, Users Are From Klingon</a>
        </h2>

        <div class="entry">

            <div>


                <div>
                    Speaker: <a href="/Speakers/632/derek-lane">Derek Lane</a>
                </div>



                <div>Category: Developers</div>

                <div title="Beginner">Level: 100</div>



            </div>

            <p>You know it's true. Trying to understand what your users want is sometimes like talking to the wall. Have you ever delivered what you were sure a group of users asked for, only to have them reject it as not even close?</p>
            <p>This **DOUBLE** session will explore some techniques to help technologists identify with what their users are asking for, and provide some techniques developers can use to help close the communication gap between users and developers.</p>
            <p>Note: This session will consume TWO time slots, and is hands on and highly interactive. This session is for any skill set or role that is involved in product development. Co-presenter with Modesto Hernandez.</p>

        </div>

    </div>



    <div class="post">

        <h2 class="title">
            <a href="/Sessions/113/Developing-Social-Ready-Web-Applications">Developing Social-Ready Web Applications</a>
        </h2>

        <div class="entry">

            <div>


                <div>
                    Speaker: <a href="/Speakers/112/craig-walls">Craig Walls</a>
                </div>


                <div>Category: Developers</div>

                <div title="Intermediate">Level: 200</div>



            </div>

            <p>Businesses are increasingly recognizing the value of connecting with their customers on a more personal level. Companies can utilize social networking to transition from &quot;Big Faceless Corporation&quot; to &quot;Friend&quot; by taking their wares to the online communities where their customers are. In this age of social media, those communities are found at social network sites such as Facebook, Twitter, and LinkedIn. In this session, you'll learn how to build applications that interact with the various social networks. We'll also look at Spring Social, a new feature in the Spring portfolio that enables integration with social networks in Spring-based applications.</p>

        </div>

    </div>



    <div class="post">

        <h2 class="title">
            <a href="/Sessions/715/Discovering-the-Potential-The-Microsoft-xRM-Development-Framework">Discovering the Potential - The Microsoft xRM Development Framework</a>
        </h2>

        <div class="entry">

            <div>


                <div>
                    Speaker: <a href="/Speakers/714/chris-griswold">Chris Griswold</a>
                </div>


                <div>Category: Developers</div>

                <div title="Intermediate">Level: 200</div>



            </div>

            <p>
                With the latest release of Dynamics CRM 2011, Microsoft introduced a much expanded and improved version of its powerful xRM development framework. This session will explore the ease and power of building custom web applications via the CRM user interface as well as the various tools and paths available for customizing, integrating and automating those applications. Topics covered will include:<br />- Building the object model and forms with the CRM UI<br />- Early-bindig vs late binding with the xRM API<br />- Interacting with the xRM API using LINQ<br />- Highlight the various customization paths and technologies such as ASP.NET, Plugins, JScript, SOAP, REST, JQuery, OData, FetchXML, etc.<br />- Office-like user interface and native Outlook integration<br />- xRM Javascript framwork for manipulating the DOM<br />- Capabilities of the new xRM Web Controls
            </p>

        </div>

    </div>


    <div class="post">

        <h2 class="title">
            <a href="/Sessions/800/Dynamic-ASPNET-MVC-and-BDD">Dynamic ASP.NET MVC and BDD</a>
        </h2>

        <div class="entry">

            <div>


                <div>
                    Speaker: <a href="/Speakers/798/amir-rajan">Amir Rajan</a>
                </div>



                <div>Category: Developers</div>

                <div title="Expert">Level: 400</div>



            </div>

            <p>ASP.NET MVC 3.0 and C# 4.0 make a great pair.  Amir Rajan will show how leveraging BDD (Behavior Driven Development), open source software and C# 4.0 constructs can lead to lean, mean MVC applications.  We'll take a look at how we can trim the fat by using the C# dynamic keyword, controller view bags, dynamic micro orms (along with dynamic dsl's for schema creation), ruby (gasp!), and a .Net testing framework built for BDD.</p>

        </div>

    </div>



    <div class="post">

        <h2 class="title">
            <a href="/Sessions/617/Entity-Framework-41-Code-First-Goodness">Entity Framework 4.1 Code First Goodness</a>
        </h2>

        <div class="entry">

            <div>


                <div>
                    Speaker: <a href="/Speakers/46/devlin">Devlin</a>
                </div>


                <div>Category: Developers</div>

                <div title="Intermediate">Level: 200</div>



            </div>

            <p>In this talk we dive into the code first approach using Entity Framework and look at using the power tools to generate the baseline configuration from existing databases to jump start the project.</p>

        </div>

    </div>



    <div class="post">

        <h2 class="title">
            <a href="/Sessions/873/EntityFramework-360-Getting-Started">EntityFramework 360: Getting Started</a>
        </h2>

        <div class="entry">

            <div>


                <div>
                    Speaker: <a href="/Speakers/871/rob-vettor">rob vettor</a>
                </div>


                <div>Category: Developers</div>

                <div title="Beginner">Level: 100</div>



            </div>

            <p>While most enterprise applications are object-oriented, the data upon which they depend is not. </p>
            <p>Come see how you can effectively bind these two worlds together by leveraging the Microsoft ADO.NET Entity Framework.  In this session, we’ll…</p>
            <p>
                • Explore the Entity Framework 4, its components and see how it all works<br />• Learn about the benefits and drawbacks of the 3 different approaches to using the tool <br />• Generate a business object model with database mappings<br />• Walk through a variety of code examples that show how to interact with the model<br />• Show how the Entity Framework automatically tracks data changes and generates updates<br />• Deep-dive into the code-only features of the recent 4.1 release
            </p>
            <p>
                You’ll walk-away with a clear understanding of the different approaches to implementing Entity Framework in your project.<br />
            </p>

        </div>

    </div>



    <div class="post">

        <h2 class="title">
            <a href="/Sessions/124/Estimate-Your-Requirements-with-Planning-Poker">Estimate Your Requirements with Planning Poker</a>
        </h2>

        <div class="entry">

            <div>


                <div>
                    Speaker: <a href="/Speakers/122/jay-smith">Jay Smith</a>
                </div>



                <div>Category: Project Managers</div>

                <div title="Beginner">Level: 100</div>



            </div>

            <p>Planning Poker is a consensus-based estimation technique for estimating, mostly used to estimate effort or relative size of tasks in software development . It is a variation of the Wideband Delphi method. In this session you will learn not only what planning poker is but how to facilitate it with your team. Using Planning Poker to estimate task on your project is not only accurate its fun.</p>
            <p>Things you will learn:</p>
            <p>
                What is Planning Poker<br />Who need to be involved in a Planning Poker session<br />What you need to have a session<br />Who to host a planning session
            </p>

        </div>

    </div>



    <div class="post">

        <h2 class="title">
            <a href="/Sessions/797/Extending-Visual-Studio">Extending Visual Studio</a>
        </h2>

        <div class="entry">

            <div>


                <div>
                    Speaker: <a href="/Speakers/791/latish">Latish</a>
                </div>


                <div>Category: Developers</div>

                <div title="Intermediate">Level: 200</div>



            </div>

            <p>Are you a big fan of productivity plugins like ReSharper and CodeRush? Ever wondered how you can write your own plug-ins for Visual Studio? Come to this session to learn about the different ways to extend Visual Studio. We'll see how one can create extensions, add-ins and packages and add new functionality to  Visual Studio (We'll talk about both Visual Studio 2008 and 2010).</p>

        </div>

    </div>



    <div class="post">

        <h2 class="title">
            <a href="/Sessions/196/Finding-the-Needle-Making-sense-of-large-event-streams-in-real-time-with-StreamInsight">Finding the Needle - Making sense of large event streams in real time with StreamInsight</a>
        </h2>

        <div class="entry">

            <div>


                <div>
                    Speaker: <a href="/Speakers/185/rob-pierry">Rob Pierry</a>
                </div>


                <div>Category: Developers</div>

                <div title="Intermediate">Level: 200</div>



            </div>

            <p>
                <br />High volume streams of events are pervasive in manufacturing, financial trading, and web analytics applications.  Sifting through these events to find the patterns that identify key business scenarios in a timely enough fashion to react used to require expensive, narrowly tailored software packages. Now, with StreamInsight in SQL Server 2008 R2, developers can use a simple and expressive LINQ API to analyze both historical streams of events and near real time streams to identify patterns and react.
            </p>
            <p>In this session we'll cover an overview of StreamInsight and then dig into examples of its use.  Whether you're monitoring assembly lines or analyzing and responding to user behavior while they're still on your site, StreamInsight can make your job easier. Since it's included with SQL Server, there aren't any extra licensing fees.</p>

        </div>

    </div>



    <div class="post">

        <h2 class="title">
            <a href="/Sessions/977/From-Delegates-to-Lamdas-and-Expression-Trees-Your-guide-to-writing-elegant-code-in-C-NET-40">From Delegates, to Lamdas and Expression Trees: Your guide to writing elegant code in C# .NET 4.0</a>
        </h2>

        <div class="entry">

            <div>


                <div>
                    Speaker: <a href="/Speakers/976/chander-dhall">Chander Dhall</a>
                </div>


                <div>Category: Developers</div>

                <div title="Beginner">Level: 100</div>



            </div>

            <p>
                This talk takes you from the delegate syntax from .net 2.0 to actions and funcs. Then it dives deep into creating elegant code using lamdas. Gives you an understanding as to how to implement expression trees for some cool and quick framework development inside your organization. This talk does not require any understanding of delegates and goes from the beginner to intermediate level. <br />
            </p>

        </div>

    </div>


    <div class="post">

        <h2 class="title">
            <a href="/Sessions/376/Get-a-better-worklife-balance-through-process-improvement">Get a better work/life balance through process improvement</a>
        </h2>

        <div class="entry">

            <div>


                <div>
                    Speaker: <a href="/Speakers/256/d-omar-villarreal">D. Omar Villarreal</a>
                </div>



                <div>Category: Developers</div>

                <div title="Beginner">Level: 100</div>



            </div>

            <p>Do you have experience improving your team's process? </p>
            <p>
                Are you frustrated or constantly working late because: <br />- One or more areas of your work process can be improved<br />- Your teammates or manager don’t see the need to improve
            </p>
            <p>
                Or maybe they do see the need to improve but are too busy (or budget is insufficient) to formally improve the way the team works?<br /> <br />Is your team ready and anxious to get better but don’t know how?
            </p>
            <p>
                Join us in this interactive birds of a feather session to share your experiences and learn how you can get process improvement implemented or kicked up a notch in your organization.<br />
            </p>

        </div>

    </div>



    <div class="post">

        <h2 class="title">
            <a href="/Sessions/721/GlassFish-31-Deploying-your-Java-EE-6-applications-in-a-cluster">GlassFish 3.1: Deploying your Java EE 6 applications in a cluster</a>
        </h2>

        <div class="entry">

            <div>


                <div>
                    Speaker: <a href="/Speakers/719/arun-gupta">Arun Gupta</a>
                </div>


                <div>Category: Developers</div>

                <div title="Beginner">Level: 100</div>



            </div>

            <p>GlassFish 3.1 has several features that are typically required for deploying a Java EE 6 application in production. An ssh-provisioned cluster can be easily created with centralized administration and has high availability for session failover. OSGi-enabled Java EE applications, RESTful administration, web-based admin console, application-scoped resources, application versioning, and many other features can make the overall experience very pleasing. Coherence*Web integration and full commercial support from Oracle makes it the first production-ready Java EE 6 compliant application server. This session will provide details about the features mentioned above and show live demos of several of them. </p>

        </div>

    </div>



    <div class="post">

        <h2 class="title">
            <a href="/Sessions/83/HTML5-Video">HTML5 Video</a>
        </h2>

        <div class="entry">

            <div>


                <div>
                    Speaker: <a href="/Speakers/82/mike-wilcox">Mike Wilcox</a>
                </div>


                <div>Category: Developers</div>

                <div title="Beginner">Level: 100</div>



            </div>

            <p>What is HTML5 Video and how is it different from what we are used to? What problems does it solve, and what issues does it have? This is the web, so it's open source right? In this presentation, we will address these questions and provide some basic terminology for understanding how video works. We'll show how to embed HTML5 Video, and how to implement a work-around for older browsers.</p>

        </div>

    </div>



    <div class="post">

        <h2 class="title">
            <a href="/Sessions/737/Introducing-Open-Admin-a-framework-to-easily-build-rich-administration-screens">Introducing Open Admin - a framework to easily build rich administration screens</a>
        </h2>

        <div class="entry">

            <div>


                <div>
                    Speaker: <a href="/Speakers/736/brian-polster">Brian Polster</a>
                </div>


                <div>Category: Developers</div>

                <div title="Intermediate">Level: 200</div>



            </div>

            <p>Building administration screens to manage data required by your application can be tedious work.    Administration screens and programs are often thought of late in the delivery cycle and rushing them tends to result in featureless screens that just barely get the job done.</p>
            <p>Open Admin is a soon to be released component of the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.broadleafcommerce.org&quot;&gt;Broadleaf Commerce framework.&lt;/a&gt;.   It grew out of necessity as we needed complex catalog, customer, and order administration screens to round out the framework.</p>
            <p>Open Admin is based on Spring, Smart-GWT, and JPA(Hibernate).   It allows for rich, functional administration programs to be developed mainly through configuration and annotation of a JPA based model.</p>
            <p>This session will briefly describe the underlying technologies and walk through examples demonstrating how the technology can help you to build awesome administration components.</p>
            <p>If your already using JPA you'll be able to build awesome administration capabilities on the model with very low effort.</p>

        </div>

    </div>



    <div class="post">

        <h2 class="title">
            <a href="/Sessions/1007/IoC-with-PHP">IoC with PHP</a>
        </h2>

        <div class="entry">

            <div>


                <div>
                    Speaker: <a href="/Speakers/87/chris-weldon">Chris Weldon</a>
                </div>


                <div>Category: Developers</div>

                <div title="Beginner">Level: 100</div>



            </div>

            <p>PHP developers have not been known for their savvy use of design patterns. One such design pattern that's been woefully underutilized in PHP projects is that of Inversion of Control (IoC). However, the smart fellas over at Sensio Labs have finally built a Dependency Injection Container for our PHP projects. </p>
            <p>For many PHP developers, IoC is rather foreign to them. Thus, I plan to show them the ropes by giving a brief overview of object-oriented patterns, what IoC is, and how a dependency injection container helps implement IoC. To drive the point home, I'll present a couple of common development problems with your typical monkey wrench challenge where IoC (and the Symfony DI container) helps solve the problem. </p>

        </div>

    </div>



    <div class="post">

        <h2 class="title">
            <a href="/Sessions/718/Java-7-Its-out-but-should-I-care">Java 7 - It's out, but should I care?</a>
        </h2>

        <div class="entry">

            <div>


                <div>
                    Speaker: <a href="/Speakers/421/erik-weibust">Erik Weibust</a>
                </div>


                <div>Category: Developers</div>

                <div title="Beginner">Level: 100</div>



            </div>

            <p>Java 7 is at Milestone 12, it has a released Developer Preview, and is Feature Complete.  It *should* be publicly available in mid-July.  (NOTE: I will change this intro paragraph as Java 7 goes GA)</p>
            <p>In this session I will walk you through what made the final cut, what is worth looking at, and what was left out.  And lastly, when we might see closures hit the JDK.</p>
            <p>This session will include some live coding to further introduce attendees to the material being presented.</p>

        </div>

    </div>



    <div class="post">

        <h2 class="title">
            <a href="/Sessions/720/Java-EE-6--Less-Code--More-Power">Java EE 6 = Less Code + More Power</a>
        </h2>

        <div class="entry">

            <div>


                <div>
                    Speaker: <a href="/Speakers/719/arun-gupta">Arun Gupta</a>
                </div>


                <div>Category: Developers</div>

                <div title="Beginner">Level: 100</div>



            </div>

            <p>The Java EE 6 platform allows you to write enterprise Java applications using much lesser code from its earlier versions. It breaks the “one size fits all” approach with Profiles and improves on the Java EE 5 developer productivity features. Several specifications like CDI, JSF 2, JAX-RS, JPA 2, and Servlets 3 make the platform more powerful. It also enables extensibility by embracing open source libraries and frameworks such that they are treated as first class citizens of the platform. NetBeans, Eclipse, and IntelliJ provide extensive tooling for Java EE 6. This hands-on workshop will explain the Java EE 6 key concepts and specifications.</p>

        </div>

    </div>


    <div class="post">

        <h2 class="title">
            <a href="/Sessions/752/jQuery-is-a-library-not-a-framework">jQuery is a library, not a framework</a>
        </h2>

        <div class="entry">

            <div>


                <div>
                    Speaker: <a href="/Speakers/751/ryan-smith">Ryan Smith</a>
                </div>



                <div>Category: Developers</div>

                <div title="Intermediate">Level: 200</div>



            </div>

            <p>jQuery has reached the level of popularity that even your grandmother is considering adding it to her Wordpress blog because she wants to &quot;Write Less, Do More.&quot; (You know the world is changing when she calls you on a Sunday afternoon for help installing AJAX onto her AOL.)</p>
            <p>It's true that these days, you can pretty much drop jQuery on your page to automagically add more cowbell to your user interactions. But should we be content to just sprinkle fairy dust on our DIVs and call it a day?</p>
            <p>If you have ever watched your front-end code grow from a few polite lines of click handling to a full-on spaghetti code mess, or lost count of your jQuery plugins and wondered in despair, &quot;How did I get here?&quot; you might have already realized that it is time to start thinking about JavaScript architecture.</p>
            <p>This talk will briefly introduce jQuery, consider what it does well and what it leaves up to the developer, and look at some patterns and best practices for taming code and thinking architecturally about client-side scripting.</p>

        </div>

    </div>



    <div class="post">

        <h2 class="title">
            <a href="/Sessions/96/jQuery-Mobile-Build-Web-Apps-for-Smartphones--Tablets">jQuery Mobile - Build Web Apps for Smartphones &amp; Tablets</a>
        </h2>

        <div class="entry">

            <div>


                <div>
                    Speaker: <a href="/Speakers/93/todd-stone">Todd Stone</a>
                </div>


                <div>Category: Developers</div>

                <div title="Beginner">Level: 100</div>



            </div>

            <p>jQuery Mobile is a touch-optimized web framework for smartphones &amp; tablets. It will allow you to design a single web application that will work on all popular smartphone and tablet platforms. I'll show how to build a web app using jQuery Mobile and share tips and tricks I've learned along the way.</p>

        </div>

    </div>



    <div class="post">

        <h2 class="title">
            <a href="/Sessions/717/Leveraging-the-Three20-Framework-for-iPhone-Applications">Leveraging the Three20 Framework for iPhone Applications</a>
        </h2>

        <div class="entry">

            <div>


                <div>
                    Speaker: <a href="/Speakers/710/phillip-verheyden">Phillip Verheyden</a>
                </div>


                <div>Category: Developers</div>

                <div title="Advanced">Level: 300</div>



            </div>

            <p>In this tech talk we will go over the advantages of using Three20 to create rich, web-enabled iPhone applications with minimal code.  The Three20 library sprang from the Facebook iPhone application, and much of the features that you see on the Facebook app is open sourced in this library.  This framework provides lots of out-of-the-box features like URL request caching, a Photo viewer, pre-made custom table cells and internet-aware table views designed for remote loading (source code: https://github.com/facebook/three20).  A demo will follow with a couple of simple examples showing how easy it is to get going, with a more complex example that combines a few of the different views to start a feature-rich application.</p>

        </div>

    </div>



    <div class="post">

        <h2 class="title">
            <a href="/Sessions/481/mgrails-Mobile-Development-with-Grails-and-jQuery">m.grails:  Mobile Development with Grails and jQuery</a>
        </h2>

        <div class="entry">

            <div>


                <div>
                    Speaker: <a href="/Speakers/81/jacob-orshalick">Jacob Orshalick</a>
                </div>


                <div>Category: Developers</div>

                <div title="Intermediate">Level: 200</div>



            </div>

            <p>Mobile development has caught fire in our industry and we all want to be a part of it.  Rather than devoting the time and effort to learn Objective C or other platform specific APIs, we can leverage our existing knowledge.  jQuery Mobile, in conjunction with Grails, provides a familiar and robust mobile application solution.</p>
            <p>The speed of Grails development combined with the simplicity of jQuery Mobile creates the ultimate mobile development platform.  This presentation will provide an introduction to jQuery Mobile and the details necessary to integrate this technology with Grails.  We will dive into code transforming the Grails scaffolding into a mobile interface.</p>

        </div>

    </div>



    <div class="post">

        <h2 class="title">
            <a href="/Sessions/886/MVx-Making-Sense-Out-of-the-Model-View-Patterns-">MVx:  Making Sense Out of the Model View Patterns… </a>
        </h2>

        <div class="entry">

            <div>


                <div>
                    Speaker: <a href="/Speakers/871/rob-vettor">rob vettor</a>
                </div>



                <div>Category: Developers</div>

                <div title="Intermediate">Level: 200</div>



            </div>

            <p>The separation enforced by the ‘Model View’ patterns can quickly transform your application into a maintainable, modular and rapidly developed package. New features are easily added, new faces are a snap, testing is enhanced and developers and designers can more easily work simultaneously.</p>
            <p>Come compare the Model-View-Controller (MVC), Model-View-Presenter (MVP) and Model-View-View-Model (MVVM) patterns.  In this session, we’ll…</p>
            <p>
                •Explore the foundation, benefits and drawbacks of each pattern at an architectural level<br />•Contrast differences between each pointing out applicable situations where each may apply<br />•Walk through a variety of examples on the Microsoft platform, including Microsoft MVC, ASP.NET, Silverlight and Windows Presentation Foundation
            </p>
            <p>
                You’ll walk away with a clear understanding of each and examples that you can implement in your projects. <br />
            </p>

        </div>

    </div>



    <div class="post">

        <h2 class="title">
            <a href="/Sessions/215/Orientation-What-is-SQL-Serverand-whats-it-for-">Orientation: What is SQL Server,and what's it for? </a>
        </h2>

        <div class="entry">

            <div>


                <div>
                    Speaker: <a href="/Speakers/211/jen-mccown">Jen McCown</a>
                </div>


                <div>Category: Developers</div>

                <div title="Beginner">Level: 100</div>



            </div>

            <p>What is SQL Server? It's just software. What is SQL Server for? At its simplest, it lets you store data safely, and get it back out again. Is there a right way to say &quot;SQL&quot;? Yes, actually! In this session we will work with the tools to show you around SQL Server, and explore what it can do. If you're looking to get into databases, this is your session.</p>

        </div>

    </div>



    <div class="post">

        <h2 class="title">
            <a href="/Sessions/71/Overview-of-Windows-Phone-Mango">Overview of Windows Phone &quot;Mango&quot;</a>
        </h2>

        <div class="entry">

            <div>


                <div>
                    Speaker: <a href="/Speakers/70/chris-koenig">Chris Koenig</a>
                </div>


                <div>Category: Developers</div>

                <div title="Advanced">Level: 300</div>



            </div>

            <p>Windows Phone 7 was only the beginning. Later this year we’ll release a new version of Windows Phone, codenamed &quot;Mango&quot; that will unlock new capabilities for developers. In this session, Microsoft Senior Developer Evangelist Chris Koenig will deliver a demo-heavy preview of the new features in Windows Phone &quot;Mango&quot; - there will be lots of code and lots of examples on everything from multi-tasking, notifications, task switching and more. </p>

        </div>

    </div>



    <div class="post">

        <h2 class="title">
            <a href="/Sessions/545/Powershell-for-complete-beginners-Part-2">Powershell for complete beginners:  Part 2</a>
        </h2>

        <div class="entry">

            <div>


                <div>
                    Speaker: <a href="/Speakers/241/sean-mccown">Sean McCown</a>
                </div>



                <div>Category: Developers</div>

                <div title="Beginner">Level: 100</div>



            </div>

            <p>You can’t learn something as complex as Powershell in a single hour so we’re going to have another one right away.  This class picks up where Part 1 left off and continues with more SQL Server administration tasks.  This session will delve more into the day-to-day tasks that will make your life as a DBA much easier and allow you to go to lunch on time.</p>

        </div>

    </div>



    <div class="post">

        <h2 class="title">
            <a href="/Sessions/544/Powershell-for-complete-beginners-Part-1">Powershell for complete beginners: Part 1</a>
        </h2>

        <div class="entry">

            <div>


                <div>
                    Speaker: <a href="/Speakers/241/sean-mccown">Sean McCown</a>
                </div>


                <div>Category: Developers</div>

                <div title="Beginner">Level: 100</div>



            </div>

            <p>Have you been wanting to learn powershell but don’t know where to get started, or even why you should bother?  This is where you start.  Here I’ll show you what powershell is, what it’s all about, how the language is organized, and how to do some real work in SQL Server.  Come see why the world is so excited about Powershell and join the club of the DBAs who work faster and smarter.  After this session you won’t be a Powershell guru, but you will be able to understand blog examples and continue your learning from other resources.  Don’t put off Powershell any longer.</p>

        </div>

    </div>



    <div class="post">

        <h2 class="title">
            <a href="/Sessions/787/Provable-APIs">Provable APIs</a>
        </h2>

        <div class="entry">

            <div>


                <div>
                    Speaker: <a href="/Speakers/73/michael-l-perry">Michael L Perry</a>
                </div>


                <div>Category: Developers</div>

                <div title="Beginner">Level: 100</div>


                <div class="session-status-Accepted">Status: Accepted</div>

                <div>None</div>
                <div>None</div>


            </div>

            <p>Tool vendors like Microsoft are not the only ones who publish APIs. When we create layered software, each layer has an API that is consumed by the next one up. To ensure the quality of our software, we should try to create provable APIs. These are interfaces that guide the caller to the correct usage patterns. They help the compiler help us to verify the correctness of our code.</p>
            <p>An unhelpful API throws exceptions whenever we get something wrong. These kinds of APIs can cause stress and lead to bugs that are difficult to correct. There is a right way to call them, but there is also a wrong way. The wrong way still compiles, but it contains bugs nonetheless.</p>
            <p>We will look at a set of language features and patterns that help us to prove that our API is being used correctly. Then we'll walk through some examples of unhelpful APIs to see which of these language features we can apply. We will be in Visual Studio during most of this talk.</p>
            <p>
                * Language features and patterns<br />          o Parameters<br />          o Callbacks<br />          o Foreign keys<br />          o Factories<br />          o Constructors<br />    * Examples<br />          o Shopping service<br />          o Cache<br />          o Phone number<br />          o Connection<br />          o Shopping service revisited<br />          o Practice management system<br />
            </p>

        </div>

    </div>



    <div class="post">

        <h2 class="title">
            <a href="/Sessions/79/RAZOR-Helpers-">RAZOR Helpers </a>
        </h2>

        <div class="entry">

            <div>


                <div>
                    Speaker: <a href="/Speakers/69/jason-kergosien">Jason Kergosien</a>
                </div>


                <div>Category: Developers</div>

                <div title="Beginner">Level: 100</div>



            </div>

            <p>Test drive the powerful Razor helper methods that speed up development. </p>
            <p>We'll review the most common methods including media and social integration. We'll also cover how to create your own custom helper methods.</p>
            <p></p>

        </div>

    </div>



    <div class="post">

        <h2 class="title">
            <a href="/Sessions/799/REST-like-the-best">REST like the best</a>
        </h2>

        <div class="entry">

            <div>


                <div>
                    Speaker: <a href="/Speakers/798/amir-rajan">Amir Rajan</a>
                </div>


                <div>Category: Developers</div>

                <div title="Advanced">Level: 300</div>



            </div>

            <p>REST is a real player when it comes to providing distributed services.  Amir will show what it really means to create a REST service.  We'll start with a crash course on what REST is then take a look at how to build, consume and test them using .NET technologies.</p>

        </div>

    </div>



    <div class="post">

        <h2 class="title">
            <a href="/Sessions/104/Secrets-of-the-C-Masters">Secrets of the C# Masters</a>
        </h2>

        <div class="entry">

            <div>


                <div>
                    Speaker: <a href="/Speakers/103/matt-hinze">Matt Hinze</a>
                </div>


                <div>Category: Developers</div>

                <div title="Advanced">Level: 300</div>



            </div>

            <p>No patterns, no principles, just hacking code. In this talk C# MVP Matt Hinze demonstrates several real-world techniques used by expert C# programmers to bend our favorite language to their will. Matt scoured the open-source landscape to see how the gurus break free from the shackles of generics, take advantage of little-known language features, master reflection and transform APIs into productivity powerhouses.</p>

        </div>

    </div>


    <div class="post">

        <h2 class="title">
            <a href="/Sessions/302/Secure-Coding-Practices-in-NET-40">Secure Coding Practices in .NET 4.0</a>
        </h2>

        <div class="entry">

            <div>


                <div>
                    Speaker: <a href="/Speakers/301/ben-floyd">Ben Floyd</a>
                </div>



                <div>Category: Developers</div>

                <div title="Intermediate">Level: 200</div>



            </div>

            <p>Staying on top of security within the development processes has become paramount. The number of attacks has been increasing, and the damage caused by these attacks is becoming more severe. </p>
            <p>Come learn about the latest security features in .NET 4.0 ASP.NET, WCF, and WPF to help keep your environment and applications secure. This session will cover the major web and desktop attacks that occur today, and demonstrate ways in which we can prevent these attacks. </p>
            <p>
                This session will also cover some first steps in integrating security into the development process, such as the MIcrosoft Security Development Lifecycle (SDL).<br />
            </p>

        </div>

    </div>



    <div class="post">

        <h2 class="title">
            <a href="/Sessions/716/Security-Choices-Using-OAuth-and-SAML-in-Java">Security Choices: Using OAuth and SAML in Java</a>
        </h2>

        <div class="entry">

            <div>


                <div>
                    Speaker: <a href="/Speakers/709/dustin-talk">Dustin Talk</a>
                </div>


                <div>Category: Developers</div>

                <div title="Intermediate">Level: 200</div>



            </div>

            <p>Working on any web project requiring &quot;Security&quot; begs several questions: What framework, how secure, and how time-consuming? Whether securing an API or producing a cross domain single sign on solution, trudging through the myths, facts, and misunderstandings will help guide you to a simpler more secure implementation. In our talk, we take a look at the OAuth authentication protocol, using SAML for SSO, and how these concepts come into play when designing your authentication mechanisms.</p>

        </div>

    </div>



    <div class="post">

        <h2 class="title">
            <a href="/Sessions/790/Simplifying-Asynchronous-Programming-with-the-Microsoft-Async-CTP">Simplifying Asynchronous Programming with the Microsoft Async CTP</a>
        </h2>

        <div class="entry">

            <div>


                <div>
                    Speaker: <a href="/Speakers/788/wil-bloodworth">Wil Bloodworth</a>
                </div>


                <div>Category: Developers</div>

                <div title="Advanced">Level: 300</div>



            </div>

            <p>The Microsoft Visual Studio Async CTP proposes a new language feature in C# and VB that will make asynchronous programming very similar to synchronous programming.  Current asynchrony patterns are very disruptive to program structure which can lead to far too complex and error prone code.  After a lot of hard work the result is likely unappealing, hard to read, and probably full of bugs.  The Async CTP aims to solve all of these problems.  By the end of this session, you should have a good introduction to the Async CTP and have the ability to put native asynchrony to work in your day-to-day work life.</p>

        </div>

    </div>



    <div class="post">

        <h2 class="title">
            <a href="/Sessions/631/Simplifying-Package-Management-with-NuGet">Simplifying Package Management with NuGet</a>
        </h2>

        <div class="entry">

            <div>


                <div>
                    Speaker: <a href="/Speakers/66/casey-watson">Casey Watson</a>
                </div>


                <div>Category: Developers</div>

                <div title="Beginner">Level: 100</div>



            </div>

            <p>It's one of those headaches that you knew you had but, until now, never had a name for. It's package management. If you're a .NET developer and you'd like to take control of how you and your organization maintains, shares and uses application libraries, you owe it to yourself to take a look at NuGet, Microsoft's answer to Ruby Gems. NuGet goes beyond simply adding references to your project and allows for fully automated configuration and setup of third-party libraries directly from within Visual Studio using either the GUI or Powershell. NuGet allows you to not only search through an ever-expanding catalog of application packages but also to discover new ones that can help you and your team be more productive. In this session, we'll start by discussing package management from a high level, move on to installing, configuring and using NuGet from within the IDE and finally we'll discuss how you can build your very own NuGet packages and distribute them either through the official NuGet stream or your own private repository. By the end of the session, you should know all that you need to know to start taking advantage of this powerful and long overdue tool.</p>

        </div>

    </div>



    <div class="post">

        <h2 class="title">
            <a href="/Sessions/99/Sitefinity-Tips-from-the-Trenches">Sitefinity: Tips from the Trenches</a>
        </h2>

        <div class="entry">

            <div>


                <div>
                    Speaker: <a href="/Speakers/98/michael-russell">Michael Russell</a>
                </div>


                <div>Category: Developers</div>

                <div title="Intermediate">Level: 200</div>



            </div>

            <p>Sitefinity is still one of the fastest growing commercial CMS's out there, but unfortunately its documentation is often out of date, features and implementations change drastically from version to version, and its idea of the ideal workflow varies dramatically from what you would expect as a developer.  In other words, it's exactly like every other CMS out there.</p>
            <p>In this session, you'll learn how to:</p>
            <p>
                - Set up Sitefinity 4 to work in a team development environment<br />- Learn how to work with Sitefinity without opening up security holes<br />- Learn how to maintain and repair Sitefinity when things go wrong<br />- Learn how to architect your site for maximum flexibility
            </p>

        </div>

    </div>



    <div class="post">

        <h2 class="title">
            <a href="/Sessions/646/So-Your-Mommas-Got-Big-Data-huh">So Your Momma's Got Big... Data, huh?</a>
        </h2>

        <div class="entry">

            <div>


                <div>
                    Speaker: <a href="/Speakers/632/derek-lane">Derek Lane</a>
                </div>


                <div>Category: Developers</div>

                <div title="Intermediate">Level: 200</div>



            </div>

            <p>After a hearty but tasteful round of &quot;yo momma&quot; jokes, this presentation reveals an overview of the NoSQL movement, what problems it is intended to solve, and an introduction of the CAP Theorem. A comparison of some of the more popular options such as CouchDB, MongoDB and Cassandra will be discussed. Attendees are invited to share their experiences with these technologies, and how these experiences differ from the more common relational approach to data.</p>

        </div>

    </div>



    <div class="post">

        <h2 class="title">
            <a href="/Sessions/318/Tableau-Delivering-Self-Serve-BI">Tableau: Delivering Self-Serve BI</a>
        </h2>

        <div class="entry">

            <div>


                <div>
                    Speaker: <a href="/Speakers/316/tim-costello">Tim Costello</a>
                </div>


                <div>Category: Business Analysts</div>

                <div title="Beginner">Level: 100</div>



            </div>

            <p>Rapid-fire visual analysis. ad hoc query capability. easy interactive dashboard building. No, this insn't going to be an hour of buzzword bingo. This time we will actually deliver on the promise of self service BI. Using a visual analysis tool like Tableau we can help our users find the questions they didn't know they wanted to answer. This session will be demo heavy and will highlight best practices in data visualization and dashboard design.</p>

        </div>

    </div>



    <div class="post">

        <h2 class="title">
            <a href="/Sessions/105/TDD-The-New-Whys-and-Hows">TDD: The New Whys and Hows</a>
        </h2>

        <div class="entry">

            <div>


                <div>
                    Speaker: <a href="/Speakers/103/matt-hinze">Matt Hinze</a>
                </div>


                <div>Category: Developers</div>

                <div title="Intermediate">Level: 200</div>



            </div>

            <p>Get started with TDD on the right foot. The developer community has suffered through years of intellectually dishonest rhetoric about test-driven development. Presented as a panacea for all software woes, TDD leaders have pushed an all or nothing approach - but is their way productive or even useful?  How can we capture and utilize what's good about TDD without the burden of making a lifestyle choice? In this session for TDD beginners C# MVP Matt Hinze shares his approach to thinking about TDD and some practical mechanics that really work.  </p>

        </div>

    </div>



    <div class="post">

        <h2 class="title">
            <a href="/Sessions/64/Test-driven-Development-Achieving-Testable-Code">Test-driven Development: Achieving Testable Code</a>
        </h2>

        <div class="entry">

            <div>


                <div>
                    Speaker: <a href="/Speakers/63/david-yancey">David Yancey</a>
                </div>


                <div>Category: Developers</div>

                <div title="Intermediate">Level: 200</div>



            </div>

            <p>Test-driven Development (TDD) has proven valuable on many development projects for more than ten years. Unfortunately, even today, many teams do not practice it. They give a myriad of excuses for not making TDD a part of their everyday practice. David Yancey reviews some of the more common excuses: “There’s not enough time allotted in this project”, “It’s impossible with this code base”, “I don’t know where to start”, “TDD only works on green field development projects”, and he will demonstrate how to overcome these excuses in a team environment. David shares a proven method for becoming proficient with TDD within a project or system. Learn the steps of this method to re-factor your existing code base into testable code; add new, testable modules to existing code bases; and start new projects with TDD. With TDD as a part of your everyday practice, your team will achieve the goal of testable code with simpler designs and fewer defects. </p>
            <p></p>

        </div>

    </div>


    <div class="post">

        <h2 class="title">
            <a href="/Sessions/796/The-Net-Ninjas-Toolbelt">The .Net Ninja's Toolbelt</a>
        </h2>

        <div class="entry">

            <div>


                <div>
                    Speaker: <a href="/Speakers/791/latish">Latish</a>
                </div>



                <div>Category: Developers</div>

                <div title="Beginner">Level: 100</div>



            </div>

            <p>As developers, we all have our favorite utilities, some used occassionally and then there are others that we refuse to work without. We might not use all of them everyday, but a good developer should know his options when the need arises. In this session, we'll go through the tools, utilities and hacks that can make you much more productive as a .Net developer. </p>

        </div>

    </div>



    <div class="post">

        <h2 class="title">
            <a href="/Sessions/123/The-Creamy-Goodness-of-NuGet">The Creamy Goodness of NuGet</a>
        </h2>

        <div class="entry">

            <div>


                <div>
                    Speaker: <a href="/Speakers/122/jay-smith">Jay Smith</a>
                </div>


                <div>Category: Developers</div>

                <div title="Beginner">Level: 100</div>



            </div>

            <p>NuGet is a free, open source developer focused package management system for the .NET platform intent on simplifying the process of incorporating third party libraries into a .NET application during development.</p>
            <p>There are a large number of useful 3rd party open source libraries out there for the .NET platform, but for those not familiar with the OSS ecosystem, it can be a pain to pull these libraries into a project.</p>
            <p>Here is what you will learn:</p>
            <p>
                What is NuGet?<br />    How to add packages to your project<br />    How to update packages in your project<br />    How to host your own package repository<br />    How to create and publish your own packages<br />
            </p>

        </div>

    </div>



    <div class="post">

        <h2 class="title">
            <a href="/Sessions/101/The-DNN-Module-Crash-Course">The DNN Module Crash Course</a>
        </h2>

        <div class="entry">

            <div>


                <div>
                    Speaker: <a href="/Speakers/69/jason-kergosien">Jason Kergosien</a>
                </div>


                <div>Category: Developers</div>

                <div title="Intermediate">Level: 200</div>



            </div>

            <p>In this session, developers will learn from beginning to end how to create a DNN module from scratch.  We'll also cover the benefits of different approaches and frameworks for module development.</p>

        </div>

    </div>



    <div class="post">

        <h2 class="title">
            <a href="/Sessions/766/The-Five-Minute-App">The Five Minute App</a>
        </h2>

        <div class="entry">

            <div>


                <div>
                    Speaker: <a href="/Speakers/66/casey-watson">Casey Watson</a>
                </div>


                <div>Category: Developers</div>

                <div title="Beginner">Level: 100</div>



            </div>

            <p>Mobile development sucks. That's just a fact. Unlike web development, each platform, at least from a development perspective, is wildly different and there are no real standards defined yet. So, as a developer, what do you do? You can't sit back and watch the wave wash by. You certainly don't have the time to learn a half-dozen platforms (and languages.) Join us as we take a close look at the tools and methods that are available right now to ease the pain of mobile development. We're not just talking about one or even two platforms. We're certainly not talking about building web applications. We're talking about building &quot;meta-applications&quot; that can be rapidly interpreted and used to build a spectrum of native mobile applications using automated tools. Think &quot;one-to-many&quot; compilation. Join us as we build &quot;The Five Minute App&quot; using these tools and learn how to make mobile development suck a whole lot less.</p>

        </div>

    </div>



    <div class="post">

        <h2 class="title">
            <a href="/Sessions/722/The-Holy-Grails-Hands-on-Learning">The Holy Grails: Hands-on Learning</a>
        </h2>

        <div class="entry">

            <div>


                <div>
                    Speaker: <a href="/Speakers/421/erik-weibust">Erik Weibust</a>
                </div>


                <div>Category: Developers</div>

                <div title="Beginner">Level: 100</div>



            </div>

            <p>Grails is a Groovy-based rapid-application development platform for building web and web-service applications that run on the JVM.</p>
            <p>This session will be very &quot;hands-on&quot;.  Please bring your laptop and plan to &quot;learn while doing.&quot;  I will start with a high-level intro to Grails, and then we will start building a demo application.  By the time we are done you will have built custom domain objects, controllers, gsps, services and tag libraries.</p>

        </div>

    </div>



    <div class="post">

        <h2 class="title">
            <a href="/Sessions/903/The-What-Why-and-How-of-Client-Side-MVC-Frameworks">The What, Why and How of Client-Side MVC Frameworks</a>
        </h2>

        <div class="entry">

            <div>


                <div>
                    Speaker: <a href="/Speakers/901/eric-sowell">Eric Sowell</a>
                </div>


                <div>Category: Developers</div>

                <div title="Intermediate">Level: 200</div>



            </div>

            <p>Client-side MVC frameworks like Spine, Backbone, JavascriptMVC and SproutCore are there to help you write richer client-side web experiences. Come learn why they can help, how these frameworks work and what some of the existing options are.</p>

        </div>

    </div>



    <div class="post">

        <h2 class="title">
            <a href="/Sessions/811/To-the-cloud-Taking-your-PHP-applications-to-the-cloud-with-Windows-Azure">To the cloud! Taking your PHP applications to the cloud with Windows Azure</a>
        </h2>

        <div class="entry">

            <div>


                <div>
                    Speaker: <a href="/Speakers/70/chris-koenig">Chris Koenig</a>
                </div>


                <div>Category: Developers</div>

                <div title="Advanced">Level: 300</div>



            </div>

            <p>Join Microsoft Senior Developer Evangelist Chris Koenig for a deep-dive session on migrating your PHP/MySQL application to the Windows Azure Platform. During this talk we'll discuss the latest tools and SDKs for taking your PHP application &quot;to the cloud!&quot; including the Windows Azure SDK, the Windows Azure Command Line Tools for PHP as well as tools for migrating your MySQL database to SQL Azure and employing Windows Azure Blob and Table Storage for even more scalability.</p>

        </div>

    </div>


    <div class="post">

        <h2 class="title">
            <a href="/Sessions/89/Unit-Testing-in-SharePoint-2010">Unit Testing in SharePoint 2010</a>
        </h2>

        <div class="entry">

            <div>


                <div>
                    Speaker: <a href="/Speakers/87/chris-weldon">Chris Weldon</a>
                </div>



                <div>Category: Developers</div>

                <div title="Intermediate">Level: 200</div>



            </div>

            <p>With SharePoint 2007, it was notoriously difficult to write unit tests for your SharePoint logic. In SharePoint 2010, you'll find that not much has changed in the API and still leaves it difficult to to unit test logic dependent upon the SharePoint APIs. However, a recent free tool unveiled by Microsoft Research called Pex &amp; Moles makes unit testing both possible and easy! In this session, I will briefly demonstrate how Pex &amp; Moles works, then run through several samples of how to unit test logic that's dependent upon SharePoint 2010 logic.</p>

        </div>

    </div>



    <div class="post">

        <h2 class="title">
            <a href="/Sessions/214/Unraveling-Tangled-Code--A-Spellbinding-Tale-of-Victory-Over-Chaos">Unraveling Tangled Code – A Spellbinding Tale of Victory Over Chaos</a>
        </h2>

        <div class="entry">

            <div>


                <div>
                    Speaker: <a href="/Speakers/211/jen-mccown">Jen McCown</a>
                </div>


                <div>Category: Developers</div>

                <div title="Intermediate">Level: 200</div>



            </div>

            <p>Once upon a time, you inherited an application or a database that was filled with chaos and inconsistencies. The T-SQL code is overly complex and impossible to ken. The architecture is painful to behold, and grueling to code for. One might optimistically say that query performance is “spectacularly mediocre”. If you’re without good documentation or system architects to guide you, how do you break the curse of confusion? </p>
            <p>In this session you’ll learn several methods for conquering chaotic code, and how to seek and destroy some of the nastier coding mistakes and inefficiencies. We will break complicated queries into key pieces, turn them upside-down, and reform them into something sensible. We will vanquish major issues like data abuse and index negligence. We will restructure joins, tame subqueries, and refactor dynamic SQL. We will emerge victorious!</p>

        </div>

    </div>



    <div class="post">

        <h2 class="title">
            <a href="/Sessions/107/Use-NET-Micro-to-create-things-that-do-things">Use .NET Micro to create things that do things</a>
        </h2>

        <div class="entry">

            <div>


                <div>
                    Speaker: <a href="/Speakers/106/paul-barriere">Paul Barriere</a>
                </div>


                <div>Category: Developers</div>

                <div title="Intermediate">Level: 200</div>



            </div>

            <p>
                The .NET Micro Framework is .NET for small and resource constrained devices. It offers a complete and innovative development and execution environment that brings the productivity of modern computing tools to this class of devices. For .NET developers, this means that you can use Visual Studio 2010 to create applications that run on hardware for applications such as remote controls, robots, balloon payloads, radio modulation and more – all with the same programming model and tools. More info at www.microsoft.com/netmf<br />
            </p>

        </div>

    </div>



    <div class="post">

        <h2 class="title">
            <a href="/Sessions/393/Using-and-Extending-the-Silverlight-PivotViewer">Using and Extending the Silverlight PivotViewer</a>
        </h2>

        <div class="entry">

            <div>


                <div>
                    Speaker: <a href="/Speakers/391/tony-champion">Tony Champion</a>
                </div>


                <div>Category: Developers</div>

                <div title="Intermediate">Level: 200</div>



            </div>

            <p>The Silverlight PivotViewer is a great way to visualize your data and Silverlight 5 will be bringing a new and improved version that makes it even more powerful. This session will go over extending and customizing the PivotViewer to help improve your user's experience. We will cover both the current version as well as see the next version in action.</p>
            <p></p>

        </div>

    </div>


    <div class="post">

        <h2 class="title">
            <a href="/Sessions/783/Using-Embedded-QA-to-Build-Rock-Solid-Software">Using Embedded QA to Build Rock-Solid Software</a>
        </h2>

        <div class="entry">

            <div>


                <div>
                    Speaker: <a href="/Speakers/781/tom-dupont">Tom DuPont</a>
                </div>



                <div>Category: Project Managers</div>

                <div title="Intermediate">Level: 200</div>



            </div>

            <p>Without an automated means to collect errors from deployed applications, how can you know that your software is performing as expected? Embedded QA can be used to augment your own internal QA efforts, greatly increasing both the effectiveness of your testing and overall stability of your applications. As Jeff Atwood phrased it, &quot;If you're waiting around for users to tell you about problems with your website or application, you're only seeing a tiny fraction of all the problems that are actually occurring. The proverbial tip of the iceberg.&quot; This presentation will go over the value of Exception Driven Development, and the tools you need to gain the vision necessary to improve your applications today.</p>

        </div>

    </div>



    <div class="post">

        <h2 class="title">
            <a href="/Sessions/287/Utilizing-Patents-to-Protect-Your-Technological-Innovations">Utilizing Patents to Protect Your Technological Innovations</a>
        </h2>

        <div class="entry">

            <div>


                <div>
                    Speaker: <a href="/Speakers/286/kevin-afghani">Kevin Afghani</a>
                </div>


                <div>Category: Business Analysts</div>

                <div title="Beginner">Level: 100</div>



            </div>

            <p>This presentation, which encourages active participation and questions from the audience, covers the basics of patents, including essential tips for protecting your intellectual property using patents.  The presentation is geared toward innovators with little or no exposure to patent law.  The goal of the presentation is to teach innovators and entrepreneurs the key concepts of patent law to help them make informed decisions regarding their intellectual property in their future entrepreneurial endeavors.  The following is an agenda for the presentation:</p>
            <p>Why get a patent?</p>
            <p>What is a patent?</p>
            <p>How do you get a patent?</p>
            <p>International patent protection</p>
            <p>Practical patent tips</p>
            <p>Alternative protection: Trade secrets and software copyrights</p>
            <p>
                Questions<br />
            </p>

        </div>

    </div>


    <div class="post">

        <h2 class="title">
            <a href="/Sessions/392/Whats-New-in-Silverlight-5">What's New in Silverlight 5</a>
        </h2>

        <div class="entry">

            <div>


                <div>
                    Speaker: <a href="/Speakers/391/tony-champion">Tony Champion</a>
                </div>



                <div>Category: Developers</div>

                <div title="Beginner">Level: 100</div>



            </div>

            <p>The second half of this year will see the fifth major release of Silverlight. With it's release, Silverlight is becoming a mature platform on which to build your applications on. In this session we will cover the new features of Silverlight from databinding debugging to the new 3D API.</p>
            <p></p>

        </div>

    </div>



    <div class="post">

        <h2 class="title">
            <a href="/Sessions/115/Whats-new-in-Spring">What's new in Spring</a>
        </h2>

        <div class="entry">

            <div>


                <div>
                    Speaker: <a href="/Speakers/112/craig-walls">Craig Walls</a>
                </div>


                <div>Category: Developers</div>

                <div title="Beginner">Level: 100</div>



            </div>

            <p>It's been 7 years since Spring 1.0 was released. In that time it has gone from a modest open-source project to being a de facto standard Java application framework. Now, as Spring enters its 8th year, it continues its attack on Java complexity, packed with many new features such as:</p>
            <p>
                * First-class REST support<br />  * A new expression language<br />  * More options for annotation-driven bean wiring<br />  * Bean profiles<br />  * Declarative caching abstraction<br />  * Enhanced Java-based configuration<br />  * A new &quot;c:&quot; namespace<br />  * Unified property management<br />  * And much more
            </p>
            <p>
                In this session, I'll lead a guided tour through the latest that Spring has to offer. Whether you're a Spring veteran or a Spring newbie, there will be something new for nearly everyone.<br />
            </p>

        </div>

    </div>



    <div class="post">

        <h2 class="title">
            <a href="/Sessions/666/Windows-Phone--Cloud-Building-Great-Mobile-Apps-with-Cloud-Services-and-Windows-Azure">Windows Phone + Cloud: Building Great Mobile Apps with Cloud Services and Windows Azure</a>
        </h2>

        <div class="entry">

            <div>


                <div>
                    Speaker: <a href="/Speakers/166/eric-d-boyd">Eric D. Boyd</a>
                </div>


                <div>Category: Developers</div>

                <div title="Intermediate">Level: 200</div>



            </div>

            <p>While today’s mobile devices are incredibly powerful, there is still processing and storage limitations that can be augmented by utilizing services in the cloud. In this session, we will explore scenarios where consuming web services make sense and consider how this benefits our users. Next we will create a Windows Phone application using available Web API’s. Then we will review the Windows Azure platform and discuss how Azure fits. Finally, we will integrate our own Windows Azure services into our Windows Phone app which will result in a Cloudy Mobile App.</p>

        </div>

    </div>


</sessions>