<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<speakers>
    <div class="post">
        <h2 class="title">
            <a href="/Speakers/798/amir-rajan">Amir Rajan</a>
        </h2>

        <div class="entry">
            <table border="0" cellpadding="3" cellspacing="0">
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top">

                        <p>
                            <a href="http://amirrajan.net/">
                                <img alt="Speaker Image" border="0" src="http://improvingenterprises.com/wp-content/uploads/2010/08/people-list-rajan.jpg" title="Speaker Image" width="100" />
                            </a>
                        </p>

                    </td>
                    <td>

                        <p>Amir is a Principal Consultant with Improving Enterprises.  He is an active member of the .Net Community and has done many presentations on WCF, ASP.NET MVC, HTML5 and Silverlight.  Amir has an unwavering passion for software and is always striving to better the industry through community involvement, mentoring, and blogging.  His blog is at http://www.amirrajan.net.</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
            </table>
        </div>
    </div>



    <div class="post">
        <h2 class="title">

            <a href="/Speakers/719/arun-gupta">Arun Gupta</a>
        </h2>
        <div class="entry">
            <table border="0" cellpadding="3" cellspacing="0">
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top">

                        <p>
                            <a href="http://blogs.oracle.com/arungupta">
                                <img alt="Speaker Image" border="0" src="http://blogs.oracle.com/arungupta/resource/personal/arun-200x200.png" title="Speaker Image" width="100" />
                            </a>
                        </p>


                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Arun Gupta is a Java evangelist working at Oracle. Arun has over 15 years of experience in the software industry working in the Java(TM) platform and several web-related technologies. In his current role, he works to create and foster the community around Java EE and GlassFish. He has been with the Java EE team since its inception and contributed to all releases. Arun has extensive world wide speaking experience on myriad of topics and loves to engage with the community, customers, partners, and Java User Groups everywhere to spread the goodness of Java.</p>
                        <p>He is a prolific blogger at http://blogs.oracle.com/arungupta with over 1200 blog entries and frequent visitors from all around the world with a cumulative page visits &gt; 1.2 million. He is a passionate runner and always up for running in any part of the world. You can catch him at @arungupta.</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
            </table>
        </div>

    </div>



    <div class="post">
        <h2 class="title">
            <a href="/Speakers/301/ben-floyd">Ben Floyd</a>
        </h2>
        <div class="entry">
            <table border="0" cellpadding="3" cellspacing="0">
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top">


                        <p>
                            <a href="http://dataplex.org/blog">
                                <img alt="Speaker Image" border="0" src="http://improvingenterprises.com/wp-content/uploads/2010/09/people-detail-benfloyd.jpg" title="Speaker Image" width="100" />
                            </a>
                        </p>

                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Ben Floyd has been doing development professionally for 10 years and practicing and teaching secure coding practices for a bit longer than that. He started out in C and assembly and has moved his way through C++, PHP, Java, and a few others. </p>
                        <p>Before becoming a programmer, Ben worked as a network administrator and security analyst. Ben is a Senior Consultant with Improving Enterprises, Inc.</p>
                        <p>More information can be found at http://www.improvingenterprises.com/about/team/consultants/ben-floyd/bio/</p>
                    </td>

                </tr>
            </table>
        </div>
    </div>



    <div class="post">
        <h2 class="title">
            <a href="/Speakers/736/brian-polster">Brian Polster</a>
        </h2>
        <div class="entry">

            <table border="0" cellpadding="3" cellspacing="0">
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top">

                        <p>
                            <img alt="Speaker Image" border="0" src="/Content/Images/PhotoNotAvailable.gif" title="Speaker Image" width="100" />
                        </p>

                        <p>
                            <a href="">Blog</a>
                        </p>

                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Career IT professional with over 18 years of experience building world class software solutions.  Brian leads the Java practice at Credera and was a founding member of the Broadleaf Commerce team.</p>

                    </td>
                </tr>
            </table>
        </div>
    </div>



    <div class="post">
        <h2 class="title">
            <a href="/Speakers/182/bryan-smith">Bryan Smith</a>
        </h2>

        <div class="entry">
            <table border="0" cellpadding="3" cellspacing="0">
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top">

                        <p>
                            <img alt="Speaker Image" border="0" src="/Content/Images/PhotoNotAvailable.gif" title="Speaker Image" width="100" />
                        </p>

                        <p>
                            <a href="">Blog</a>
                        </p>

                    </td>
                    <td>

                        <p>Bryan Smith is a Database Technology Specialist with Microsoft in Dallas, Texas. Prior to joining Microsoft, Bryan served as a Senior Manager at Hitachi Consulting where he focused on the design and implementation of database solutions using Microsoft technologies.</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
            </table>
        </div>
    </div>



    <div class="post">
        <h2 class="title">

            <a href="/Speakers/66/casey-watson">Casey Watson</a>
        </h2>
        <div class="entry">
            <table border="0" cellpadding="3" cellspacing="0">
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top">

                        <p>
                            <a href="http://caseywatson.com/">
                                <img alt="Speaker Image" border="0" src="http://i.imgur.com/kpUE3.jpg" title="Speaker Image" width="100" />
                            </a>
                        </p>


                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Casey Watson is a Partner at Konverge Labs (http://konvergelabs.com/), Microsoft Certified Solution Developer, hopeless mobile development geek and proud father. For the last seven years, Casey has been focused on helping customers realize business value through the development of quality software products, primarily on the Microsoft .NET platform. As a Certified Scrum Master, Casey is a firm proponent of agile practices and deeply believes in the value of product over process. Recently his focus has been on helping companies build solid mobile presences through the use of cross-platform development tools like Konnector. While not blogging, coding, or updating his Twitter status (@_caseywatson), Casey enjoys spending time with his family and never turns down an ice cold bottle of Blue Moon.</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
            </table>
        </div>
    </div>


    <div class="post">
        <h2 class="title">
            <a href="/Speakers/976/chander-dhall">Chander Dhall</a>
        </h2>
        <div class="entry">
            <table border="0" cellpadding="3" cellspacing="0">
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top">

                        <p>
                            <img alt="Speaker Image" border="0" src="/Content/Images/PhotoNotAvailable.gif" title="Speaker Image" width="100" />
                        </p>


                        <p>
                            <a href="">Blog</a>
                        </p>

                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Chander Dhall is a professional software architect/lead developer, trainer, INETA speaker, open source contributor, community leader and organizer with more than seven years of experience in enterprise Software Development. He works in a goal oriented, technologically driven, fast paced AGILE (SCRUM) environment. He is the founder of Dallas day of dot net. He has a Master’s Degree in computer science with specialization in algorithms, principles and patterns and is focused on building high performing modular software. Chander leads the UT Dallas .NET user group and co-leads the Dallas dot net user group. Chander recently got recognized as &quot;One of the top organizers by Eventbrite. </p>
                        <p>Chander has been a featured speaker in numerous conferences and code camps all over US. He shall be presenting in UK and India this year. He has been instrumental in mentoring and training several UTD students over the period of last 2 years. </p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
            </table>

        </div>
    </div>



    <div class="post">
        <h2 class="title">
            <a href="/Speakers/714/chris-griswold">Chris Griswold</a>
        </h2>
        <div class="entry">
            <table border="0" cellpadding="3" cellspacing="0">
                <tr>

                    <td valign="top">

                        <p>
                            <a href="http://blogs.credera.com/">
                                <img alt="Speaker Image" border="0" src="/Content/Images/PhotoNotAvailable.gif" title="Speaker Image" width="100" />
                            </a>
                        </p>

                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Mr. Griswold is a Manager with Credera, a full-service business and technology consulting firm serving clients across a broad range of industries and technologies.  He has over 13 years of experience in custom software architecture design and development working with both Java and Microsoft technologies.  Since joining Credera, Chris has worked on a diverse collection of client engagements primarily focused on interpreting complex business requirements into powerful technology solutions.  These projects have included architecting and building custom .NET web applications as well as implementing and customizing Microsoft Dynamics CRM.  Chris has a B.A. degree in Computer Science from Baylor University as well as a M.S. degree in Engineering Management from Southern Methodist University.  Chris is a certified Microsoft Dynamics CRM 4.0 Technical Specialist, a Microsoft certified Business Management Solutions Specialist, and holds several other technical Microsoft certifications.</p>
                    </td>

                </tr>
            </table>
        </div>
    </div>



    <div class="post">
        <h2 class="title">
            <a href="/Speakers/70/chris-koenig">Chris Koenig</a>
        </h2>
        <div class="entry">

            <table border="0" cellpadding="3" cellspacing="0">
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top">

                        <p>
                            <a href="http://chriskoenig.net/">
                                <img alt="Speaker Image" border="0" src="http://chriskoenig.net/wp-content/uploads/2010/06/2009-11-26-Chris-Koenig-Headshot-small.jpg" title="Speaker Image" width="100" />
                            </a>
                        </p>

                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Chris Koenig is a Senior Developer Evangelist with Microsoft, based in Dallas, TX. Prior to joining Microsoft in March of 2007, Chris worked as a Senior Architect for The Capital Group in San Antonio, and as an Architect for the global solution provider Avanade. As an Architect and  consultant, Chris worked with a variety of clients from many vertical markets, ISVs and other solution providers on enterprise-class Windows and web-based applications. Today, Chris focuses on building, growing, and enhancing the developer communities in Texas, Oklahoma, Arkansas and Louisiana while specializing in Windows Phone 7 and Silverlight development.</p>

                    </td>
                </tr>
            </table>
        </div>
    </div>



    <div class="post">
        <h2 class="title">
            <a href="/Speakers/87/chris-weldon">Chris Weldon</a>
        </h2>

        <div class="entry">
            <table border="0" cellpadding="3" cellspacing="0">
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top">

                        <p>
                            <a href="http://www.chrisweldon.net/">
                                <img alt="Speaker Image" border="0" src="http://www.agiledotnet.com/wp-content/uploads/2010/10/image-1.png" title="Speaker Image" width="100" />
                            </a>
                        </p>

                    </td>
                    <td>

                        <p>Chris Weldon is a Consultant for Improving Enterprises based out of the rural sourcing office in College Station, TX. A Fightin' Texas Aggie, Chris has 10 years of software development experience with expertise in PHP and .Net. As an avid agile enthusiast, Chris has lead teams of software developers using variants of Scrum and XP, encouraging the practice of unit testing with automation and continuous integration through tools such as (N)Ant and MSBuild on a variety of different build systems including Visual Studio Team Foundation Server, Atlassian Bamboo, and countless others. He’s also played the roles of ScrumMaster, configuration manager, analyst, and product owner. Most recently, Chris has become an avid SharePoint technology enthusiast, developing unit tested SharePoint solutions for customers that leverage many parts of the .Net stack, especially WCF and WIF. </p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
            </table>
        </div>
    </div>



    <div class="post">
        <h2 class="title">

            <a href="/Speakers/1128/cory-smith">Cory Smith</a>
        </h2>
        <div class="entry">
            <table border="0" cellpadding="3" cellspacing="0">
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top">

                        <p>
                            <a href="http://www.addressof.com/">
                                <img alt="Speaker Image" border="0" src="http://profile.ak.fbcdn.net/hprofile-ak-snc4/41365_631889568_8825_n.jpg" title="Speaker Image" width="100" />
                            </a>
                        </p>


                        <p>
                            <a href="https://mvp.support.microsoft.com/profile=2B225077-B33C-4A12-BAE2-D0D984E3A350">Microsoft MVP</a>
                        </p>

                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Cory Smith maintains a .NET related blog at AddressOf.com and is very active in the .NET community.   His community involvement includes: President of the Dallas/Fort Worth DNUX group, Vice President of the Fort Worth .NET Users Group, Microsoft VBInsider member, Microsoft MVP, member of the South Central District Developer Guidance Council and a previously a member of the INETA Speakers Bureau.   A veteran developer (professionally writing software for almost 20 years) working on projects ranging anywhere from major e-commerce sites such as RadioShack.com and InterstateBatteries.com to applications that are at the heart and soul of over 4600 radio stations around the world.  His work history includes working for Tandy/RadioShack, Rare Medium, Inc., Electric Works Corp., Scott Studios Corp. and Shiny Stone Digital.</p>
                        <p> </p>
                        <p>In his spare time, Cory is also owns and operates a combative martial arts academy, coaches a MMA fight team, is an avid motorcycle enthusiast and attempts to watch every action movie ever released. </p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
            </table>

        </div>
    </div>



    <div class="post">
        <h2 class="title">
            <a href="/Speakers/112/craig-walls">Craig Walls</a>
        </h2>
        <div class="entry">
            <table border="0" cellpadding="3" cellspacing="0">
                <tr>

                    <td valign="top">

                        <p>
                            <a href="http://blog.springsource.com/author/cwalls/">
                                <img alt="Speaker Image" border="0" src="http://nofluffjuststuff.com/s/images/bio/38_Walls_20110408_053039.jpg" title="Speaker Image" width="100" />
                            </a>
                        </p>

                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Craig Walls has been professionally developing software for over 17 years (and longer than that for the pure geekiness of it). He is a senior engineer with SpringSource and is the author of Modular Java (published by Pragmatic Bookshelf) and Spring in Action and XDoclet in Action (both published by Manning). He's a zealous promoter of the Spring Framework, speaking frequently at local user groups and conferences and writing about Spring and OSGi on his blog. When he's not slinging code, Craig spends as much time as he can with his wife, two daughters, 5 birds and 3 dogs.</p>
                    </td>

                </tr>
            </table>
        </div>
    </div>



    <div class="post">
        <h2 class="title">
            <a href="/Speakers/256/d-omar-villarreal">D. Omar Villarreal</a>
        </h2>
        <div class="entry">

            <table border="0" cellpadding="3" cellspacing="0">
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top">

                        <p>
                            <img alt="Speaker Image" border="0" src="/Content/Images/PhotoNotAvailable.gif" title="Speaker Image" width="100" />
                        </p>

                        <p>
                            <a href="https://mvp.support.microsoft.com/profile/Villarreal">Microsoft MVP</a>
                        </p>

                        <p>
                            <a href="">Blog</a>
                        </p>

                    </td>
                    <td>

                        <p>
                            D. Omar Villarreal works as a Director of Governance at Epsilon Data Management, LLC. helping development teams improve their processes and procedures<br />In his most recent endeavors prior to Epsilon he worked as a Silverlight developer and before that as a Development Process Consultant Notion Solutions, Inc. helping clients improve their development processes and increase the return of their investments in Visual Studio Application Lifecycle Management tools. He is passionate about helping development teams implement better project management and development processes as well as to produce better quality software in record times through the use of the right tools; he started doing that since the early beta releases of Visual Studio Team System.<br />Omar is a Visual Studio ALM MVP, MCP, President of the Dallas .Net Users Group and has organized two Code Camps in Dallas, Tx. Omar also speaks about Visual Studio, Team Foundation Server and Silverlight at regional and local community events and when there is none of that going on, he rides his mountain bike at different off-road trails in the Dallas/Fort-Worth area.
                        </p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
            </table>
        </div>
    </div>




    <div class="post">
        <h2 class="title">
            <a href="/Speakers/63/david-yancey">David Yancey</a>
        </h2>
        <div class="entry">
            <table border="0" cellpadding="3" cellspacing="0">
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top">

                        <p>
                            <a href="http://www.david-yancey.com/">
                                <img alt="Speaker Image" border="0" src="http://www.david-yancey.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2008/11/dave.jpg" title="Speaker Image" width="100" />
                            </a>

                        </p>

                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>With 10+ years of experience as a programmer is Manager Consultant with the Enterprise Microsoft Solutions of Sogeti, Inc. Specializing in C#, .NET 4 and other Microsoft Technologies. I enjoy the challenge of finding solutions to difficult technical / design problems, often finding myself evangelizing Agile methodologies and XP practices. In addition to my work with Sogeti, I can also be found as an active member of the .NET community as a speaker, founding member of the North Texas Silverlight Group, and attendee of other User Groups in the DFW Metroplex. Outside of work and the community I enjoy spending my time with my family, including traveling, helping my wife Robin as she completes her degree in Speech &amp; Language Pathology, and spending time my 2 kids.</p>
                        <p></p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
            </table>

        </div>
    </div>



    <div class="post">
        <h2 class="title">
            <a href="/Speakers/632/derek-lane">Derek Lane</a>
        </h2>
        <div class="entry">
            <table border="0" cellpadding="3" cellspacing="0">
                <tr>

                    <td valign="top">

                        <p>
                            <img alt="Speaker Image" border="0" src="/Content/Images/PhotoNotAvailable.gif" title="Speaker Image" width="100" />
                        </p>

                        <p>
                            <a href="">Blog</a>
                        </p>

                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Derek Lane is an Enterprise Architect at Thomson Reuters. He has worn various hats in his career including mentor, coach, architect, manager, developer, trainer, methodologist and all around cool guy. Derek is a contributor to various projects as author, presenter, committer, and technical reviewer.</p>
                        <p>Derek is the Founder of both the Oklahoma City Java User Group (OKCJUG) and the Dallas/Fort Worth, Texas MicroJava User Group; and has been active as a member, presenter, and mentor for over two decades at various technology user groups across the Midwest and Southern US.</p>
                        <p>Derek can on occasion be found utilizing his background in engineering, Virtual Reality and 3D graphics to think in four or more dimensions - some of which have yet to be independently verified. When not exploring the mind numbing edge of technology, he can be found listening to Bluegrass music and watching old Kung Fu movies - a dangerous combination from any point of view.</p>
                    </td>

                </tr>
            </table>
        </div>
    </div>



    <div class="post">
        <h2 class="title">
            <a href="/Speakers/46/devlin">Devlin</a>
        </h2>
        <div class="entry">

            <table border="0" cellpadding="3" cellspacing="0">
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top">

                        <p>
                            <img alt="Speaker Image" border="0" src="/Content/Images/PhotoNotAvailable.gif" title="Speaker Image" width="100" />
                        </p>

                        <p>
                            <a href="">Blog</a>
                        </p>

                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Test</p>

                    </td>
                </tr>
            </table>
        </div>
    </div>



    <div class="post">
        <h2 class="title">
            <a href="/Speakers/709/dustin-talk">Dustin Talk</a>
        </h2>

        <div class="entry">
            <table border="0" cellpadding="3" cellspacing="0">
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top">

                        <p>
                            <a href="http://www.dustinwtalk.com/">
                                <img alt="Speaker Image" border="0" src="http://www.dustinwtalk.com/profilepic.png" title="Speaker Image" width="100" />
                            </a>
                        </p>

                    </td>
                    <td>

                        <p>Dustin Talk is a Senior Consultant with Credera. He has a B.S. and graduate degree in Computer Science from Texas A&amp;M University. Dustin has several years experience in custom web application development with a focus on security, emerging technologies, and the Spring stack. During his time with Credera, he has led and worked on many teams building various applications in Java from supply chain optimization to eCommerce implementations utilizing Broadleaf Commerce.</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
            </table>
        </div>
    </div>



    <div class="post">

        <h2 class="title">
            <a href="/Speakers/166/eric-d-boyd">Eric D. Boyd</a>
        </h2>
        <div class="entry">
            <table border="0" cellpadding="3" cellspacing="0">
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top">

                        <p>
                            <a href="http://www.ericdboyd.com/">
                                <img alt="Speaker Image" border="0" src="http://ericdboyd.com/files/2011/06/200.jpg" title="Speaker Image" width="100" />
                            </a>

                        </p>

                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Eric D. Boyd is a Director for Centare Group, Ltd. and is responsible for their Chicago business and Cloud Computing Practice. Eric began his technology career by starting a web development firm in the 90’s and has served in multiple roles since including developer, consultant, business owner and technology executive. Today, he primarily helps Fortune 500 companies with software development practices and cloud computing in the Chicago-Milwaukee area.</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
            </table>
        </div>

    </div>



    <div class="post">
        <h2 class="title">
            <a href="/Speakers/901/eric-sowell">Eric Sowell</a>
        </h2>
        <div class="entry">
            <table border="0" cellpadding="3" cellspacing="0">
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top">


                        <p>
                            <a href="http://thecodinghumanist.com/blog">
                                <img alt="Speaker Image" border="0" src="http://northdallas.net/files/headshot/headshot-esowell.jpg" title="Speaker Image" width="100" />
                            </a>
                        </p>

                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>
                            Eric Sowell is an avid developer who gets into as many technologies as he can. He is development lead at Match.com on the international platform and enjoys writing code which serves up Html millions of times on a daily basis. Eric is the father of three children and the husband of one wife. He also has fish. When not being a geek or hanging with the family, he enjoys reading, writing and doing research primarily in the realms of ancient Greek, biblical studies and early Christianity.<br />
                        </p>
                    </td>
                </tr>

            </table>
        </div>
    </div>



    <div class="post">
        <h2 class="title">
            <a href="/Speakers/421/erik-weibust">Erik Weibust</a>
        </h2>
        <div class="entry">
            <table border="0" cellpadding="3" cellspacing="0">

                <tr>
                    <td valign="top">

                        <p>
                            <a href="http://erik.weibust.net/">
                                <img alt="Speaker Image" border="0" src="http://a3.twimg.com/profile_images/105305569/IMG_0147.jpg" title="Speaker Image" width="100" />
                            </a>
                        </p>

                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>I am a Sr Architect at Credera.  I am very active in the DFW technology user group scene.  I help lead JavaMUG a DFW Java focused user group.  I help lead the DFW2GUG, a Groovy and Grails focused user group in Dallas.  I also was the founder of the Spring Dallas UG.  A group focused on promoting and educating Dallas Java developers on the Spring Framework.</p>
                        <p>I'm also proud to call myself a Fightin' Texas Aggie. Whoop!</p>
                        <p>Feel free to follow me on Twitter - @erikweibust (http://twitter.com/erikweibust)</p>

                    </td>
                </tr>
            </table>
        </div>
    </div>



    <div class="post">
        <h2 class="title">
            <a href="/Speakers/81/jacob-orshalick">Jacob Orshalick</a>
        </h2>

        <div class="entry">
            <table border="0" cellpadding="3" cellspacing="0">
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top">

                        <p>
                            <a href="http://solutionsfit.com/blog/">
                                <img alt="Speaker Image" border="0" src="http://media.linkedin.com/mpr/pub/image-1OYPKP9SuP2N58m8VhCoKX1F4B0h58U8xBEiKBlQpu2Lvfhb/jacob-orshalick.jpg" title="Speaker Image" width="100" />
                            </a>
                        </p>

                    </td>
                    <td>

                        <p>Jacob Orshalick is an independent software consultant, open source enthusiast, agile practitioner, author, and the co-founder of solutionsfit, an independent software consulting firm. He aids clients in developing cutting edge software solutions to meet business needs and actively contributes to open-source projects.  Jacob has developed software in a variety of domains including:  telecommunications, media, retail, financial, real estate, technology, and health care.</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
            </table>
        </div>
    </div>



    <div class="post">
        <h2 class="title">

            <a href="/Speakers/69/jason-kergosien">Jason Kergosien</a>
        </h2>
        <div class="entry">
            <table border="0" cellpadding="3" cellspacing="0">
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top">

                        <p>
                            <img alt="Speaker Image" border="0" src="http://openca.mp/wp-content/uploads/Jason.jpg" title="Speaker Image" width="100" />
                        </p>

                        <p>
                            <a href="">Blog</a>
                        </p>

                    </td>

                    <td>
                        <p>Jason Kergosien, Ingen Systems</p>
                        <p>Jason is CEO and lead architect of Ingen Systems. He has more than 10 years experience in the development and implementation of web strategies and architecture in varied industries, including financial services, public utilities, energy, hospitality, retail, manufacturing and high-tech. His extensive background incorporates leading companies in data management, portals and content management in Microsoft technologies. He is a 2009 recipient of the Microsoft Most Valuable Professional (MVP) Award.</p>
                        <p>Prior to founding Ingen Systems, he held positions with White Rock Networks, Covenant Church, TXU Energy, Compucom, Deloitte, Trammell Crow and Tactica Technology Group.  He leads the Dallas DotNetNuke Users Group and is a key speaker at many Microsoft and other technical conferences across the country.</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
            </table>
        </div>
    </div>


    <div class="post">
        <h2 class="title">
            <a href="/Speakers/122/jay-smith">Jay Smith</a>
        </h2>
        <div class="entry">
            <table border="0" cellpadding="3" cellspacing="0">
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top">

                        <p>
                            <a href="http://jaysmith.us/">

                                <img alt="Speaker Image" border="0" src="http://jaysmith.us/JaySmith/image.axd?picture=avatar_thumb.jpg" title="Speaker Image" width="100" />
                            </a>
                        </p>

                        <p>
                            <a href="https://mvp.support.microsoft.com/profile/Jay.Smith">Microsoft MVP</a>
                        </p>

                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Jay Smith is a Lead Programmer Analyst with Tyson Foods, Inc, based in Fayetteville, AR.  Prior to joining Tyson Foods in April 2, 2001, Jay worked as a Windows Server Engineer for Wal-Mart Stores, Inc. in Bentonville, AR.  Jay as worked on a variety of web based applications for internal use, as well as, worked with internal teams to improve team efficiency and developer practice adoption.  Jay focuses on building, growing, and enhancing the developer community in the Northwest Arkansas area while specializing in Software Architecture, Agile Practices(Scurm and Extreme Programming), and ASPNET MVC.</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>

            </table>
        </div>
    </div>



    <div class="post">
        <h2 class="title">
            <a href="/Speakers/711/jeff-hewitt">Jeff Hewitt</a>
        </h2>
        <div class="entry">
            <table border="0" cellpadding="3" cellspacing="0">

                <tr>
                    <td valign="top">

                        <p>
                            <a href="http://blogs.credera.com/">
                                <img alt="Speaker Image" border="0" src="http://www.jthewitt.com/jeffhewitt.jpg" title="Speaker Image" width="100" />
                            </a>
                        </p>

                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Jeff Hewitt is an architect with Credera. He has more than 8 years of experience in technology consulting with an emphasis in Microsoft technologies.  He spends much of his time working with SharePoint and is passionate about custom development.  Jeff lives with his wife and five children in Richardson Texas.</p>

                    </td>
                </tr>
            </table>
        </div>
    </div>



    <div class="post">
        <h2 class="title">
            <a href="/Speakers/211/jen-mccown">Jen McCown</a>
        </h2>

        <div class="entry">
            <table border="0" cellpadding="3" cellspacing="0">
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top">

                        <p>
                            <a href="http://www.midnightdba.com/Jen">
                                <img alt="Speaker Image" border="0" src="http://midnightdba.itbookworm.com/Images/Jen.jpg" title="Speaker Image" width="100" />
                            </a>
                        </p>

                        <p>
                            <a href="https://mvp.support.microsoft.com/profile=5A3C842D-4104-405C-946B-9A849F04C9C1">Microsoft MVP</a>
                        </p>


                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>
                            Jen McCown is a SQL Server developer and DBA, currently serving as the lead DBA at a state trade association in Texas. She is Senior Editor at MidnightDBA.com, where she creates training videos, the DBAs at Midnight webshow, blogs, reviews, and podcasts. She also writes for Petri IT Knowledgebase and is a forum moderator. Jen is a member, volunteer, and speaker in NTSSUG, PASS, and the PASS Women in Technology virtual chapter. She has presented at multiple SQL Saturday and 24 Hours of PASS events, PASS Summit 2010, and PASS SQLRally 2011.<br />
                        </p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
            </table>
        </div>
    </div>


    <div class="post">
        <h2 class="title">
            <a href="/Speakers/888/justin-weinberg">Justin Weinberg</a>
        </h2>
        <div class="entry">
            <table border="0" cellpadding="3" cellspacing="0">
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top">

                        <p>
                            <a href="http://www.codeconfessions.com/">

                                <img alt="Speaker Image" border="0" src="http://www.ntsilverlight.com/wp-content/uploads/2010/09/justin.jpg" title="Speaker Image" width="100" />
                            </a>
                        </p>

                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Justin Weinberg is a manager consultant with the Microsoft Enterprise practice at Sogeti and a cofounder of the North Texas Silverlight User Group.  Justin brings nearly 10 years of development experience with a focus on .NET, C#,and XAML. He is also a Microsoft Certified Solution Developer (MCSD). Justin obtained Bachelor degrees in Information Decision Systems and Economics from Carnegie Mellon University where the school colors are indeed plaid. When not working or engaging with other user groups in the community such as the XAML and ASP.NET user groups, Justin spends time with his wonderful wife and three rambunctious boys. You can read his blog at codeconfessions.com</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
            </table>

        </div>
    </div>



    <div class="post">
        <h2 class="title">
            <a href="/Speakers/286/kevin-afghani">Kevin Afghani</a>
        </h2>
        <div class="entry">
            <table border="0" cellpadding="3" cellspacing="0">
                <tr>

                    <td valign="top">

                        <p>
                            <img alt="Speaker Image" border="0" src="http://afghanilawfirm.com/images/home.png" title="Speaker Image" width="100" />
                        </p>

                        <p>
                            <a href="">Blog</a>
                        </p>

                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Kevin Afghani, founder of Afghani Law firm, has extensive experience in preparing and prosecuting patent applications in the United States and around the world.  Prior to forming Afghani Law Firm, Kevin was a patent attorney at the Dallas office of Sonnenschein, Nath &amp; Rosenthal, a leading global law firm based in Chicago.  Kevin founded Afghani Law Firm to deliver the same impeccable-quality patent services found at the world’s leading law firms, but with an increased emphasis on human contact, responsiveness, and adaptability to the needs of each client.  His carefully-crafted legal arguments and candid approach with the U.S. Patent and Trademark Office has earned Kevin a high success rate in obtaining allowed patent applications. </p>
                        <p>Among the many distinguished clients represented by Kevin are The University of Texas at Dallas, De La Rue North America, and G7 Solutions.  In addition, Kevin has developed or expanded the patent portfolios for numerous distinguished companies, including International Business Machines Corp (IBM), Kinetic Concepts, Inc., Embarq Holdings (now CenturyLink), Micro-Poise Measurement Systems, Halliburton, Independent Natural Resources, Inc., Brooks Instrument, Uniden, JMK, Schlumberger, and various start-up businesses.  He has prepared and prosecuted mechanical, electrical, computer, telecom, and business method patent applications in a wide range of technological fields, including medical devices, oil &amp; gas, financial services, agricultural machinery, textile machinery, consumer devices, measurement/calibration systems, network architecture, “green” technology, printers, and synthetic chemical compounds.</p>
                        <p>Kevin has managed the international patent portfolios for global corporations, and provided legal and strategic advice regarding their patent portfolios to ensure the broadest possible protection for their intellectual property assets.  </p>
                        <p>Prior to becoming a lawyer, Kevin researched and helped develop micro-fabrication techniques for constructing electron-emitters at the William B. Hanson Center for Space Sciences in Richardson, Texas.  Kevin also assisted in developing techniques for applying zeolite matrices to the tips of optical fibers.  While obtaining his physics degree at the University of Texas at Dallas, Kevin was awarded a National Science Foundation grant to construct an antenna for an ionosonde system at the Wallops Island, Virginia NASA facility.  He was also a technical writer for several years at Window on WallStreet, Inc. (now TradeStation Technologies, Inc.), which is one of the leading investment software and technology companies.</p>
                        <p>Kevin obtained his law degree from Tulane University, where he was the managing editor of the Tulane Journal of Technology and Intellectual Property.  He obtained his Bachelor’s degree in physics, magna cum laude, from the University of Texas at Dallas.  After completing his law degree, Kevin earned his LLM in International and European Law from the University of Amsterdam, giving him unique insight on the treaties that govern international patent prosecution.  Kevin has authored numerous publications and presentations during his career, and enjoys staying on the cutting edge of the rapidly changing field of patent law.</p>
                        <p>Presentations</p>
                        <p>•	&quot;Utilizing Intellectual Property to Protect Your Technological Innovations,&quot;  Alcatel-Lucent/AT&amp;T University Entrepreneurial Workshop, May 2011</p>
                        <p>•	&quot;Recent Developments: In re Bilski,&quot; Texas-certified CLE, November 2008</p>
                        <p>•	&quot;The Effect of Prosecution History on Related Applications,&quot; Texas-certified CLE, September 2008</p>
                        <p>•	“Software-Related Inventions Under the European Patent Convention and In the United States”, Continuing Legal Education lecture presented to Boeing, 2007</p>
                        <p>Publications</p>
                        <p>•	“Keeping it Physical: Convergence on a Physicality Requirement for Patentability of Software-Related Inventions Under the European Patent Convention and United States law,” University of Georgia Journal of Intellectual Property Law, Spring 2008 (Lead co-author)</p>
                        <p>•	“Harrods Limited v. Sixty Internet Domain Names: A Non-Expansive Expansion of the Anticybersquatting Consumer Protection Act?,” Tulane Journal of Technology and Intellectual Property, Spring 2003</p>

                    </td>
                </tr>
            </table>
        </div>
    </div>



    <div class="post">
        <h2 class="title">
            <a href="/Speakers/791/latish">Latish</a>
        </h2>

        <div class="entry">
            <table border="0" cellpadding="3" cellspacing="0">
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top">

                        <p>
                            <a href="http://www.dotnetsurfers.com/">
                                <img alt="Speaker Image" border="0" src="http://0.gravatar.com/avatar/2a40aef5d2e97619610b60b87defc38f" title="Speaker Image" width="100" />
                            </a>
                        </p>

                    </td>
                    <td>

                        <p>Latish is a .NET consultant with Improving Enterprises and very passionate about software development and solving customer problems. He also leads the Dallas C# SIG. He can be reached via his blog at http://www.dotnetsurfers.com/ or twitter (http://twitter.com/latish).</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
            </table>
        </div>
    </div>



    <div class="post">
        <h2 class="title">

            <a href="/Speakers/103/matt-hinze">Matt Hinze</a>
        </h2>
        <div class="entry">
            <table border="0" cellpadding="3" cellspacing="0">
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top">

                        <p>
                            <a href="http://mhinze.com/">
                                <img alt="Speaker Image" border="0" src="https://mvp.support.microsoft.com/profile/MvpPhoto.aspx?ID=D1FA436D-53FC-48D4-B8DB-954111265004&amp;ln=en-us" title="Speaker Image" width="100" />
                            </a>
                        </p>


                        <p>
                            <a href="https://mvp.support.microsoft.com/profile=D1FA436D-53FC-48D4-B8DB-954111265004">Microsoft MVP</a>
                        </p>

                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Matt Hinze is a programmer and software designer from Austin, TX. He has successfully delivered technical courses to software developers since 2005. Meanwhile he is a full time developer and architect working in the trenches on major software projects. Passionate about software and programming, Matt is active in the developer community and presents technical talks to community groups and at conferences. Matt is an ASPInsider and Microsoft MVP for C# and an author of ASP.NET MVC 2 in Action and the upcoming ASP.NET MVC 3 in Action. Matt works at Sogeti on a large e-commerce implementation in Round Rock, and lives in the North Austin suburbs with his wife and son.</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
            </table>
        </div>

    </div>



    <div class="post">
        <h2 class="title">
            <a href="/Speakers/73/michael-l-perry">Michael L Perry</a>
        </h2>
        <div class="entry">
            <table border="0" cellpadding="3" cellspacing="0">
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top">


                        <p>
                            <a href="http://qedcode.com/">
                                <img alt="Speaker Image" border="0" src="http://qedcode.com/extras/Perry_Headshot_Medium.jpg" title="Speaker Image" width="100" />
                            </a>
                        </p>

                        <p>
                            <a href="https://mvp.support.microsoft.com/profile=D37EE3B7-E40C-4795-8BBF-271521967A6F">Microsoft MVP</a>
                        </p>

                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Throughout his career, Michael has applied mathematical concepts to the construction of software. As a Solutions Architect at AmerisourceBergen, he applies the concepts of eventual consistency, event sourcing, and CQRS to building scalable and robust enterprise systems. He has written about the mathematical underpinnings of various algorithms in C/C++ Users Journal, Delphi Informant, and Code Magazine. Craig Shoemaker interviewed him on the Polymorphic Podcast about Update Controls, an open source project based on the mathematical concept of dependency. You can find out more at qedcode.com.</p>
                    </td>

                </tr>
            </table>
        </div>
    </div>



    <div class="post">
        <h2 class="title">
            <a href="/Speakers/98/michael-russell">Michael Russell</a>
        </h2>
        <div class="entry">

            <table border="0" cellpadding="3" cellspacing="0">
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top">

                        <p>
                            <a href="http://romsteady.blogspot.com/">
                                <img alt="Speaker Image" border="0" src="/Content/Images/PhotoNotAvailable.gif" title="Speaker Image" width="100" />
                            </a>
                        </p>

                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Director of IT at Meeting Professionals International.  Formerly QA Manager, Ritual Entertainment; Software Test Lead, Microsoft Game Studios; Developer, Layton City (Utah).</p>

                    </td>
                </tr>
            </table>
        </div>
    </div>



    <div class="post">
        <h2 class="title">
            <a href="/Speakers/82/mike-wilcox">Mike Wilcox</a>
        </h2>

        <div class="entry">
            <table border="0" cellpadding="3" cellspacing="0">
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top">

                        <p>
                            <a href="http://clubajax.org/">
                                <img alt="Speaker Image" border="0" src="http://clubajax.org/wp-content/uploads/2010/02/Mike125x150.jpg" title="Speaker Image" width="100" />
                            </a>
                        </p>

                    </td>
                    <td>

                        <p>Mike Wilcox is Director of Technology for a fast growing startup in Frisco Texas, BetterVideo™ where he is in charge of front end engineering and the online video services. Mike is a regular speaker on AJAX and other web technologies, having spoken at many conferences including the 2009 Rich Web Experience, and 2009 DallasTechFest. His open source work is on display in the Dojo Toolkit, where as a committer, he's implemented many of the multimedia technologies including the Multi-File Uploader, The audio and video components, and the vector-based DojoX Drawing.</p>
                        <p>Follow Mike on Twitter http://twitter.com/clubajax</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
            </table>
        </div>
    </div>



    <div class="post">

        <h2 class="title">
            <a href="/Speakers/946/nirav-assar">Nirav Assar</a>
        </h2>
        <div class="entry">
            <table border="0" cellpadding="3" cellspacing="0">
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top">

                        <p>
                            <a href="http://assarconsulting.blogspot.com/">
                                <img alt="Speaker Image" border="0" src="http://www.blogger.com/profile/15474798428329603952" title="Speaker Image" width="100" />
                            </a>

                        </p>

                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Nirav Assar is an independent consultant and owner of solutionsfit, a consulting firm based in the Dallas-Fort Worth Area. He has consulted on several projects in various industries, such as financial, real estate, government, and retail. His expertise is based in  several Java technologies like Grails, Groovy, Spring, and Seam. Agile philosophy is at the heart of his profession, and he enjoys sharing techniques and tools that help software people excel at their jobs. You may contact him at nirav@solutionsfit.com. View his blog at http://assarconsulting.blogspot.com/.  </p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
            </table>
        </div>

    </div>



    <div class="post">
        <h2 class="title">
            <a href="/Speakers/106/paul-barriere">Paul Barriere</a>
        </h2>
        <div class="entry">
            <table border="0" cellpadding="3" cellspacing="0">
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top">


                        <p>
                            <img alt="Speaker Image" border="0" src="/Content/Images/PhotoNotAvailable.gif" title="Speaker Image" width="100" />
                        </p>

                        <p>
                            <a href="">Blog</a>
                        </p>

                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Paul has been a software developer for over 12 years and used .NET Micro on multiple projects including a high altitude balloon project that traveled over 200 miles and climbed to an altitude of more than 96,000 feet. </p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
            </table>

        </div>
    </div>



    <div class="post">
        <h2 class="title">
            <a href="/Speakers/710/phillip-verheyden">Phillip Verheyden</a>
        </h2>
        <div class="entry">
            <table border="0" cellpadding="3" cellspacing="0">
                <tr>

                    <td valign="top">

                        <p>
                            <a href="http://www.phillipuniverse.com/">
                                <img alt="Speaker Image" border="0" src="/Content/Images/PhotoNotAvailable.gif" title="Speaker Image" width="100" />
                            </a>
                        </p>

                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Phillip Verheyden resides in Austin, Texas and is currently a consultant at Credera.  He graduated from the University of Texas at Austin with a Computer Science degree.  Phillip has a wide range of expertise across multiple technologies such as web development (both LAMP and the Java stack), server administration, cluster computing, and mobile applications.</p>
                    </td>

                </tr>
            </table>
        </div>
    </div>



    <div class="post">
        <h2 class="title">
            <a href="/Speakers/185/rob-pierry">Rob Pierry</a>
        </h2>
        <div class="entry">

            <table border="0" cellpadding="3" cellspacing="0">
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top">

                        <p>
                            <img alt="Speaker Image" border="0" src="http://capturaonline.com/images/uploads/Thumb_Rob.jpg" title="Speaker Image" width="100" />
                        </p>

                        <p>
                            <a href="">Blog</a>
                        </p>

                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Rob has taught .NET web development to mainframe programmers, built a multitude of distributed systems, helped businesses to understand the implications of IT modernization, and designed frameworks that reduce the friction of everyday development. His previous speaking engagements include the Microsoft Vista Launch, Microsoft DevCare, and Tulsa TechFest.  He has had articles published in MSDN Magazine and Visual Studio Magazine.</p>
                        <p>He is presently a Principal Consultant at Captura ( http://capturaonline.com ) - a consulting company that delivers innovative user experiences backed by scalable technology.</p>

                    </td>
                </tr>
            </table>
        </div>
    </div>



    <div class="post">
        <h2 class="title">
            <a href="/Speakers/871/rob-vettor">rob vettor</a>
        </h2>

        <div class="entry">
            <table border="0" cellpadding="3" cellspacing="0">
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top">

                        <p>
                            <img alt="Speaker Image" border="0" src="/Content/Images/PhotoNotAvailable.gif" title="Speaker Image" width="100" />
                        </p>

                        <p>
                            <a href="https://mvp.support.microsoft.com/profile=6A1D338D-71AC-4433-B2D6-A88681BE97C7">Microsoft MVP</a>
                        </p>

                        <p>
                            <a href="">Blog</a>
                        </p>

                    </td>

                    <td>
                        <p>Rob Vettor is a C# MVP, INETA Regional Speaker and senior .NET Technologist for Oz Systems. Rob has built systems for a number of corporations, including Avanade, Raytheon, American Express and Jack Henry and Associates. Rob lives in Dallas, TX, with his wife, twin sons and three dogs, and is the founder of Hands-On-Coding (http://www.hands-on-coding.net/), a user group in which attendees bring their laptops and learn .NET coding by doing.  You can contact Rob at robvettor@hotmail.com</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
            </table>
        </div>
    </div>




    <div class="post">
        <h2 class="title">
            <a href="/Speakers/751/ryan-smith">Ryan Smith</a>
        </h2>
        <div class="entry">
            <table border="0" cellpadding="3" cellspacing="0">
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top">

                        <p>
                            <img alt="Speaker Image" border="0" src="/Content/Images/PhotoNotAvailable.gif" title="Speaker Image" width="100" />
                        </p>

                        <p>
                            <a href="">Blog</a>
                        </p>


                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Front-end architect at Credera, with an emphasis on optimizing the user experience through well-crafted client-side code. Current interests include HTML5, CSS3, mobile development, and JavaScript MVC patterns.</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
            </table>
        </div>
    </div>


    <div class="post">
        <h2 class="title">
            <a href="/Speakers/241/sean-mccown">Sean McCown</a>
        </h2>
        <div class="entry">
            <table border="0" cellpadding="3" cellspacing="0">
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top">

                        <p>
                            <a href="http://www.midnightdba.com/DBARant">

                                <img alt="Speaker Image" border="0" src="/Content/Images/PhotoNotAvailable.gif" title="Speaker Image" width="100" />
                            </a>
                        </p>

                        <p>
                            <a href="https://mvp.support.microsoft.com/profile=5EED7BA6-4310-42C7-99DE-28383D17C29C">Microsoft MVP</a>
                        </p>

                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>
                            Sean McCown holds a double MCITP in SQL Server 2008 for both Administration and Development.  He is also a SQL Server MVP with over 15yrs experience in databases.  Sean is a Contributing Editor with InfoWorld Magazine and a frequent contributor to many community sites and forums.<br />Sean is also founder and co-owner of the renowned website MidnightDBA.com where he records free SQL Server training videos and co-hosts the popular webshow, DBAs@Midnight.  <br />Sean has also created content for TrainingSpot.com, TrainSignal, and moderates the Petri IT Knowledgebase SQL forums.<br />Sean also speaks a various SQLSaturday events and is a board member of his local user group, NTSSUG.<br />
                        </p>

                    </td>
                </tr>
            </table>
        </div>
    </div>



    <div class="post">
        <h2 class="title">
            <a href="/Speakers/828/shawn-weisfeld">Shawn Weisfeld</a>
        </h2>

        <div class="entry">
            <table border="0" cellpadding="3" cellspacing="0">
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top">

                        <p>
                            <a href="http://www.shawnweisfeld.com/">
                                <img alt="Speaker Image" border="0" src="http://2.gravatar.com/avatar/b585fe62863e53ab90769ae7fc2dfec9?size=100" title="Speaker Image" width="100" />
                            </a>
                        </p>

                        <p>
                            <a href="https://mvp.support.microsoft.com/profile=D7A463F8-78BB-434A-9646-0FEA8CF493DB">Microsoft MVP</a>
                        </p>


                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Shawn is passionate about building awesome line of business applications and websites with .NET technologies. He is currently a Microsoft C# MVP and founder of http://UserGroup.tv. Read his full bio at http://about.me/shawnweisfeld</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
            </table>
        </div>
    </div>


    <div class="post">
        <h2 class="title">
            <a href="/Speakers/708/thiago-silva">Thiago Silva</a>
        </h2>
        <div class="entry">
            <table border="0" cellpadding="3" cellspacing="0">
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top">

                        <p>
                            <a href="http://silvaware.net/">

                                <img alt="Speaker Image" border="0" src="https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-sDbOwubtIIM/TfJByZZWlfI/AAAAAAAAAGo/WXBNfrIvVE8/tsilva-mugshot.jpg?sz=200" title="Speaker Image" width="100" />
                            </a>
                        </p>

                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>
                            Thiago Silva is a software and business intelligence consultant, based out of Dallas Texas. He is an architect for the Microsoft practice at Credera in Dallas and has helped several clients implement SharePoint, business intelligence, and reporting solutions using .NET and SQL Server technologies.<br />Thiago is co-author of the book &quot;Professional SQL Server 2008 Reporting Services&quot; by Wrox Publishing, and contributor on the book &quot;Microsoft SQL Server Reporting Services Recipes: for Designing Expert Reports&quot;. You can visit his blog, Silvaware, at http://silvaware.net, and follow him on twitter at http://twitter.com/tafs7
                        </p>

                    </td>
                </tr>
            </table>
        </div>
    </div>



    <div class="post">
        <h2 class="title">
            <a href="/Speakers/316/tim-costello">Tim Costello</a>
        </h2>

        <div class="entry">
            <table border="0" cellpadding="3" cellspacing="0">
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top">

                        <p>
                            <a href="http://www.timcost.com/">
                                <img alt="Speaker Image" border="0" src="https://picasaweb.google.com/TimCost/Tim?authkey=Gv1sRgCK6s8_y4w7i9Vw#5601004794683197186" title="Speaker Image" width="100" />
                            </a>
                        </p>

                    </td>
                    <td>

                        <p>Tim Costello is Microsoft certified (MCITP - MCTS) business intelligence developer specializing in etl and data analytics for Interworks Inc.  Tim is an international speaker with 25 presentations in the US and Canada since January of 2010.  Tim is active in the SQL community and leads a data visualization focused user group in the Dallas area.  Tim Started working with data in Access 95 and has worked in every version of SQL Server from SQL 7 forward.</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
            </table>
        </div>
    </div>



    <div class="post">
        <h2 class="title">

            <a href="/Speakers/93/todd-stone">Todd Stone</a>
        </h2>
        <div class="entry">
            <table border="0" cellpadding="3" cellspacing="0">
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top">

                        <p>
                            <a href="http://toddastone.com/">
                                <img alt="Speaker Image" border="0" src="http://www.gravatar.com/avatar/84bfa92df0af3b10764c52f9c1deeb01.jpg" title="Speaker Image" width="100" />
                            </a>
                        </p>


                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Todd Stone is a senior software developer at HBS Systems in Dallas, TX, where he has been building web apps for smartphones and tablets.  He also works with communicating and converting data from a variety of different platforms including Windows, UNIX, LINUX, and the IBM iSeries (AS/400).</p>
                        <p>He's active in the local .NET community as President of the DFW Connected Systems User Group, member of the South Central District Developer Guidance Council, and as a speaker at local user groups and regional events.</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
            </table>
        </div>
    </div>



    <div class="post">
        <h2 class="title">
            <a href="/Speakers/781/tom-dupont">Tom DuPont</a>
        </h2>
        <div class="entry">
            <table border="0" cellpadding="3" cellspacing="0">
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top">


                        <p>
                            <a href="http://tomdupont.net/">
                                <img alt="Speaker Image" border="0" src="http://tomdupont.net/BlogEngine/image.axd?picture=2010/11/tdupont_large.png" title="Speaker Image" width="100" />
                            </a>
                        </p>

                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Tom DuPont lives in Dallas, Texas, where he is the Vice President of CodeSmith Tools, LLC. But don’t let the title fool you, Tom is a total code monkey! He specializes in .NET development with C#, ASP.NET MVC, and even that crazy JavaScript stuff. Tom has a bachelor's degree in Computer Science and Software Engineering from the University of Texas at Dallas.</p>
                        <p>In his spare time Tom enjoys long rides across the country on his motorcycle.</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>

            </table>
        </div>
    </div>



    <div class="post">
        <h2 class="title">
            <a href="/Speakers/391/tony-champion">Tony Champion</a>
        </h2>
        <div class="entry">
            <table border="0" cellpadding="3" cellspacing="0">

                <tr>
                    <td valign="top">

                        <p>
                            <a href="http://tonychampion.net/">
                                <img alt="Speaker Image" border="0" src="http://profile.ak.fbcdn.net/hprofile-ak-snc4/48983_1327209012_3754_n.jpg" title="Speaker Image" width="100" />
                            </a>
                        </p>

                        <p>
                            <a href="http://mvp.support.microsoft.com/profile/tony.champion">Microsoft MVP</a>
                        </p>

                    </td>
                    <td>

                        <p>Tony Champion is a .NET architect with over 16 years of experience developing user experiences in a breadth of technolgoies.  Currently he focuses mostly in the web space, developing applications in Silverlight, ASP.NET, ASP.NET MVC, and SharePoint.  He is also working on several WP7 applications.</p>
                        <p>This year Tony has been awarded a Silverlight MVP and Microsoft Community Contributor award.  He has been a leading member in in the North Houston .NET Users Group since 2008.  He is also a founding member of Give Camp Houston.  Tony continues to grow as a speaker in the .NET community and has been delivering talks on Silverlight and WP7 to user groups and conferences for the past two years.</p>
                        <p>
                            Tony has been president and chief architect of CDS since 2003, where they have focuses on delivering custom software solutions, consulting, and training in Microsoft technologies. <br />
                        </p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
            </table>
        </div>
    </div>




    <div class="post">
        <h2 class="title">
            <a href="/Speakers/788/wil-bloodworth">Wil Bloodworth</a>
        </h2>
        <div class="entry">
            <table border="0" cellpadding="3" cellspacing="0">
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top">

                        <p>
                            <a href="http://www.wilbloodworth.com/">
                                <img alt="Speaker Image" border="0" src="http://wilbloodworth.com/wp-content/uploads/PIWB20081212_203355_0007-Edit.jpg" title="Speaker Image" width="100" />
                            </a>

                        </p>

                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <p>Wil Bloodworth is an officer at Koverge Labs (http://KonvergeLabs.com). For the past decade or so, Wil has been focused on optimization, efficiency, and clean code.  Wil is also a Certified Scrum Master and has been working with agile practices for the last four years.  When not coding and speaking about coding, Wil is playing chess, leading photography tours across North America, and enjoying his family and friends as much as time allows.</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
            </table>
        </div>

    </div>

</speakers>