<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<feed xml:base="http://devlink.us/OData.svc/" xmlns:d="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices" xmlns:m="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/metadata" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title type="text">speakers</title>
  <id>http://devlink.us/odata.svc/speakers</id>
  <updated>2011-07-07T14:05:35Z</updated>
  <link rel="self" title="speakers" href="speakers" />
  <entry>
    <id>http://devlink.us/OData.svc/speakers(5)</id>
    <title type="text"></title>
    <updated>2011-07-07T14:05:35Z</updated>
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <link rel="edit" title="speaker" href="speakers(5)" />
    <link rel="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/related/sessions" type="application/atom+xml;type=feed" title="sessions" href="speakers(5)/sessions" />
    <category term="devlink2011Model.speaker" scheme="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/scheme" />
    <content type="application/xml">
      <m:properties>
        <d:speakerid m:type="Edm.Int32">5</d:speakerid>
        <d:firstname>Chris</d:firstname>
        <d:lastname>Williams</d:lastname>
        <d:company m:null="true" />
        <d:url></d:url>
        <d:imageurl>http://devlink.net/Portals/0/Users/171/51/1451/devlink2.jpg</d:imageurl>
        <d:bio>Chris G. Williams was abandoned at birth and raised by a pack of wild satellite feeds. Sometime around his 12th birthday he discovered you could hook a computer to a TV and he hasn't seen actual sunlight since. The "big room" is a scary place. Shortly after getting his first computer, he discovered Rogue and the rest is a series of rather unspectacular deaths. Eventually he tried his hand at creating his own roguelike game and the underdog cult favorite "Heroic Adventure"" was born. When XNA was first released, the temptation to move HA" (as his mom calls it) to Xbox 360 was too strong to resist. While HA" never actually made it to the Xbox 360, a love affair with XNA was born and he never looked back. Much like "that guy in the Wendy's commercials" Chris became an unofficial spokesperson for XNA and spent much of his time writing articles and touring around the country speaking about XNA. Eventually the mothership noticed and bestowed the coveted Microsoft MVP award on him for his efforts. Last year, he locked himself in a Starbucks bathroom for 6 months and emerged only recently as the author of Professional Windows Phone 7 Game Development (Wrox). After a quick shower, he was back on the road again talking about that which he loves most... games, game development, XNA and his collection of vintage arcade machines (current count is 14.) When not doing any of the above stuff, he can often be found in a Waffle House. He likes 'em scattered, covered and chunked.</d:bio>
        <d:twitter>chrisgwilliams</d:twitter>
      </m:properties>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>http://devlink.us/OData.svc/speakers(6)</id>
    <title type="text"></title>
    <updated>2011-07-07T14:05:35Z</updated>
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <link rel="edit" title="speaker" href="speakers(6)" />
    <link rel="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/related/sessions" type="application/atom+xml;type=feed" title="sessions" href="speakers(6)/sessions" />
    <category term="devlink2011Model.speaker" scheme="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/scheme" />
    <content type="application/xml">
      <m:properties>
        <d:speakerid m:type="Edm.Int32">6</d:speakerid>
        <d:firstname>Paul</d:firstname>
        <d:lastname>Sheriff</d:lastname>
        <d:company m:null="true" />
        <d:url>www.pdsa.com</d:url>
        <d:imageurl>http://devlink.net/Portals/0/Users/002/02/2/paulsheriff.jpeg</d:imageurl>
        <d:bio>Paul D. Sheriff is the President of PDSA, Inc. (www.pdsa.com), a Microsoft Partner in Southern California. Paul acts as the Microsoft Regional Director for Southern California assisting the local Microsoft offices with several of their events each year and being an evangalist for them. Paul has authored literally hundreds of books, webcasts, videos and articles on .NET, WPF, Silverlight, Windows Phone and SQL Server. Paul can be reached via email at PSheriff@pdsa.com. Check out Paul's new code generator 'Haystack' at www.CodeHaystack.com.</d:bio>
        <d:twitter></d:twitter>
      </m:properties>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>http://devlink.us/OData.svc/speakers(7)</id>
    <title type="text"></title>
    <updated>2011-07-07T14:05:35Z</updated>
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <link rel="edit" title="speaker" href="speakers(7)" />
    <link rel="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/related/sessions" type="application/atom+xml;type=feed" title="sessions" href="speakers(7)/sessions" />
    <category term="devlink2011Model.speaker" scheme="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/scheme" />
    <content type="application/xml">
      <m:properties>
        <d:speakerid m:type="Edm.Int32">7</d:speakerid>
        <d:firstname>Joel</d:firstname>
        <d:lastname>Cochran</d:lastname>
        <d:company m:null="true" />
        <d:url>http://www.developingfor.net</d:url>
        <d:imageurl m:null="true" />
        <d:bio>Joel Cochran is an Expression Blend MVP, an INETA Community Champion, and a Microsoft Certified Technology Specialist (MCTS) in Windows Forms and WPF. He has been developing in C# since 2003 and is a Blend fanatic and self-proclaimed "Blend Evangelist". A frequent speaker at User Groups and Code Camps, he enjoys teaching and writing about .NET and other topics. You can find him online at http://www.developingfor.net or on Twitter at http://twitter.com/joelcochran. Joel has served as the Director of Operations for Stonewall Technologies, Inc., an ISV, in Staunton, VA, since 2000.</d:bio>
        <d:twitter>joelcochran</d:twitter>
      </m:properties>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>http://devlink.us/OData.svc/speakers(8)</id>
    <title type="text"></title>
    <updated>2011-07-07T14:05:35Z</updated>
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <link rel="edit" title="speaker" href="speakers(8)" />
    <link rel="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/related/sessions" type="application/atom+xml;type=feed" title="sessions" href="speakers(8)/sessions" />
    <category term="devlink2011Model.speaker" scheme="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/scheme" />
    <content type="application/xml">
      <m:properties>
        <d:speakerid m:type="Edm.Int32">8</d:speakerid>
        <d:firstname>Wally</d:firstname>
        <d:lastname>McClure</d:lastname>
        <d:company m:null="true" />
        <d:url></d:url>
        <d:imageurl m:null="true" />
        <d:bio>Wallace B. "Wally" McClure graduated from the Georgia Institute of Technology (Georgia Tech) in 1990 with a Bachelor of Science degree in Electrical Engineering and a Master's of Science in Electrical Engineering in 1991. He has done consulting and development for such organizations as The United States Department of Education, Coca-Cola, Bechtel National, Magnatron, and Lucent Technologies, among others. Wally has been working with the .NET Framework since the first public alpha in the summer of 2000. Wally McClure specializes in building applications that have large numbers of users and large amounts of data, as well as user interface specific technologies, such as AJAX, MonoTouch on the iPhone, and now the Android. He is a Microsoft MVP, ASPInsider, member of the national INETA Speaker's Bureau, author of seven programming books, and a partner in Scalable Development, Inc. Wally authored the first book that was published for MonoTouch development for the iPhone in November, 2009. In Summer, 2010, Wally's second book on MonoTouch shipped. Currently, Wally is in the final stages of an Android programming book titled, "Professional Android Programming with MonoDroid and .NET/C#." Wally has an interest in all things mobile, including mobile apps and mobile web, and has been harassing his publisher for 10 years about mobile. It wasn't until the summer of 2009 that they relented. You can read Wally's blog at http://www.morewally.com/. Wally also co-hosts the ASP.NET Podcast. You can listen to it at http://www.aspnetpodcast.com.</d:bio>
        <d:twitter>wbm</d:twitter>
      </m:properties>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>http://devlink.us/OData.svc/speakers(9)</id>
    <title type="text"></title>
    <updated>2011-07-07T14:05:35Z</updated>
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <link rel="edit" title="speaker" href="speakers(9)" />
    <link rel="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/related/sessions" type="application/atom+xml;type=feed" title="sessions" href="speakers(9)/sessions" />
    <category term="devlink2011Model.speaker" scheme="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/scheme" />
    <content type="application/xml">
      <m:properties>
        <d:speakerid m:type="Edm.Int32">9</d:speakerid>
        <d:firstname>Rob</d:firstname>
        <d:lastname>Windsor</d:lastname>
        <d:company m:null="true" />
        <d:url></d:url>
        <d:imageurl>http://devlink.net/Portals/0/Users/185/65/1465/ObjectSharp02.jpg</d:imageurl>
        <d:bio>Rob Windsor is a developer, trainer, writer and Senior Consultant with ObjectSharp Consulting - a Microsoft Gold Partner based in Toronto, Canada. He has over fifteen years experience developing rich-client and web applications with Delphi, VB, C# and VB.NET and is currently spending a majority of his time working with SharePoint. Rob is a member of the INETA Speakers Bureau and is a regular speaker at conferences, code camps, and user groups across North America and Europe. He regularly contributes articles and videos to MSDN, TechNet, and the Pluralsight On-Demand library and is the co-author of Professional Visual Basic 2010 and .NET for Wrox. Rob is President of the Toronto Visual Basic User Group and has been recognized as a Microsoft Most Valuable Professional for his involvement in the developer community.</d:bio>
        <d:twitter>robwindsor</d:twitter>
      </m:properties>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>http://devlink.us/OData.svc/speakers(10)</id>
    <title type="text"></title>
    <updated>2011-07-07T14:05:35Z</updated>
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <link rel="edit" title="speaker" href="speakers(10)" />
    <link rel="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/related/sessions" type="application/atom+xml;type=feed" title="sessions" href="speakers(10)/sessions" />
    <category term="devlink2011Model.speaker" scheme="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/scheme" />
    <content type="application/xml">
      <m:properties>
        <d:speakerid m:type="Edm.Int32">10</d:speakerid>
        <d:firstname>Mark</d:firstname>
        <d:lastname>Rackley</d:lastname>
        <d:company m:null="true" />
        <d:url>http://www.sharepointhillbilly.com</d:url>
        <d:imageurl m:null="true" />
        <d:bio>Mark has been developing software applications for over 15 years filling the roles of Project Manager, Business Analyst, Lead Developer, and Software Architect. He has been involved in projects for such companies as Dell, Motorola, Intel and Agilent Technologies. He has worked in large corporate environments, small software start-ups, and as a consultant. Mark currently works for Juniper Strategy, LLC (http://www.juniper-strategy.com) as a Solutions Architect and SharePoint Practice Lead making key SharePoint architecture and development decisions as well as bringing the appropriate SharePoint Best Practices to his clients and customers. Mark's goal as a speaker, blogger, and author is to help every new architect and developer avoid the frustrations and brick walls he ran into while learning SharePoint.</d:bio>
        <d:twitter>mrackley</d:twitter>
      </m:properties>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>http://devlink.us/OData.svc/speakers(11)</id>
    <title type="text"></title>
    <updated>2011-07-07T14:05:35Z</updated>
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <link rel="edit" title="speaker" href="speakers(11)" />
    <link rel="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/related/sessions" type="application/atom+xml;type=feed" title="sessions" href="speakers(11)/sessions" />
    <category term="devlink2011Model.speaker" scheme="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/scheme" />
    <content type="application/xml">
      <m:properties>
        <d:speakerid m:type="Edm.Int32">11</d:speakerid>
        <d:firstname>Chris</d:firstname>
        <d:lastname>Gardner</d:lastname>
        <d:company m:null="true" />
        <d:url>http://www.tnwops.com</d:url>
        <d:imageurl m:null="true" />
        <d:bio>Chris Gardner is the Senior Software Engineer and Architect for T &amp; W Operations, L.L.C. Tortured by years of contracts that valued buzzwords over results, Chris has developed a true passion for finding solutions that fit the problem, not the status quo. Chris received his B.S. in Mathematics and B.A. in Philosophy from the University of Alabama in Huntsville and is currently a Microsoft Certified Professional Developer, Information Technology Professional and Trainer.</d:bio>
        <d:twitter>freestylecoder</d:twitter>
      </m:properties>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>http://devlink.us/OData.svc/speakers(12)</id>
    <title type="text"></title>
    <updated>2011-07-07T14:05:35Z</updated>
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <link rel="edit" title="speaker" href="speakers(12)" />
    <link rel="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/related/sessions" type="application/atom+xml;type=feed" title="sessions" href="speakers(12)/sessions" />
    <category term="devlink2011Model.speaker" scheme="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/scheme" />
    <content type="application/xml">
      <m:properties>
        <d:speakerid m:type="Edm.Int32">12</d:speakerid>
        <d:firstname>Daniel</d:firstname>
        <d:lastname>Mohl</d:lastname>
        <d:company m:null="true" />
        <d:url></d:url>
        <d:imageurl>http://devlink.net/Portals/0/Users/079/35/335/dan_twitterpic.jpg</d:imageurl>
        <d:bio>Daniel Mohl is a professional software engineer/architect whose interests include understanding the intricacies of various programming languages, enterprise application architecture, and how to bridge the gap between business and technology. He is a C# MVP, F# Insider, blogger, speaker, event organizer, and an application architect at Deloitte. He works with F#, C#, Erlang, ASP.NET MVC, WPF, Silverlight, WP7, WCF, RabbitMQ, CouchDB, SQL Server, etc. You can follow him on twitter at www.twitter.com/dmohl. You can view his blog at blog.danielmohl.com.</d:bio>
        <d:twitter>dmohl</d:twitter>
      </m:properties>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>http://devlink.us/OData.svc/speakers(13)</id>
    <title type="text"></title>
    <updated>2011-07-07T14:05:35Z</updated>
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <link rel="edit" title="speaker" href="speakers(13)" />
    <link rel="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/related/sessions" type="application/atom+xml;type=feed" title="sessions" href="speakers(13)/sessions" />
    <category term="devlink2011Model.speaker" scheme="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/scheme" />
    <content type="application/xml">
      <m:properties>
        <d:speakerid m:type="Edm.Int32">13</d:speakerid>
        <d:firstname>Rod</d:firstname>
        <d:lastname>Paddock</d:lastname>
        <d:company m:null="true" />
        <d:url></d:url>
        <d:imageurl m:null="true" />
        <d:bio>Rod Paddock founded Dash Point Software, Inc. in 2001 to develop high quality custom software solutions. With over 20+ Rod's current and past clients include: Six Flags, First Premier Bank, Microsoft, Calamos Investments, The US Coast Guard and US Navy. Along with developing software Rod is a well know author and conference speaker. Beginning in 1995 Rod has given talks, training sessions and keynotes in The United States, Canada and Europe. Rod was made an MSDN Canada speaker in 2004 and is currently a Microsoft VB.NET MVP. Rod is has been Editor in Chief of Code Magazine since 2001.</d:bio>
        <d:twitter>rodpaddock</d:twitter>
      </m:properties>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>http://devlink.us/OData.svc/speakers(14)</id>
    <title type="text"></title>
    <updated>2011-07-07T14:05:35Z</updated>
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <link rel="edit" title="speaker" href="speakers(14)" />
    <link rel="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/related/sessions" type="application/atom+xml;type=feed" title="sessions" href="speakers(14)/sessions" />
    <category term="devlink2011Model.speaker" scheme="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/scheme" />
    <content type="application/xml">
      <m:properties>
        <d:speakerid m:type="Edm.Int32">14</d:speakerid>
        <d:firstname>Geoff</d:firstname>
        <d:lastname>Varosky</d:lastname>
        <d:company m:null="true" />
        <d:url></d:url>
        <d:imageurl m:null="true" />
        <d:bio>Geoff Varosky is the Director of Development and Evangelism for Grace-Hunt, LLC (www.grace-hunt.com), a Microsoft Gold Partner focusing on SharePoint and Dynamics Solutions based out of Hudson, MA. He has been architecting and developing web based applications for over 13 years, and has been working with SharePoint for the past 6 years. Geoff is an active member of the SharePoint community, Co-Founder and Co-Organizer of the Boston Area SharePoint Users Group (www.bostonsharepointug.org), co-organizer for SharePoint Saturday Boston (www.sharepointsaturday.org/boston) and speaks regularly at SharePoint events and user groups, including the SharePoint Best Practices 2010 Conference and the SharePoint Technology Conference. He also maintains a blog on SharePoint at www.geoffvarosky.com</d:bio>
        <d:twitter>gvaro</d:twitter>
      </m:properties>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>http://devlink.us/OData.svc/speakers(16)</id>
    <title type="text"></title>
    <updated>2011-07-07T14:05:35Z</updated>
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <link rel="edit" title="speaker" href="speakers(16)" />
    <link rel="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/related/sessions" type="application/atom+xml;type=feed" title="sessions" href="speakers(16)/sessions" />
    <category term="devlink2011Model.speaker" scheme="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/scheme" />
    <content type="application/xml">
      <m:properties>
        <d:speakerid m:type="Edm.Int32">16</d:speakerid>
        <d:firstname>Michael</d:firstname>
        <d:lastname>Norton</d:lastname>
        <d:company m:null="true" />
        <d:url>http://www.docondev.com/</d:url>
        <d:imageurl>http://devlink.net/Portals/0/Users/214/94/1494/doc_presentation.jpg</d:imageurl>
        <d:bio>Michael Norton (doc) is an Agile Coach and a partner with LeanDog living in Wadsworth, OH. Michael's experience covers a wide range of development topics. Michael declares expertise in no single language or methodology and is immediately suspicious of anyone who declares such expertise. Michael is passionate about Software Craftsmanship, assisting developers to improve their career, and helping teams deliver.</d:bio>
        <d:twitter>DocOnDev</d:twitter>
      </m:properties>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>http://devlink.us/OData.svc/speakers(17)</id>
    <title type="text"></title>
    <updated>2011-07-07T14:05:35Z</updated>
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <link rel="edit" title="speaker" href="speakers(17)" />
    <link rel="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/related/sessions" type="application/atom+xml;type=feed" title="sessions" href="speakers(17)/sessions" />
    <category term="devlink2011Model.speaker" scheme="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/scheme" />
    <content type="application/xml">
      <m:properties>
        <d:speakerid m:type="Edm.Int32">17</d:speakerid>
        <d:firstname>John</d:firstname>
        <d:lastname>Petersen</d:lastname>
        <d:company m:null="true" />
        <d:url>johnvpetersen.com</d:url>
        <d:imageurl>http://devlink.net/Portals/0/Users/220/32/732/jvp.jpg</d:imageurl>
        <d:bio>I've been developing software for 20 years, starting with dBase, Clipper and FoxBase + thereafter, migrating to FoxPro and Visual FoxPro and Visual Basic. Other areas of concentration include Oracle and SQL Server - versions 6-2008. From 1995 to 2001, I was a Microsoft Visual FoxPro MVP. Today, my emphasis is on ASP MVC .NET applications. I am a current Microsoft ASP .NET MVP as well as being an ASPInsider. Today, I consult for one of the most prevalent web properties around today: YellowBook.com. As part of their web team, I am responsible for developing new and maintaining existing features into this MVC-based website. Publishing: In 1999, I wrote the definitive whitepaper on ADO for VFP Developers. In 2002, I wrote the Absolute Beginner's Guide to Databases for Que Publishing. I was a co-author of Visual FoxPro Enterprise Development from Prima Publishing with Rod Paddock, Ron Talmadge and Eric Ranft. I was also a co-author of Visual Basic Web Development from Prima Publishing with Rod Paddock and Richard Campbell. Education - B.S Business Administration – Mansfield University - M.B.A. – Information Systems – Saint Joseph's University - J.D. – Rutgers University School of Law (Camden) In 2004, I graduated from the Rutgers University School of Law with a Juris Doctor Degree. I passed the Pennsylvania and New Jersey Bar exams and was in private practice for several years – concentrating transactional and general business law (contracts, copyrights, trademarks, independent contractor agreements, NDA's, intellectual property and mergers and acquisitions.</d:bio>
        <d:twitter>johnvpetersen</d:twitter>
      </m:properties>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>http://devlink.us/OData.svc/speakers(18)</id>
    <title type="text"></title>
    <updated>2011-07-07T14:05:35Z</updated>
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <link rel="edit" title="speaker" href="speakers(18)" />
    <link rel="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/related/sessions" type="application/atom+xml;type=feed" title="sessions" href="speakers(18)/sessions" />
    <category term="devlink2011Model.speaker" scheme="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/scheme" />
    <content type="application/xml">
      <m:properties>
        <d:speakerid m:type="Edm.Int32">18</d:speakerid>
        <d:firstname>Laura</d:firstname>
        <d:lastname>Rose</d:lastname>
        <d:company m:null="true" />
        <d:url>www.RoseCoaching.info</d:url>
        <d:imageurl m:null="true" />
        <d:bio>About the author Laura is a certified efficiency and business coach. Laura offers one-on-one career and life coaching, small group coaching, seminars and workshops. She has been in the software and testing industry for over 20 years. She's worked with such international companies as IBM, Ericsson, Staples, Fidelity Investments and Sogeti in various client advocacy and project management roles. The techniques she uses in her business coaching and client advocacy work saved these companies both time and money, which resulted in on-time, quality product delivery with higher client satisfaction. Laura now uses her client focus, project, quality and people management skills in her business and personal life coaching career. As a personal life coach, she helps people integrate their goals and dreams into their everyday lives. Laura uses creative and practical tools to help her clients realize what really matters to them in their professional careers as well as personal development. They then follow-through with project and time management techniques to create the reality they really want. You can learn more about her at www.RoseCoaching.info and contact her at LauraRose@RoseCoaching.info</d:bio>
        <d:twitter></d:twitter>
      </m:properties>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>http://devlink.us/OData.svc/speakers(19)</id>
    <title type="text"></title>
    <updated>2011-07-07T14:05:35Z</updated>
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <link rel="edit" title="speaker" href="speakers(19)" />
    <link rel="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/related/sessions" type="application/atom+xml;type=feed" title="sessions" href="speakers(19)/sessions" />
    <category term="devlink2011Model.speaker" scheme="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/scheme" />
    <content type="application/xml">
      <m:properties>
        <d:speakerid m:type="Edm.Int32">19</d:speakerid>
        <d:firstname>Robert</d:firstname>
        <d:lastname>Cain</d:lastname>
        <d:company m:null="true" />
        <d:url>http://arcanecode.com</d:url>
        <d:imageurl m:null="true" />
        <d:bio>Robert C. Cain is a Microsoft MVP in SQL Development, MCTS certified in BI, and works as a Senior Business Intelligence Architect for ComFrame. He is also a technical contributor to Plurasight Training, and co-author of the book "SQL Server MVP Deep Dives". Robert has over 20 years experience in the IT field, working in a variety of fields ranging from manufacturing to telecommunications to nuclear power. He maintains the popular blog http://arcanecode.com.</d:bio>
        <d:twitter>arcanecode</d:twitter>
      </m:properties>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>http://devlink.us/OData.svc/speakers(20)</id>
    <title type="text"></title>
    <updated>2011-07-07T14:05:35Z</updated>
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <link rel="edit" title="speaker" href="speakers(20)" />
    <link rel="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/related/sessions" type="application/atom+xml;type=feed" title="sessions" href="speakers(20)/sessions" />
    <category term="devlink2011Model.speaker" scheme="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/scheme" />
    <content type="application/xml">
      <m:properties>
        <d:speakerid m:type="Edm.Int32">20</d:speakerid>
        <d:firstname>Stacie</d:firstname>
        <d:lastname>Garlieb</d:lastname>
        <d:company m:null="true" />
        <d:url></d:url>
        <d:imageurl>http://devlink.net/Portals/0/Users/209/89/1489/Stacie%20Garlieb%20Picture%202.JPG</d:imageurl>
        <d:bio>Stacie Garlieb Bio Stacie Garlieb is the President of Successful Impressions, LLC which assists students and working professionals with career search processes and skills. She has been featured on NBC television and KFYI radio during morning and evening news with resume, interview, and career skill tips. In partnership with University of Phoenix, Stacie is the creator and presenter for 'Career Workshop Series' on resume building, interview preparation, interview skills, and 're-careering' and transition in the workforce. Stacie developed and presented three sessions for the 'Build Your Career Event' (Career Builder/University of Phoenix), and was a featured seminar speaker at the Arizona Women's Expo. She will be the career skills speaker for a second year at the American Marketing Association International Conference in New Orleans. Stacie also presented interview skills sessions at the Jobs for AZ Graduates Career Development Conference and Reinvent Your Future 2010: Career Builder Job Fair. She was invited to judge at the Jobs for America's Graduates National Leadership Conference. Her career search tips and interview skills advice have been published in Career Builder, national sorority and alumni publications. As the author of the 'Career Search Skills Series' books available on Amazon and college bookstores, she collaborated with other hiring managers to create generation specific guides to help people navigate the job search process. Stacie is currently also featured as an expert as the Phoenix Career Transition Examiner at examiner.com and as the Career Planning Expert for College Parenting. Through group presentations and one-on-one coaching on all career search related topics, she has worked with public and private college students nationally since 1991. She has consulted to American Marketing Association, business fraternities, Greek Life chapters, and other student organizations at private and public institutions regarding career search processes and interview techniques. To expand practical work experiences for collegiates, she has created internship programs with national and local businesses and coordinates recruitment for the positions. Over more than twenty years, she has worked for Fortune 500 organizations in sales, marketing, and management positions. After graduating in 1988 from Arizona State University with a B.S. in Sociology, Stacie moved to San Francisco, and as a Regional Manager with Bristol-Myers Squibb consumer products, she recruited and managed college graduates for entry-level sales, merchandising, and management training positions. Stacie was invited by California State Sacramento and University of the Pacific to act as a Career Consultant to the career services departments. She developed the Career Fair Training Program for University of the Pacific, and assisted in writing the "Career Services Interview Skills" guide. In management roles with The Pillsbury Company, a division of Grand Metropolitan, she recruited and coached interns and entry-level sales representatives. Once returning to Arizona in marketing with Frito-Lay, Inc., a division of PepsiCo, Stacie assisted in the national MBA recruitment program for sales and marketing.</d:bio>
        <d:twitter></d:twitter>
      </m:properties>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>http://devlink.us/OData.svc/speakers(21)</id>
    <title type="text"></title>
    <updated>2011-07-07T14:05:35Z</updated>
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <link rel="edit" title="speaker" href="speakers(21)" />
    <link rel="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/related/sessions" type="application/atom+xml;type=feed" title="sessions" href="speakers(21)/sessions" />
    <category term="devlink2011Model.speaker" scheme="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/scheme" />
    <content type="application/xml">
      <m:properties>
        <d:speakerid m:type="Edm.Int32">21</d:speakerid>
        <d:firstname>Brad</d:firstname>
        <d:lastname>McGehee</d:lastname>
        <d:company m:null="true" />
        <d:url>http://www.bradmcgehee.com</d:url>
        <d:imageurl>http://devlink.net/Portals/0/Users/159/59/159/brad_mcgehee_115x130.jpg</d:imageurl>
        <d:bio>Brad M. McGehee is a MCSE+I, MCSD, and MCT (former) with a Bachelor's degree in Economics and a Masters in Business Administration. Currently the Director of DBA Education for Red Gate Software, Brad is an accomplished Microsoft SQL Server MVP with over 16 years SQL Server experience, over 7 years training experience, and has been involved in the industry since 1982. Brad is a frequent speaker at SQL PASS, European PASS, SQL Server Connections, SQLTeach, devLINK, SQLBits, SQL Saturdays, TechFests, Code Camps, SQL Server user groups, and other industry seminars, where he shares his 16 years' cumulative knowledge and experience. In 2009, Brad made 33 public presentations to a total of 1,853 attendees, in six different countries. In 2010, Brad made 31 public presentations to a total of 3,156 attendees in two different countries. Brad was the founder of the popular community site SQL-Server-Performance.Com, and operated it from 2000 through 2006, where he wrote over one million words on SQL Server topics. A well-respected and trusted name in SQL Server literature, Brad is the author or co-author of more than 15 technical books and over 275 published articles. His most recent books include How to Become an Exceptional DBA (2nd Edition), Brad's Sure Guide to SQL Server 2008: The Top Ten New Features for DBAs, Mastering SQL Server Profiler, and Brad's Sure Guide to SQL Server Maintenance Plans. These books are available free in PDF format at: http://www.sqlservercentral.com/Books/. He blogs at www.bradmcgehee.com.</d:bio>
        <d:twitter>bradmcgehee</d:twitter>
      </m:properties>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>http://devlink.us/OData.svc/speakers(22)</id>
    <title type="text"></title>
    <updated>2011-07-07T14:05:35Z</updated>
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <link rel="edit" title="speaker" href="speakers(22)" />
    <link rel="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/related/sessions" type="application/atom+xml;type=feed" title="sessions" href="speakers(22)/sessions" />
    <category term="devlink2011Model.speaker" scheme="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/scheme" />
    <content type="application/xml">
      <m:properties>
        <d:speakerid m:type="Edm.Int32">22</d:speakerid>
        <d:firstname>Daniel</d:firstname>
        <d:lastname>Norton</d:lastname>
        <d:company m:null="true" />
        <d:url>framewreck.net</d:url>
        <d:imageurl>http://devlink.net/Portals/0/Users/191/71/1471/DanMugshot2011.JPG</d:imageurl>
        <d:bio>Daniel is the lead iOS developer at Firefly Logic. He has been building iOS apps for clients since the first public release of the iPhone SDK. Preceding that, Daniel has over a decade of Microsoft experience, primarily with C# and .NET. Daniel has presented iOS development topics at devLink for three years.</d:bio>
        <d:twitter>daniel_norton</d:twitter>
      </m:properties>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>http://devlink.us/OData.svc/speakers(24)</id>
    <title type="text"></title>
    <updated>2011-07-07T14:05:35Z</updated>
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <link rel="edit" title="speaker" href="speakers(24)" />
    <link rel="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/related/sessions" type="application/atom+xml;type=feed" title="sessions" href="speakers(24)/sessions" />
    <category term="devlink2011Model.speaker" scheme="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/scheme" />
    <content type="application/xml">
      <m:properties>
        <d:speakerid m:type="Edm.Int32">24</d:speakerid>
        <d:firstname>Todd</d:firstname>
        <d:lastname>Anglin</d:lastname>
        <d:company m:null="true" />
        <d:url>telerikwatch.com</d:url>
        <d:imageurl>http://devlink.net/Portals/0/Users/085/65/1365/ToddAnglin-BioPic-150_g.jpg</d:imageurl>
        <d:bio>Todd Anglin is Chief Evangelist for Telerik, a leading vendor of development, team productivity, and automated testing tools, as well as UI components and content management solutions for Microsoft .NET. Before joining Telerik, he worked for a large Fortune 200 financial services company IT shop where he learned the way of the "Enterprise" - big budgets, big projects, legacy systems, and incessant measurement. He now leverages this Enterprise experience at Telerik to create tools that help software development teams every day to be more productive and to deliver reliable applications on time and under budget. Todd is an active author and speaker in the .NET community, focusing on web development technologies, a Microsoft MVP, ASP Insider, founder and President of the North Houston .NET Users Group, and an O'Reilly author.</d:bio>
        <d:twitter>toddanglin</d:twitter>
      </m:properties>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>http://devlink.us/OData.svc/speakers(25)</id>
    <title type="text"></title>
    <updated>2011-07-07T14:05:35Z</updated>
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <link rel="edit" title="speaker" href="speakers(25)" />
    <link rel="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/related/sessions" type="application/atom+xml;type=feed" title="sessions" href="speakers(25)/sessions" />
    <category term="devlink2011Model.speaker" scheme="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/scheme" />
    <content type="application/xml">
      <m:properties>
        <d:speakerid m:type="Edm.Int32">25</d:speakerid>
        <d:firstname>Matthew</d:firstname>
        <d:lastname>Groves</d:lastname>
        <d:company m:null="true" />
        <d:url>http://mgroves.com</d:url>
        <d:imageurl m:null="true" />
        <d:bio>Matthew D. Groves is a guy who loves to code. It doesn't matter if it's "enterprisey" C# apps, cool jQuery stuff, contributing to OSS, or rolling up his sleeves to dig into some PHP. He has been coding professionally ever since he wrote a QuickBASIC point-of-sale app for his parent's pizza shop back in the 90s. He currently works from home on the Telligent Analytics product team, and loves spending time with his wife and 2 kids, watching the Cincinnati Reds, and getting involved in the developer community. He has a BS in Computer Science, an MBA, a PMP certification, and has experience in education, consulting, and product development.</d:bio>
        <d:twitter>mgroves</d:twitter>
      </m:properties>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>http://devlink.us/OData.svc/speakers(26)</id>
    <title type="text"></title>
    <updated>2011-07-07T14:05:35Z</updated>
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <link rel="edit" title="speaker" href="speakers(26)" />
    <link rel="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/related/sessions" type="application/atom+xml;type=feed" title="sessions" href="speakers(26)/sessions" />
    <category term="devlink2011Model.speaker" scheme="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/scheme" />
    <content type="application/xml">
      <m:properties>
        <d:speakerid m:type="Edm.Int32">26</d:speakerid>
        <d:firstname>Philip</d:firstname>
        <d:lastname>Japikse</d:lastname>
        <d:company m:null="true" />
        <d:url>www.skimedic.com/blog</d:url>
        <d:imageurl>http://devlink.net/Portals/0/Users/221/01/1501/Phil_Japikse.jpg</d:imageurl>
        <d:bio>Phil Japikse has been working with .Net since the first betas, and developing software for over 20 years. Phil is a Microsoft MVP and also holds MCSD, MCDBA, CSM, and CSP certifications. Phil is an international speaker and a passionate member of the developer community, speaking at events all around the world as well as serving as the Lead Director for the Cincinnati .Net User's Group. Phil works as the Patterns and Practices Evangelist for Telerik (www.telerik.com), is a Firefighter/Paramedic, and a volunteer for the Ski Patrol. You can follow Phil on twitter via www.twitter.com/skimedic and read his blog at www.skimedic.com/blog.</d:bio>
        <d:twitter>skimedic</d:twitter>
      </m:properties>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>http://devlink.us/OData.svc/speakers(27)</id>
    <title type="text"></title>
    <updated>2011-07-07T14:05:35Z</updated>
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <link rel="edit" title="speaker" href="speakers(27)" />
    <link rel="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/related/sessions" type="application/atom+xml;type=feed" title="sessions" href="speakers(27)/sessions" />
    <category term="devlink2011Model.speaker" scheme="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/scheme" />
    <content type="application/xml">
      <m:properties>
        <d:speakerid m:type="Edm.Int32">27</d:speakerid>
        <d:firstname>Jeremy</d:firstname>
        <d:lastname>Likness</d:lastname>
        <d:company m:null="true" />
        <d:url>http://csharperimage.jeremylikness.com</d:url>
        <d:imageurl>http://devlink.net/Portals/0/Users/202/82/1482/jeremy400.PNG</d:imageurl>
        <d:bio>Jeremy Likness is a Senior Consultant for Wintellect with 15 years of experience developing enterprise applications. He has worked with software in multiple verticals ranging from insurance, health and wellness, supply chain management, and mobility. His primary focus for the past decade has been building highly scalable web-based solutions using the Microsoft technology stack. Prior to Wintellect, Jeremy was Director of Information Technology and served as development manager and architect for AirWatch, LLC, where he helped the company grow and solidify its position as one of the leading wireless technology solution providers in the United States by managing the development of their product portfolio that includes public HotSpot solutions and a management console for enterprise grade wireless networks, mobile devices, and their consumers. A fluent Spanish speaker, Jeremy served as Director of Information Technology for Hispanicare, where he architected a multi-lingual content management system for the company's Hispanic-focused online diet program. Jeremy accepted his role there after serving as Development Manager for Manhattan Associates, a software company that provides supply chain management solutions. Jeremy has a passion for fitness and owned his own health and wellness company for several years when he authored an internationally selling book focused on lifestyle changes after losing 65 pounds. He has produced online audio programs, CD series, and toured the country presenting seminars designed to empower people to lose weight after he obtained his certifications as a Fitness Trainer and Specialist in Performance Nutrition. Jeremy enjoys running, hiking, and weight lifting, but above all spending time with his wife and daughter when he is not glued to his computer screen.</d:bio>
        <d:twitter>JeremyLikness</d:twitter>
      </m:properties>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>http://devlink.us/OData.svc/speakers(28)</id>
    <title type="text"></title>
    <updated>2011-07-07T14:05:35Z</updated>
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <link rel="edit" title="speaker" href="speakers(28)" />
    <link rel="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/related/sessions" type="application/atom+xml;type=feed" title="sessions" href="speakers(28)/sessions" />
    <category term="devlink2011Model.speaker" scheme="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/scheme" />
    <content type="application/xml">
      <m:properties>
        <d:speakerid m:type="Edm.Int32">28</d:speakerid>
        <d:firstname>Rich</d:firstname>
        <d:lastname>Dudley</d:lastname>
        <d:company m:null="true" />
        <d:url></d:url>
        <d:imageurl m:null="true" />
        <d:bio>Rich Dudley is a former scientist, but these days instead of studying organisms you'll find him working with Microsoft Visual Studio. With over 10 years of enterprise development experience, Rich has written articles and given talks relating to ASP.NET, SQL, XML, Windows Phone 7 and Azure. Rich has been working with Azure since the early beta days, with Windows Phone 7 since before you could leave one in a bar, and is co-author of "Microsoft Azure: Enterprise Application Development" from Packt Publishing. As a Technical Evangelist for ComponentOne, you'll find Rich at your local user group event or tradeshow or blogging online. His passion for development is evident in his work, whether it's a demonstration, talk, or sample project. Follow Rich's blog at http://c1.ms/c1_richd, or on Twitter at http://twitter.com/#"/rj_dudley.</d:bio>
        <d:twitter>rj_dudley</d:twitter>
      </m:properties>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>http://devlink.us/OData.svc/speakers(29)</id>
    <title type="text"></title>
    <updated>2011-07-07T14:05:35Z</updated>
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <link rel="edit" title="speaker" href="speakers(29)" />
    <link rel="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/related/sessions" type="application/atom+xml;type=feed" title="sessions" href="speakers(29)/sessions" />
    <category term="devlink2011Model.speaker" scheme="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/scheme" />
    <content type="application/xml">
      <m:properties>
        <d:speakerid m:type="Edm.Int32">29</d:speakerid>
        <d:firstname>Daniel</d:firstname>
        <d:lastname>Evans</d:lastname>
        <d:company m:null="true" />
        <d:url></d:url>
        <d:imageurl m:null="true" />
        <d:bio>Dan Evans is a Senior Group Manager / Technical Lead with the Avanade South Region specializing in Business Intelligence solutions. In recent years, Dan has focused on enterprise information management as it relates to data strategy, data governance, competency centers, service-oriented architectures and enterprise performance management. Dan has broad expertise and experience architecting and delivering complex information solutions across a various industries. He has related experience in full information lifecycle design, development and delivery utilizing both onshore and offshore models Dan received a Bachelor of Engineering in Computer Science from University of Alabama in Tuscaloosa. He also holds a Certified Business Intelligence Professional (CBIP) certification with mastery in leadership and management, data analysis and design, business analytics and data integration.</d:bio>
        <d:twitter></d:twitter>
      </m:properties>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>http://devlink.us/OData.svc/speakers(30)</id>
    <title type="text"></title>
    <updated>2011-07-07T14:05:35Z</updated>
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <link rel="edit" title="speaker" href="speakers(30)" />
    <link rel="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/related/sessions" type="application/atom+xml;type=feed" title="sessions" href="speakers(30)/sessions" />
    <category term="devlink2011Model.speaker" scheme="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/scheme" />
    <content type="application/xml">
      <m:properties>
        <d:speakerid m:type="Edm.Int32">30</d:speakerid>
        <d:firstname>Matt</d:firstname>
        <d:lastname>Casto</d:lastname>
        <d:company m:null="true" />
        <d:url></d:url>
        <d:imageurl>http://devlink.net/Portals/0/Users/154/22/922/Matt-Casto-01.png</d:imageurl>
        <d:bio>Matt Casto is an Architect for the Software Development Group at Information Control Corporation. He has been designing and programming web and windows applications on the Microsoft platform for over 12 years. Recently, Matt has been focusing on Silverlight, WPF and Windows Phone 7. Matt is an avid video and board gamer, and lives in Columbus, Ohio with his wife and two kids.</d:bio>
        <d:twitter>mattcasto</d:twitter>
      </m:properties>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>http://devlink.us/OData.svc/speakers(31)</id>
    <title type="text"></title>
    <updated>2011-07-07T14:05:35Z</updated>
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <link rel="edit" title="speaker" href="speakers(31)" />
    <link rel="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/related/sessions" type="application/atom+xml;type=feed" title="sessions" href="speakers(31)/sessions" />
    <category term="devlink2011Model.speaker" scheme="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/scheme" />
    <content type="application/xml">
      <m:properties>
        <d:speakerid m:type="Edm.Int32">31</d:speakerid>
        <d:firstname>Michael</d:firstname>
        <d:lastname>Eaton</d:lastname>
        <d:company m:null="true" />
        <d:url></d:url>
        <d:imageurl m:null="true" />
        <d:bio>Michael Eaton has been developing awesome solutions using Microsoft tools and technologies since 1994, but in 2001 he broke free from the confines of the cube farm to go out on his own. While he lives in the middle-of-nowhere Michigan, he serves clients throughout the mid-west. Well known for his dislike of web development and box lunches, his focus over the past few years has been on XAML-based technologies like WPF and Silverlight. He speaks at regional events and user groups, runs the Kalamazoo X Conference and helps with the Ann Arbor Give Camp. He is also a C# MVP. When not working on projects or spending time with his family, he treats his World of Warcraft addiction with ample doses of time on his XBox 360.</d:bio>
        <d:twitter>mjeaton</d:twitter>
      </m:properties>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>http://devlink.us/OData.svc/speakers(32)</id>
    <title type="text"></title>
    <updated>2011-07-07T14:05:35Z</updated>
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <link rel="edit" title="speaker" href="speakers(32)" />
    <link rel="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/related/sessions" type="application/atom+xml;type=feed" title="sessions" href="speakers(32)/sessions" />
    <category term="devlink2011Model.speaker" scheme="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/scheme" />
    <content type="application/xml">
      <m:properties>
        <d:speakerid m:type="Edm.Int32">32</d:speakerid>
        <d:firstname>Rick</d:firstname>
        <d:lastname>Schummer</d:lastname>
        <d:company m:null="true" />
        <d:url>http://whitelightcomputing.com</d:url>
        <d:imageurl m:null="true" />
        <d:bio>Rick Schummer is the president and lead geek at White Light Computing, Inc., headquartered in southeast Michigan, USA. He prides himself in guiding his customer's Information Technology investment toward success. He enjoys working with top-notch developers; has a passion for developing software using best practices, and for surpassing customer expectations, not just meeting them. After hours you might find him creating developer tools that improve developer productivity, or writing articles for his favorite periodicals. Rick is a co-author of Making Sense of Sedna and SP2, Visual FoxPro Best Practices for the Next Ten Years, What's New In Nine: Visual FoxPro's Latest Hits, Deploying Visual FoxPro Solutions, MegaFox: 1002 Things You Wanted To Know About Extending Visual FoxPro, and 1001 Things You Always Wanted to Know About Visual FoxPro. He is regular presenter at user groups in North America and is founding member and Secretary of the Detroit Area Fox User Group (DAFUG). Rick is one of the organizers of the Southwest Fox Conference, and is a regular presenter at other conferences in North America, Europe, and Australia. He is also an administrator of VFPX which is an open source project, and a Microsoft VFP MVP since 2002. You can contact him via email at raschummer@whitelightcomputing.com, find him on Twitter @rschummer, or via his company Web site: http://www.whitelightcomputing.com. Read more of his thoughts on Visual FoxPro in his blog: Shedding Some Light (http://rickschummer.com/blog).</d:bio>
        <d:twitter>rschummer</d:twitter>
      </m:properties>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>http://devlink.us/OData.svc/speakers(33)</id>
    <title type="text"></title>
    <updated>2011-07-07T14:05:35Z</updated>
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <link rel="edit" title="speaker" href="speakers(33)" />
    <link rel="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/related/sessions" type="application/atom+xml;type=feed" title="sessions" href="speakers(33)/sessions" />
    <category term="devlink2011Model.speaker" scheme="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/scheme" />
    <content type="application/xml">
      <m:properties>
        <d:speakerid m:type="Edm.Int32">33</d:speakerid>
        <d:firstname>Joe</d:firstname>
        <d:lastname>Webb</d:lastname>
        <d:company m:null="true" />
        <d:url></d:url>
        <d:imageurl m:null="true" />
        <d:bio>Since its inception, Joe Webb has served as Chief Operating Manager for WebbTech Solutions, a Nashville-based consulting company. He has over 15 years of industry experience and has consulted extensively with companies in the areas of business process analysis and improvements, database design and architecture, software development, and technical training. In addition to helping his consulting clients, Joe enjoys writing and speaking at technical conferences. He has spoken at conferences in Europe and the North America and has authored or co-authored three books including "SQL Server MVP Deep Dives", "The Rational Guide To: SQL Server Notification Services", and "The Rational Guide To: IT Consulting". Joe served for six years on the Board of Directors for the Professional Association for SQL Server (PASS), an international user group with 30,000 members worldwide. Joe culminated his tenure on the board by serving as the Executive Vice President of Finance for the organization. Joe also volunteers his time by serving on the MBA Advisory Board for Auburn University and the Computer Science Advisory Committee for Nashville State Community College. Joe received a Bachelors Degree in Electrical Engineering (BSEE) and a Masters in Business Administration (MBA), both from Auburn University. He has also earned Microsoft Certified Database Administrator (MCDBA), Microsoft Certified Solution Developer (MCSD), Microsoft Certified Systems Engineer (MCSE), and Microsoft Certified Trainer (MCT) accreditations as well as other non-Microsoft certifications such as the Linux Professional Institute Level I (LPIC-1). Joe is a six time recipient of the prestigious Microsoft MVP Award for demonstrating a willingness to share his expertise with the SQL Server Community.</d:bio>
        <d:twitter>joewebb</d:twitter>
      </m:properties>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>http://devlink.us/OData.svc/speakers(34)</id>
    <title type="text"></title>
    <updated>2011-07-07T14:05:35Z</updated>
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <link rel="edit" title="speaker" href="speakers(34)" />
    <link rel="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/related/sessions" type="application/atom+xml;type=feed" title="sessions" href="speakers(34)/sessions" />
    <category term="devlink2011Model.speaker" scheme="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/scheme" />
    <content type="application/xml">
      <m:properties>
        <d:speakerid m:type="Edm.Int32">34</d:speakerid>
        <d:firstname>Tim</d:firstname>
        <d:lastname>Corbett</d:lastname>
        <d:company m:null="true" />
        <d:url></d:url>
        <d:imageurl>http://devlink.net/Portals/0/Users/238/18/1518/photo.JPG</d:imageurl>
        <d:bio>Tim is a consultant with Intellithought, Inc. in Kingsport, TN. He has been on assignment full time for the last 27 months to a large coal mining company in VA. Tim has been programming with .Net since version 1.0 and has used every version since. He was primarily a VB.net programmer until 2010 when he wanted to write MVVM apps and decided C# would be a better way to proceed. He forced himself into writing code in C# and now is an avid C# developer working on many MVVM projects. Although he has been toying with some Azure apps, he really likes programming for the Windows Phone 7. Tim founded and is the leader of the Tri-Cities .NET user group in Kingsport, TN. When not writing apps he likes quite family time, smooth scotch and following his favorite drivers in Nascar.</d:bio>
        <d:twitter>tcorbett</d:twitter>
      </m:properties>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>http://devlink.us/OData.svc/speakers(35)</id>
    <title type="text"></title>
    <updated>2011-07-07T14:05:35Z</updated>
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <link rel="edit" title="speaker" href="speakers(35)" />
    <link rel="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/related/sessions" type="application/atom+xml;type=feed" title="sessions" href="speakers(35)/sessions" />
    <category term="devlink2011Model.speaker" scheme="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/scheme" />
    <content type="application/xml">
      <m:properties>
        <d:speakerid m:type="Edm.Int32">35</d:speakerid>
        <d:firstname>Elijah</d:firstname>
        <d:lastname>Manor</d:lastname>
        <d:company m:null="true" />
        <d:url></d:url>
        <d:imageurl>http://devlink.net/Portals/0/Users/002/02/2/elijahmanor.jpeg</d:imageurl>
        <d:bio>Elijah Manor is a Christian and a family man. He develops at appendTo as a System Architect providing corporate jQuery support, training, and consulting. He is an ASP.NET MVP, ASPInsider and specializes in ASP.NET MVC and jQuery development. He has written several articles for the MSDN Script Junkie website and enjoys blogging about the things he learns. He is also active on Twitter and provides daily up-to-date Tech Tweets"</d:bio>
        <d:twitter>elijahmanor</d:twitter>
      </m:properties>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>http://devlink.us/OData.svc/speakers(37)</id>
    <title type="text"></title>
    <updated>2011-07-07T14:05:35Z</updated>
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <link rel="edit" title="speaker" href="speakers(37)" />
    <link rel="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/related/sessions" type="application/atom+xml;type=feed" title="sessions" href="speakers(37)/sessions" />
    <category term="devlink2011Model.speaker" scheme="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/scheme" />
    <content type="application/xml">
      <m:properties>
        <d:speakerid m:type="Edm.Int32">37</d:speakerid>
        <d:firstname>Jesse</d:firstname>
        <d:lastname>Liberty</d:lastname>
        <d:company m:null="true" />
        <d:url></d:url>
        <d:imageurl>http://devlink.net/Portals/0/Users/002/02/2/jesseliberty.jpeg</d:imageurl>
        <d:bio>To follow....</d:bio>
        <d:twitter>jesseliberty</d:twitter>
      </m:properties>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>http://devlink.us/OData.svc/speakers(38)</id>
    <title type="text"></title>
    <updated>2011-07-07T14:05:35Z</updated>
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <link rel="edit" title="speaker" href="speakers(38)" />
    <link rel="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/related/sessions" type="application/atom+xml;type=feed" title="sessions" href="speakers(38)/sessions" />
    <category term="devlink2011Model.speaker" scheme="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/scheme" />
    <content type="application/xml">
      <m:properties>
        <d:speakerid m:type="Edm.Int32">38</d:speakerid>
        <d:firstname>Jay</d:firstname>
        <d:lastname>Harris</d:lastname>
        <d:company m:null="true" />
        <d:url>http://www.aranasoft.com</d:url>
        <d:imageurl>http://devlink.net/Portals/0/Users/077/89/589/Headshot,%20Color,%20200x.png</d:imageurl>
        <d:bio>Jay is a .NET developer, a software consultant, and is president of Arana Software (www.aranasoft.com). He has been developing on the web for 15 years, since he abandoned VB3 for JavaScript because he didn't have to wait for a compile. With a career focus on end-user experience, he is a strong advocate of practices and processes that improve quality through code, ranging from automated testing, continuous integration, and performance analysis, to designing applications from the user's perspective. Jay is also an active speaker and leader in the developer community, serving as President of Ann Arbor .NET Developers and is co-founder for the Lansing and the Indianapolis Give Camp. Originally from Rochester, New York, he and his wife, Amy, have lived in Michigan since 2003. They like Michigan, but still consider themselves tourists, and probably always will.</d:bio>
        <d:twitter>jayharris</d:twitter>
      </m:properties>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>http://devlink.us/OData.svc/speakers(39)</id>
    <title type="text"></title>
    <updated>2011-07-07T14:05:35Z</updated>
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <link rel="edit" title="speaker" href="speakers(39)" />
    <link rel="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/related/sessions" type="application/atom+xml;type=feed" title="sessions" href="speakers(39)/sessions" />
    <category term="devlink2011Model.speaker" scheme="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/scheme" />
    <content type="application/xml">
      <m:properties>
        <d:speakerid m:type="Edm.Int32">39</d:speakerid>
        <d:firstname>Brian</d:firstname>
        <d:lastname>Prince</d:lastname>
        <d:company m:null="true" />
        <d:url></d:url>
        <d:imageurl>http://devlink.net/Portals/0/Users/002/02/2/brianprince.jpeg</d:imageurl>
        <d:bio>Expect Brian to get (in his own words) "super excited" whenever he talks about technology, especially cloud computing, patterns, and practices. That's a good thing, given that his job is to help customers strategically leverage Microsoft technologies and take their architecture to new heights. Before joining Microsoft in March 2008, Brian was senior director of technology strategy for a major Midwest partner and has over 13 years of expertise in information technology management. His consulting experience includes e-commerce, extranets and business technology for numerous industries, including real estate, financial services, health care, retail, and state government institutions. Brian also has exceptional proficiency in the Microsoft .NET framework, Service Oriented Architecture, building ESBs, and both smart client and web based applications. Brian's the co-founder of the non-profit organization CodeMash (www.codemash.org), runs the global Windows Azure Boot Camp program, and speaks at various regional and international technology events. Armed with a Bachelor of Arts degree in Computer Science and Physics from Capital University in Columbus, Ohio, Brian is a zealous gamer with a special weakness for Fallout 3. Brian is the co-author of "Azure in Action", published by Manning Press.</d:bio>
        <d:twitter>brianhprince</d:twitter>
      </m:properties>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>http://devlink.us/OData.svc/speakers(40)</id>
    <title type="text"></title>
    <updated>2011-07-07T14:05:35Z</updated>
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <link rel="edit" title="speaker" href="speakers(40)" />
    <link rel="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/related/sessions" type="application/atom+xml;type=feed" title="sessions" href="speakers(40)/sessions" />
    <category term="devlink2011Model.speaker" scheme="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/scheme" />
    <content type="application/xml">
      <m:properties>
        <d:speakerid m:type="Edm.Int32">40</d:speakerid>
        <d:firstname>Brian</d:firstname>
        <d:lastname>Sullivan</d:lastname>
        <d:company m:null="true" />
        <d:url></d:url>
        <d:imageurl m:null="true" />
        <d:bio>Brian Sullivan is a developer analyst for Falcon Applications, LLC in Shreveport, LA. He got his start in programming maintaining legacy mainframe applications in COBOL at a large trucking company, but quickly realized he needed to find a more productive environment in order to stay sane. He jumped at the opportunity to help transition some of those COBOL applications to .NET, and he hasn't looked back since. He has been working with Microsoft technologies for about 6 years, and is interested in increasing the exposure of agile techniques and methodologies in the Microsoft developer community. He currently runs the Shreveport .NET User Group and speaks frequently at local user groups and regional conferences. Brian is a graduate of Harding University in Searcy, AR.</d:bio>
        <d:twitter>bmsullivan</d:twitter>
      </m:properties>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>http://devlink.us/OData.svc/speakers(41)</id>
    <title type="text"></title>
    <updated>2011-07-07T14:05:35Z</updated>
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <link rel="edit" title="speaker" href="speakers(41)" />
    <link rel="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/related/sessions" type="application/atom+xml;type=feed" title="sessions" href="speakers(41)/sessions" />
    <category term="devlink2011Model.speaker" scheme="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/scheme" />
    <content type="application/xml">
      <m:properties>
        <d:speakerid m:type="Edm.Int32">41</d:speakerid>
        <d:firstname>Lee</d:firstname>
        <d:lastname>Brandt</d:lastname>
        <d:company m:null="true" />
        <d:url></d:url>
        <d:imageurl>http://devlink.net/Portals/0/Users/247/27/1527/me.jpg</d:imageurl>
        <d:bio>Lee has been programming professionally for more than a decade and currently works as a Project Lead Consultant with AdventureTech. He speaks regionally about software development practices and has mentored teams on improving their approach to lean software development through achieving technical proficiency. He is a Microsoft Most Valuable Professional, one of the leaders of the Kansas City .Net User Group, and serves as the Regional Mentor for .Net user groups in Kansas and Missouri.</d:bio>
        <d:twitter>leebrandt</d:twitter>
      </m:properties>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>http://devlink.us/OData.svc/speakers(43)</id>
    <title type="text"></title>
    <updated>2011-07-07T14:05:35Z</updated>
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <link rel="edit" title="speaker" href="speakers(43)" />
    <link rel="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/related/sessions" type="application/atom+xml;type=feed" title="sessions" href="speakers(43)/sessions" />
    <category term="devlink2011Model.speaker" scheme="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/scheme" />
    <content type="application/xml">
      <m:properties>
        <d:speakerid m:type="Edm.Int32">43</d:speakerid>
        <d:firstname>Chris</d:firstname>
        <d:lastname>Meadows</d:lastname>
        <d:company m:null="true" />
        <d:url></d:url>
        <d:imageurl m:null="true" />
        <d:bio>Chris blends the skills learned through his experience as a flight instructor, trained financial counselor, physics researcher, and software engineer to to enable himself and others to pick up and make practical use of technologies in solving business challenges. He is currently a Senior .Net Architect at Terenine Technologies here in Chattanooga. He lives in the Chattanooga area with his wife and two children.</d:bio>
        <d:twitter></d:twitter>
      </m:properties>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>http://devlink.us/OData.svc/speakers(44)</id>
    <title type="text"></title>
    <updated>2011-07-07T14:05:35Z</updated>
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <link rel="edit" title="speaker" href="speakers(44)" />
    <link rel="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/related/sessions" type="application/atom+xml;type=feed" title="sessions" href="speakers(44)/sessions" />
    <category term="devlink2011Model.speaker" scheme="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/scheme" />
    <content type="application/xml">
      <m:properties>
        <d:speakerid m:type="Edm.Int32">44</d:speakerid>
        <d:firstname>Chris</d:firstname>
        <d:lastname>Woodruff</d:lastname>
        <d:company m:null="true" />
        <d:url>http://blog.cloudsocket.com</d:url>
        <d:imageurl>http://devlink.net/Portals/0/Users/006/62/262/WoodyMug.jpg</d:imageurl>
        <d:bio>Chris Woodruff (or Woody as he is commonly known as) has a degree in Computer Science from Michigan State University's College of Engineering. Woody has been developing and architecting software solutions for almost 15 years and has worked in many different platforms and tools. He is a community leader, helping such events as Day of .NET Ann Arbor, West Michigan Day of .NET and CodeMash. He was also instrumental in bringing the popular Give Camp event to Western Michigan where technology professionals lend their time and development expertise to assist local non-profits. As a speaker and podcaster, Woody has spoken and discussed a variety of topics, including database design and open source. He is a Microsoft MVP in Data Platform Development and was recently recognized as one of the top 20 MVPs world-wide. Woody works at Perficient, Inc.. Woody is the co-host of the popular podcast "Deep Fried Bytes" and blogs at www.chriswoodruff.com. He is the President of the West Michigan .NET User Group and also is a co-founder of the software architecture online portal nPlus1.org. Woody has worked in many arenas throughout the years, including healthcare, manufacturing, publishing, promotion execution and the automotive industry. He has experience with starting and running new ventures, including past work with technology startups. Woody continues to develop his expertise by learning &amp; developing new technologies to better meet the needs of his clients, while devoting his free time to improving the development community at large, and giving back to the community in which he lives.</d:bio>
        <d:twitter>cwoodruff</d:twitter>
      </m:properties>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>http://devlink.us/OData.svc/speakers(45)</id>
    <title type="text"></title>
    <updated>2011-07-07T14:05:35Z</updated>
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <link rel="edit" title="speaker" href="speakers(45)" />
    <link rel="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/related/sessions" type="application/atom+xml;type=feed" title="sessions" href="speakers(45)/sessions" />
    <category term="devlink2011Model.speaker" scheme="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/scheme" />
    <content type="application/xml">
      <m:properties>
        <d:speakerid m:type="Edm.Int32">45</d:speakerid>
        <d:firstname>Todd</d:firstname>
        <d:lastname>Miranda</d:lastname>
        <d:company m:null="true" />
        <d:url>www.xperimentality.com</d:url>
        <d:imageurl>http://devlink.net/Portals/0/Users/002/02/2/toddmiranda.jpeg</d:imageurl>
        <d:bio>Todd Miranda is a software engineer with over 20 years of experience in building software applications and web sites. He is a Microsoft MVP. Todd is one of the founders and still serves on the boards of both the Birmingham .NET User Group and the Silverlight Nights User Group. He regularly presents for user groups and has presented at many events including Code Camps, Microsoft events, and other technical conferences. He is passionate about technology and sharing his knowledge and experience with others.</d:bio>
        <d:twitter>tmiranda</d:twitter>
      </m:properties>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>http://devlink.us/OData.svc/speakers(46)</id>
    <title type="text"></title>
    <updated>2011-07-07T14:05:35Z</updated>
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <link rel="edit" title="speaker" href="speakers(46)" />
    <link rel="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/related/sessions" type="application/atom+xml;type=feed" title="sessions" href="speakers(46)/sessions" />
    <category term="devlink2011Model.speaker" scheme="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/scheme" />
    <content type="application/xml">
      <m:properties>
        <d:speakerid m:type="Edm.Int32">46</d:speakerid>
        <d:firstname>Alan</d:firstname>
        <d:lastname>Stevens</d:lastname>
        <d:company m:null="true" />
        <d:url>http://halanstevens.com</d:url>
        <d:imageurl>http://devlink.net/Portals/0/Users/027/27/27/Alan_headshot.jpg</d:imageurl>
        <d:bio>Alan Stevens is a father, geek, vegan and software artisan living in Knoxville, TN. Alan regularly speaks at conferences and user group meetings about how to be a better software developer. Alan is an Open Space Technology facilitator. Alan received the Microsoft Most Valuable Professional (MVP) award in C# in 2009, 2010 &amp; 2011. Alan is a member of ASP Insiders. When Alan is not hanging out with his family, posting on Twitter, singing or playing his acoustic guitar, he occasionally updates his website at http://halanstevens.com.</d:bio>
        <d:twitter>alanstevens</d:twitter>
      </m:properties>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>http://devlink.us/OData.svc/speakers(47)</id>
    <title type="text"></title>
    <updated>2011-07-07T14:05:35Z</updated>
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <link rel="edit" title="speaker" href="speakers(47)" />
    <link rel="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/related/sessions" type="application/atom+xml;type=feed" title="sessions" href="speakers(47)/sessions" />
    <category term="devlink2011Model.speaker" scheme="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/scheme" />
    <content type="application/xml">
      <m:properties>
        <d:speakerid m:type="Edm.Int32">47</d:speakerid>
        <d:firstname>Jason</d:firstname>
        <d:lastname>Follas</d:lastname>
        <d:company m:null="true" />
        <d:url></d:url>
        <d:imageurl>http://devlink.net/Portals/0/Users/251/31/1531/jfollas.png</d:imageurl>
        <d:bio>Jason Follas is a Technical Architect for Perficient, serving clients primarily located in the greater Detroit region (including Toledo, where he lives and serves as the President of the Northwest Ohio .NET User Group). Since 1994, he has developed many interesting solutions on the Microsoft platform, including an Aircraft Weight and Balance system used by an air freight company, several e-Commerce websites, Risk Management systems, and blend optimization software. Jason has also been recognized by Microsoft in the past as a Microsoft MVP (SQL Server).</d:bio>
        <d:twitter>jfollas</d:twitter>
      </m:properties>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>http://devlink.us/OData.svc/speakers(48)</id>
    <title type="text"></title>
    <updated>2011-07-07T14:05:35Z</updated>
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <link rel="edit" title="speaker" href="speakers(48)" />
    <link rel="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/related/sessions" type="application/atom+xml;type=feed" title="sessions" href="speakers(48)/sessions" />
    <category term="devlink2011Model.speaker" scheme="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/scheme" />
    <content type="application/xml">
      <m:properties>
        <d:speakerid m:type="Edm.Int32">48</d:speakerid>
        <d:firstname>David</d:firstname>
        <d:lastname>Buckingham</d:lastname>
        <d:company m:null="true" />
        <d:url></d:url>
        <d:imageurl>http://devlink.net/Portals/0/Users/121/77/377/IMG_0231.JPG</d:imageurl>
        <d:bio>Born in the dark ages when computers were behemoths, David cut his teeth on numerous programming languages. As the years progressed, he migrated towards the middle-tier/back-end, shying away from anything "pretty". Large-scale, high-performance applications have been his motivation to specialize in the SQL Server database engine. David has worked with SQL Server from its beginning, but didn't begin to specialize in performance tuning (code, architecture, and hardware) until SQL 2000. He has worked with SQL Server exclusively since then and have worked with combinations of high volume and very large databases at multiple clients. Beyond performance tuning existing/new systems, David also specialized in elevating development teams to best practices via mentoring, peer reviews, and team presentations. He finds overcoming the challenges of adapting and enhancing design and coding techniques for each unique application and environment very rewarding.</d:bio>
        <d:twitter></d:twitter>
      </m:properties>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>http://devlink.us/OData.svc/speakers(49)</id>
    <title type="text"></title>
    <updated>2011-07-07T14:05:35Z</updated>
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <link rel="edit" title="speaker" href="speakers(49)" />
    <link rel="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/related/sessions" type="application/atom+xml;type=feed" title="sessions" href="speakers(49)/sessions" />
    <category term="devlink2011Model.speaker" scheme="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/scheme" />
    <content type="application/xml">
      <m:properties>
        <d:speakerid m:type="Edm.Int32">49</d:speakerid>
        <d:firstname>Kevin</d:firstname>
        <d:lastname>Hazzard</d:lastname>
        <d:company m:null="true" />
        <d:url>http://devjourney.com</d:url>
        <d:imageurl>http://devlink.net/Portals/0/Users/002/02/2/kevinhazzard.jpeg</d:imageurl>
        <d:bio>In every permutation and instantaneously, Kevin is geek, mentor, student, teacher, hacker, polyglot, MVP, husband, Dad, consultant and friend.</d:bio>
        <d:twitter>KevinHazzard</d:twitter>
      </m:properties>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>http://devlink.us/OData.svc/speakers(50)</id>
    <title type="text"></title>
    <updated>2011-07-07T14:05:35Z</updated>
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <link rel="edit" title="speaker" href="speakers(50)" />
    <link rel="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/related/sessions" type="application/atom+xml;type=feed" title="sessions" href="speakers(50)/sessions" />
    <category term="devlink2011Model.speaker" scheme="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/scheme" />
    <content type="application/xml">
      <m:properties>
        <d:speakerid m:type="Edm.Int32">50</d:speakerid>
        <d:firstname>Timothy</d:firstname>
        <d:lastname>Korson</d:lastname>
        <d:company m:null="true" />
        <d:url>www.qualsys.org</d:url>
        <d:imageurl>http://devlink.net/Portals/0/Users/001/37/1537/tim%20black%20background%20smaller.jpg</d:imageurl>
        <d:bio>Timothy Korson is a Scrum trainer and coach. He has had over a decade of substantial experience working on a large variety of systems developed using modern agile software engineering techniques. This experience includes distributed, real time, embedded systems as well as business information systems in an n-tier, client-server environment. Dr. Korson's current focus is on helping organizations implement high value software using Scrum. As a leader in the field of agile software development, Tim has authored articles, given numerous tutorials on agile techniques, and worked with numerous organizations transitioning to Scrum.</d:bio>
        <d:twitter></d:twitter>
      </m:properties>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>http://devlink.us/OData.svc/speakers(51)</id>
    <title type="text"></title>
    <updated>2011-07-07T14:05:35Z</updated>
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <link rel="edit" title="speaker" href="speakers(51)" />
    <link rel="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/related/sessions" type="application/atom+xml;type=feed" title="sessions" href="speakers(51)/sessions" />
    <category term="devlink2011Model.speaker" scheme="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/scheme" />
    <content type="application/xml">
      <m:properties>
        <d:speakerid m:type="Edm.Int32">51</d:speakerid>
        <d:firstname>Michael</d:firstname>
        <d:lastname>Crump</d:lastname>
        <d:company>http://www.pointclearsolutions.com</d:company>
        <d:url>http://michaelcrump.net</d:url>
        <d:imageurl>http://devlink.net/Portals/0/Users/188/68/1468/mike_small.jpg</d:imageurl>
        <d:bio>Michael Crump is an MCPD that has been involved with computers in one way or another for as long as he can remember, but started professionally in 2002. After spending years working as a systems administrator/tech support analyst, Michael branched out and started developing internal utilities that automated repetitive tasks and freed up full-time employees. From there, he was offered a job working at McKesson corporation and has been working with some form of .NET and VB/C# since 2003. He has worked at Fortune 500 companies where he gained experience in embedded systems design and software development to systems administration and database programming, and everything in between. His primary focus right now is developing healthcare software solutions using Microsoft .NET technologies. He prefers building infrastructure components, reusable shared libraries and helping companies define, develop and automate process standards and guidelines.</d:bio>
        <d:twitter>mbcrump</d:twitter>
      </m:properties>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>http://devlink.us/OData.svc/speakers(52)</id>
    <title type="text"></title>
    <updated>2011-07-07T14:05:35Z</updated>
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <link rel="edit" title="speaker" href="speakers(52)" />
    <link rel="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/related/sessions" type="application/atom+xml;type=feed" title="sessions" href="speakers(52)/sessions" />
    <category term="devlink2011Model.speaker" scheme="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/scheme" />
    <content type="application/xml">
      <m:properties>
        <d:speakerid m:type="Edm.Int32">52</d:speakerid>
        <d:firstname>Bastian</d:firstname>
        <d:lastname>Hofmann</d:lastname>
        <d:company m:null="true" />
        <d:url></d:url>
        <d:imageurl>http://devlink.net/Portals/0/Users/005/41/1541/profile_big.jpg</d:imageurl>
        <d:bio>Bastian is the developer and architect behind the integration of OpenSocial and OpenID into the largest german based social networks, studiVZ, schülerVZ and meinVZ. After the successful launch he is now working on bridging the islands of social networks further with the help of open standards and protocols. This, together with his activity in the OpenSocial foundation and as a committer and PMC member for the Apache Shindig project makes him a strong advocate for the vision of an truly open and distributed social web.</d:bio>
        <d:twitter>BastianHofmann</d:twitter>
      </m:properties>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>http://devlink.us/OData.svc/speakers(53)</id>
    <title type="text"></title>
    <updated>2011-07-07T14:05:35Z</updated>
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <link rel="edit" title="speaker" href="speakers(53)" />
    <link rel="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/related/sessions" type="application/atom+xml;type=feed" title="sessions" href="speakers(53)/sessions" />
    <category term="devlink2011Model.speaker" scheme="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/scheme" />
    <content type="application/xml">
      <m:properties>
        <d:speakerid m:type="Edm.Int32">53</d:speakerid>
        <d:firstname>Jeff</d:firstname>
        <d:lastname>McWherter</d:lastname>
        <d:company m:null="true" />
        <d:url></d:url>
        <d:imageurl>http://devlink.net/Portals/0/Users/002/02/2/jeffmcwherter.jpeg</d:imageurl>
        <d:bio>Jeff McWherter is the Director of Development at Gravity Works Design and Development (www.GravityWorksDesign.com). Jeff graduated from Michigan State University with a degree in Telecommunications, and has thirteen years of professional experience in software development. He is a founding member and current Vice President for the Greater Lansing Users for .NET (GLUG.net). He enjoys profiling code, applying design patterns, finding obscure namespaces, and long walks in the park. His lifelong interest in programming began with a Home Computing Magazine in 1983, which included an article about writing a game called Boa Alley in BASIC. Jeff currently lives in a farming community near Lansing, MI. When he is not in front of the computer he enjoys rock and ice climbing with his smart and beautiful wife; which leads to his favorite activity of all, road trips.</d:bio>
        <d:twitter>jmcw</d:twitter>
      </m:properties>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>http://devlink.us/OData.svc/speakers(55)</id>
    <title type="text"></title>
    <updated>2011-07-07T14:05:35Z</updated>
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <link rel="edit" title="speaker" href="speakers(55)" />
    <link rel="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/related/sessions" type="application/atom+xml;type=feed" title="sessions" href="speakers(55)/sessions" />
    <category term="devlink2011Model.speaker" scheme="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/scheme" />
    <content type="application/xml">
      <m:properties>
        <d:speakerid m:type="Edm.Int32">55</d:speakerid>
        <d:firstname>Rob</d:firstname>
        <d:lastname>Gillen</d:lastname>
        <d:company m:null="true" />
        <d:url></d:url>
        <d:imageurl>http://devlink.net/Portals/0/Users/088/12/1112/RobHeadshot.png</d:imageurl>
        <d:bio>Rob has worked for over 11 years as a Solutions Architect for Planet Technologies. During that time he spent 7 years working with service providers and hosting companies around the world helping them deploy Microsoft technologies to deliver services to their customers. For the past four years he has been at Oak Ridge National Laboratory where he is a member of the Computer Science Research Group studying the applicability of cloud computing to the computational needs of ORNL researchers. Rob is an active user of the Amazon Web Services Platform, Windows Azure, and various private cloud technologies. Rob is a Windows Azure MVP. You can often find Rob speaking at conferences, working in the clouds, or riding his bike around the hills of East Tennessee.</d:bio>
        <d:twitter>argodev</d:twitter>
      </m:properties>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>http://devlink.us/OData.svc/speakers(58)</id>
    <title type="text"></title>
    <updated>2011-07-07T14:05:35Z</updated>
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <link rel="edit" title="speaker" href="speakers(58)" />
    <link rel="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/related/sessions" type="application/atom+xml;type=feed" title="sessions" href="speakers(58)/sessions" />
    <category term="devlink2011Model.speaker" scheme="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/scheme" />
    <content type="application/xml">
      <m:properties>
        <d:speakerid m:type="Edm.Int32">58</d:speakerid>
        <d:firstname>Randy</d:firstname>
        <d:lastname>Walker</d:lastname>
        <d:company m:null="true" />
        <d:url></d:url>
        <d:imageurl m:null="true" />
        <d:bio>One of the first Microsoft MVP award winners in Arkansas, Randy helped start the NWA .Net User Group and has helped educate and motivate regional developers to the .Net Framework. Randy is the owner of Harvest I.T. Inc which provides Retail Link automation to Walmart Vendors and has 15 years of development experience.</d:bio>
        <d:twitter>_RandyWalker</d:twitter>
      </m:properties>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>http://devlink.us/OData.svc/speakers(59)</id>
    <title type="text"></title>
    <updated>2011-07-07T14:05:35Z</updated>
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <link rel="edit" title="speaker" href="speakers(59)" />
    <link rel="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/related/sessions" type="application/atom+xml;type=feed" title="sessions" href="speakers(59)/sessions" />
    <category term="devlink2011Model.speaker" scheme="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/scheme" />
    <content type="application/xml">
      <m:properties>
        <d:speakerid m:type="Edm.Int32">59</d:speakerid>
        <d:firstname>Alex</d:firstname>
        <d:lastname>Robson</d:lastname>
        <d:company m:null="true" />
        <d:url>http://sharplearningcurve.com/blog</d:url>
        <d:imageurl m:null="true" />
        <d:bio>Alex is a Sr. Software Developer and Architect obsessed with distributed architecture and the technologies that enable them. He enjoys contributing to one of many open source projects, reading about new languages and writing the occasional blog post.</d:bio>
        <d:twitter>A_Robson</d:twitter>
      </m:properties>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>http://devlink.us/OData.svc/speakers(60)</id>
    <title type="text"></title>
    <updated>2011-07-07T14:05:35Z</updated>
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <link rel="edit" title="speaker" href="speakers(60)" />
    <link rel="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/related/sessions" type="application/atom+xml;type=feed" title="sessions" href="speakers(60)/sessions" />
    <category term="devlink2011Model.speaker" scheme="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/scheme" />
    <content type="application/xml">
      <m:properties>
        <d:speakerid m:type="Edm.Int32">60</d:speakerid>
        <d:firstname>Jim</d:firstname>
        <d:lastname>Cowart</d:lastname>
        <d:company m:null="true" />
        <d:url>http://ifandelse.com</d:url>
        <d:imageurl>http://devlink.net/Portals/0/Users/142/54/654/Jim%20Cowart.JPG</d:imageurl>
        <d:bio>Jim Cowart has over 11 years of experience in development - including time spent as middle-tier application developer, database developer, data architect, data warehouse architect, desktop and web UI developer. He's particularly passionate about distributed architectures, and the role web clients can play in them. He currently works as a Senior Architect and Developer at Terenine in Chattanooga, TN.</d:bio>
        <d:twitter>ifandelse</d:twitter>
      </m:properties>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>http://devlink.us/OData.svc/speakers(61)</id>
    <title type="text"></title>
    <updated>2011-07-07T14:05:35Z</updated>
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <link rel="edit" title="speaker" href="speakers(61)" />
    <link rel="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/related/sessions" type="application/atom+xml;type=feed" title="sessions" href="speakers(61)/sessions" />
    <category term="devlink2011Model.speaker" scheme="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/scheme" />
    <content type="application/xml">
      <m:properties>
        <d:speakerid m:type="Edm.Int32">61</d:speakerid>
        <d:firstname>Don</d:firstname>
        <d:lastname>Demsak</d:lastname>
        <d:company m:null="true" />
        <d:url></d:url>
        <d:imageurl>http://devlink.net/Portals/0/Users/002/02/2/domdemsak.jpeg</d:imageurl>
        <d:bio>Don Demsak is the Chief Technical Officer at Tellago, Inc. and Tellago Studios. Don specializes in building enterprise service oriented applications with .Net. He has a popular blog at http://www.donxml.com, is a Microsoft MVP – Data Platform, and a member of the INETA Community Speakers Program. Don lives in NJ, and has been helping organizations build enterprise level solutions based on Microsoft technologies for over 15 years.</d:bio>
        <d:twitter>donxml</d:twitter>
      </m:properties>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>http://devlink.us/OData.svc/speakers(62)</id>
    <title type="text"></title>
    <updated>2011-07-07T14:05:35Z</updated>
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <link rel="edit" title="speaker" href="speakers(62)" />
    <link rel="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/related/sessions" type="application/atom+xml;type=feed" title="sessions" href="speakers(62)/sessions" />
    <category term="devlink2011Model.speaker" scheme="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/scheme" />
    <content type="application/xml">
      <m:properties>
        <d:speakerid m:type="Edm.Int32">62</d:speakerid>
        <d:firstname>Jeff</d:firstname>
        <d:lastname>Blankenburg</d:lastname>
        <d:company m:null="true" />
        <d:url>http://www.jeffblankenburg.com</d:url>
        <d:imageurl>http://devlink.net/Portals/0/Users/002/02/2/jeffblankenburg.jpeg</d:imageurl>
        <d:bio></d:bio>
        <d:twitter>jeffblankenburg</d:twitter>
      </m:properties>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>http://devlink.us/OData.svc/speakers(63)</id>
    <title type="text"></title>
    <updated>2011-07-07T14:05:35Z</updated>
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <link rel="edit" title="speaker" href="speakers(63)" />
    <link rel="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/related/sessions" type="application/atom+xml;type=feed" title="sessions" href="speakers(63)/sessions" />
    <category term="devlink2011Model.speaker" scheme="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/scheme" />
    <content type="application/xml">
      <m:properties>
        <d:speakerid m:type="Edm.Int32">63</d:speakerid>
        <d:firstname>Mickey</d:firstname>
        <d:lastname>Gousset</d:lastname>
        <d:company m:null="true" />
        <d:url>http://www.teamsystemrocks.com/blogs/mickey_gousset</d:url>
        <d:imageurl>http://devlink.net/Portals/0/Users/002/02/2/mickeygousset.jpeg</d:imageurl>
        <d:bio>Mickey Gousset is a Senior Technical Developer for Infront Consulting Group, a consulting company focused on the Microsoft System Center family of products. He is a Microsoft ALM MVP, a certified professional in Team Foundation Server and SCOM 2007, and author of the books "Professional Team Foundation Server" and "Professional Application Lifecycle Management with Visual Studio 2010" from Wrox Publishing. Mickey runs Team System Rocks" (http://www.teamsystemrocks.com), a community site devoted to Visual Studio 2010 and TFS 2010. He has spoken on ALM, Visual Studio, TFS, and System Center topics at various user groups, code camps, and conferences, including Microsoft Tech Ed Developer - North America 2008 and 2009, and Devlink 2010.</d:bio>
        <d:twitter>mickey_gousset</d:twitter>
      </m:properties>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>http://devlink.us/OData.svc/speakers(64)</id>
    <title type="text"></title>
    <updated>2011-07-07T14:05:35Z</updated>
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <link rel="edit" title="speaker" href="speakers(64)" />
    <link rel="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/related/sessions" type="application/atom+xml;type=feed" title="sessions" href="speakers(64)/sessions" />
    <category term="devlink2011Model.speaker" scheme="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/scheme" />
    <content type="application/xml">
      <m:properties>
        <d:speakerid m:type="Edm.Int32">64</d:speakerid>
        <d:firstname>Randy</d:firstname>
        <d:lastname>Pagels</d:lastname>
        <d:company m:null="true" />
        <d:url></d:url>
        <d:imageurl>http://devlink.net/Portals/0/Users/229/09/1509/Randy-Headshot.JPG</d:imageurl>
        <d:bio>Randy is a Sr. Developer Technology Specialist and a Developer Platform and Evangelism tools team member covering the Heartland District (MI, OH, KY, TN). His expertise includes Visual Studio, Team Foundation Server, Test Professional, and Lab Management products. He educates the customer to maximize their ALM tools by explaining best practices, installation, and configuration through presentations, workshops, or quick starts. Prior to Microsoft he worked for 16 years as a developer in the IT area and has designed and developed many .Net web applications using agile methodologies. Randy is a Microsoft Certified Technology Specialist (MCTS) on Team Foundation Server. For further resource information, please refer to his website teamsystemcafe.net.</d:bio>
        <d:twitter>RandyPagels</d:twitter>
      </m:properties>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>http://devlink.us/OData.svc/speakers(65)</id>
    <title type="text"></title>
    <updated>2011-07-07T14:05:35Z</updated>
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <link rel="edit" title="speaker" href="speakers(65)" />
    <link rel="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/related/sessions" type="application/atom+xml;type=feed" title="sessions" href="speakers(65)/sessions" />
    <category term="devlink2011Model.speaker" scheme="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/scheme" />
    <content type="application/xml">
      <m:properties>
        <d:speakerid m:type="Edm.Int32">65</d:speakerid>
        <d:firstname>Michael</d:firstname>
        <d:lastname>Perry</d:lastname>
        <d:company m:null="true" />
        <d:url>http://qedcode.com</d:url>
        <d:imageurl>http://devlink.net/Portals/0/Users/032/68/1568/Perry_Headshot.JPG</d:imageurl>
        <d:bio>Throughout his career, Michael has applied mathematical concepts to the construction of software. As a Solutions Architect at AmerisourceBergen, he applies the concepts of eventual consistency, event sourcing, and CQRS to building scalable and robust enterprise systems. He has written about the mathematical underpinnings of various algorithms in C/C++ Users Journal, Delphi Informant, and Code Magazine. Craig Shoemaker interviewed him on the Polymorphic Podcast about Update Controls, an open source project based on the mathematical concept of dependency. You can find out more at qedcode.com.</d:bio>
        <d:twitter>michaellperry</d:twitter>
      </m:properties>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>http://devlink.us/OData.svc/speakers(66)</id>
    <title type="text"></title>
    <updated>2011-07-07T14:05:35Z</updated>
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <link rel="edit" title="speaker" href="speakers(66)" />
    <link rel="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/related/sessions" type="application/atom+xml;type=feed" title="sessions" href="speakers(66)/sessions" />
    <category term="devlink2011Model.speaker" scheme="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/scheme" />
    <content type="application/xml">
      <m:properties>
        <d:speakerid m:type="Edm.Int32">66</d:speakerid>
        <d:firstname>John</d:firstname>
        <d:lastname>Sheehan</d:lastname>
        <d:company m:null="true" />
        <d:url>http://john-sheehan.com/blog</d:url>
        <d:imageurl>http://devlink.net/Portals/0/Users/033/69/1569/me500.jpg</d:imageurl>
        <d:bio>John Sheehan is a Developer Evangelist for Twilio, a cloud communications provider that offers a simple RESTful API for sending and receiving phone calls and SMS text messages from your applications. John is also the author of RestSharp, a popular and award-winning .NET REST and HTTP API client library. John has been developing for the web with Microsoft technologies since 1996 and currently resides in San Francisco, CA.</d:bio>
        <d:twitter>johnsheehan</d:twitter>
      </m:properties>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>http://devlink.us/OData.svc/speakers(67)</id>
    <title type="text"></title>
    <updated>2011-07-07T14:05:35Z</updated>
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <link rel="edit" title="speaker" href="speakers(67)" />
    <link rel="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/related/sessions" type="application/atom+xml;type=feed" title="sessions" href="speakers(67)/sessions" />
    <category term="devlink2011Model.speaker" scheme="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/scheme" />
    <content type="application/xml">
      <m:properties>
        <d:speakerid m:type="Edm.Int32">67</d:speakerid>
        <d:firstname>Jeremiah</d:firstname>
        <d:lastname>Peschka</d:lastname>
        <d:company m:null="true" />
        <d:url>http://facility9.com</d:url>
        <d:imageurl>http://devlink.net/Portals/0/Users/237/17/1517/badgers%20with%20badgers.jpg</d:imageurl>
        <d:bio>Jeremiah Peschka is a principal with Brent Ozar PLF. He's a Microsoft SQL Sever MVP with over a decade of experience on a variety of platforms, programming languages, and databases.</d:bio>
        <d:twitter>peschkaj</d:twitter>
      </m:properties>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>http://devlink.us/OData.svc/speakers(68)</id>
    <title type="text"></title>
    <updated>2011-07-07T14:05:35Z</updated>
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <link rel="edit" title="speaker" href="speakers(68)" />
    <link rel="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/related/sessions" type="application/atom+xml;type=feed" title="sessions" href="speakers(68)/sessions" />
    <category term="devlink2011Model.speaker" scheme="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/scheme" />
    <content type="application/xml">
      <m:properties>
        <d:speakerid m:type="Edm.Int32">68</d:speakerid>
        <d:firstname>Travis</d:firstname>
        <d:lastname>Smith</d:lastname>
        <d:company m:null="true" />
        <d:url>http://legomaster.net</d:url>
        <d:imageurl>http://devlink.net/Portals/0/Users/206/86/1486/small%20headshot.jpeg</d:imageurl>
        <d:bio>Travis focus on .NET technologies with his day job, helping to keep enterprises truly interconnected in close to real time. Travis also contributes to and maintains a number of open source projects, primarily on the .NET platform. You can find out what Travis is currently working on in the open source work at his github page, http://github.com/legomaster. Travis also has a love for learning new languages and platforms.</d:bio>
        <d:twitter>legomasternet</d:twitter>
      </m:properties>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>http://devlink.us/OData.svc/speakers(69)</id>
    <title type="text"></title>
    <updated>2011-07-07T14:05:35Z</updated>
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <link rel="edit" title="speaker" href="speakers(69)" />
    <link rel="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/related/sessions" type="application/atom+xml;type=feed" title="sessions" href="speakers(69)/sessions" />
    <category term="devlink2011Model.speaker" scheme="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/scheme" />
    <content type="application/xml">
      <m:properties>
        <d:speakerid m:type="Edm.Int32">69</d:speakerid>
        <d:firstname>Joe</d:firstname>
        <d:lastname>Kuemerle</d:lastname>
        <d:company m:null="true" />
        <d:url>www.kuemerle.com</d:url>
        <d:imageurl m:null="true" />
        <d:bio>Joe Kuemerle is a developer and speaker in the Cleveland, OH area specializing in .NET development, security, database and application lifecycle topics. He is currently a Lead Developer at PreEmptive Solutions, LLC . PreEmptive is the maker of Dotfuscator, the premier obfuscator for .NET; DashO, the top Java obfuscator; and Runtime Intelligence, a solution to inject application usage tracking into .NET and Java applications. Joe is active in the technical community as well as a speaker at local, regional and national events.</d:bio>
        <d:twitter>jkuemerle</d:twitter>
      </m:properties>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>http://devlink.us/OData.svc/speakers(70)</id>
    <title type="text"></title>
    <updated>2011-07-07T14:05:35Z</updated>
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <link rel="edit" title="speaker" href="speakers(70)" />
    <link rel="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/related/sessions" type="application/atom+xml;type=feed" title="sessions" href="speakers(70)/sessions" />
    <category term="devlink2011Model.speaker" scheme="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/scheme" />
    <content type="application/xml">
      <m:properties>
        <d:speakerid m:type="Edm.Int32">70</d:speakerid>
        <d:firstname>Jim</d:firstname>
        <d:lastname>Wooley</d:lastname>
        <d:company m:null="true" />
        <d:url>www.ThinqLinq.com</d:url>
        <d:imageurl>http://devlink.net/Portals/0/Users/002/02/2/jimwooley.jpeg</d:imageurl>
        <d:bio>By day, Jim Wooley is a consultant for Slalom Consulting. In his free time, Jim is a frequent speaker, MVP, and author of "LINQ in Action". He is always striving to stay at the forefront of technology and enjoys the thrill of a new challenge. He has been active evangelizing LINQ since it's announcement in 2005. In addition, he attempts to pass on the insights he has gained by being active in the community, including organizing and speaking at code camps and regional events, including DevLink, DevWeek, CodeMash, CodeStock, VS Live, and MIX.</d:bio>
        <d:twitter>jimwooley</d:twitter>
      </m:properties>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>http://devlink.us/OData.svc/speakers(71)</id>
    <title type="text"></title>
    <updated>2011-07-07T14:05:35Z</updated>
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <link rel="edit" title="speaker" href="speakers(71)" />
    <link rel="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/related/sessions" type="application/atom+xml;type=feed" title="sessions" href="speakers(71)/sessions" />
    <category term="devlink2011Model.speaker" scheme="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/scheme" />
    <content type="application/xml">
      <m:properties>
        <d:speakerid m:type="Edm.Int32">71</d:speakerid>
        <d:firstname>Michael</d:firstname>
        <d:lastname>Brown</d:lastname>
        <d:company m:null="true" />
        <d:url></d:url>
        <d:imageurl>http://devlink.net/Portals/0/Users/236/16/1516/meatpdc.png</d:imageurl>
        <d:bio>Mike Brown is the President of KharaSoft, Inc. (a Microsoft Partner specializing in Virtualization, Cloud Services, and Custom Software Development) and author of the upcoming MVVM Unleashed. He is a 15 year veteran IT who refuses to choose between his passion for hardware and software. He is a WPF and Silverlight pioneer, working with the technologies in their various forms since 2006 (during the Beta of WPF) and a WPF MVP for three years running.</d:bio>
        <d:twitter>browniepoints</d:twitter>
      </m:properties>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>http://devlink.us/OData.svc/speakers(72)</id>
    <title type="text"></title>
    <updated>2011-07-07T14:05:35Z</updated>
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <link rel="edit" title="speaker" href="speakers(72)" />
    <link rel="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/related/sessions" type="application/atom+xml;type=feed" title="sessions" href="speakers(72)/sessions" />
    <category term="devlink2011Model.speaker" scheme="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/scheme" />
    <content type="application/xml">
      <m:properties>
        <d:speakerid m:type="Edm.Int32">72</d:speakerid>
        <d:firstname>Michael</d:firstname>
        <d:lastname>Wood</d:lastname>
        <d:company m:null="true" />
        <d:url></d:url>
        <d:imageurl>http://devlink.net/Portals/0/Users/002/02/2/MikeWo-Med.jpg</d:imageurl>
        <d:bio>Michael Wood is a Microsoft Practice Director for Strategic Data Systems in Centerville, OH, but lives across the river in Kentucky. He describes himself as a problem solving, outdoorsy, user group leading, dog-loving, blog writing, solution creating, event planning, married, technology speaking, father of one kind of guy. When he's not living up to that title he's an avid reader, (horrible) violinist and gamer. Michael is one of the Founding Directors of the Cincinnati .NET User Group as well as the founder of the Cincinnati Software Architecture Special Interest Group. He is also a founding member of the software architecture web resource nPlus1 (http://nplus1.org), instigator of the informal code pairing Bitslinger events in Cincinnati and a Microsoft MVP in Windows Azure. You can catch up with Mike on his blog at http://mvwood.com/blog and on twitter under the handle @mikewo.</d:bio>
        <d:twitter>mikewo</d:twitter>
      </m:properties>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>http://devlink.us/OData.svc/speakers(73)</id>
    <title type="text"></title>
    <updated>2011-07-07T14:05:35Z</updated>
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <link rel="edit" title="speaker" href="speakers(73)" />
    <link rel="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/related/sessions" type="application/atom+xml;type=feed" title="sessions" href="speakers(73)/sessions" />
    <category term="devlink2011Model.speaker" scheme="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/scheme" />
    <content type="application/xml">
      <m:properties>
        <d:speakerid m:type="Edm.Int32">73</d:speakerid>
        <d:firstname>Sarah</d:firstname>
        <d:lastname>Dutkiewicz</d:lastname>
        <d:company m:null="true" />
        <d:url>http://www.codinggeekette.com</d:url>
        <d:imageurl m:null="true" />
        <d:bio>Sarah Dutkiewicz is a seasoned technology professional and has been working in a variety of technologies for more than eight years. Sarah's well-rounded background includes roles in technical support, desktop support, database administrator, system administrator, and professional developer. Sarah's true passion comes from developing and writing code. Currently Sarah develops for a Cleveland, Ohio–based company, focusing mostly on ASP.NET development and improving processes using various .NET solutions. Sarah has been a Microsoft MVP in Visual C# and is deeply passionate about the technical community. Sarah's many community activities include blogging, running a technical community website, planning events, and speaking at regional and national conferences. Her book - Automating Microsoft Windows Server 2008 R2 Administration with Windows PowerShell 2.0 - will be released May 2011.</d:bio>
        <d:twitter>sadukie</d:twitter>
      </m:properties>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>http://devlink.us/OData.svc/speakers(74)</id>
    <title type="text"></title>
    <updated>2011-07-07T14:05:35Z</updated>
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <link rel="edit" title="speaker" href="speakers(74)" />
    <link rel="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/related/sessions" type="application/atom+xml;type=feed" title="sessions" href="speakers(74)/sessions" />
    <category term="devlink2011Model.speaker" scheme="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/scheme" />
    <content type="application/xml">
      <m:properties>
        <d:speakerid m:type="Edm.Int32">74</d:speakerid>
        <d:firstname>Bryan</d:firstname>
        <d:lastname>Hunter</d:lastname>
        <d:company m:null="true" />
        <d:url>http://codeswamp.com</d:url>
        <d:imageurl>http://devlink.net/Portals/0/Users/013/49/1549/BryanHunter.Office001.jpg</d:imageurl>
        <d:bio>Bryan Hunter is a geek and a founding partner of Firefly Logic, a Nashville-based custom software development shop. Bryan is obsessed with Lean, functional programming (C#, F#, Erlang), CQRS and Caliburn.Micro. You can say hi to Bryan on Twitter (@bryan_hunter), read his neglected blog at http://codeswamp.com, and see what Firefly Logic is all about here: http://fireflylogic.com</d:bio>
        <d:twitter>bryan_hunter</d:twitter>
      </m:properties>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>http://devlink.us/OData.svc/speakers(75)</id>
    <title type="text"></title>
    <updated>2011-07-07T14:05:35Z</updated>
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <link rel="edit" title="speaker" href="speakers(75)" />
    <link rel="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/related/sessions" type="application/atom+xml;type=feed" title="sessions" href="speakers(75)/sessions" />
    <category term="devlink2011Model.speaker" scheme="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/scheme" />
    <content type="application/xml">
      <m:properties>
        <d:speakerid m:type="Edm.Int32">75</d:speakerid>
        <d:firstname>Esteban</d:firstname>
        <d:lastname>Garcia</d:lastname>
        <d:company m:null="true" />
        <d:url>http://estebanfg.blogspot.com/</d:url>
        <d:imageurl>http://devlink.net/Portals/0/Users/008/44/1544/Esteban.JPG</d:imageurl>
        <d:bio>Esteban Garcia is Principal Consultant at M2E Solutions, Telerik Insider, and president of the Orlando .NET User Group (ONETUG). He has over 12 years of professional experience in software development, working in all phases of distributed object oriented enterprise application development and design using Microsoft technologies. Esteban excels in architecture and best practices and is passionate about Scrum and SDLC improvements using Visual Studio and TFS. Esteban also has a bachelor of science degree in Computer Engineering with an emphasis in software design from the University of Central Florida.</d:bio>
        <d:twitter>EstebanFGarcia</d:twitter>
      </m:properties>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>http://devlink.us/OData.svc/speakers(76)</id>
    <title type="text"></title>
    <updated>2011-07-07T14:05:35Z</updated>
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <link rel="edit" title="speaker" href="speakers(76)" />
    <link rel="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/related/sessions" type="application/atom+xml;type=feed" title="sessions" href="speakers(76)/sessions" />
    <category term="devlink2011Model.speaker" scheme="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/scheme" />
    <content type="application/xml">
      <m:properties>
        <d:speakerid m:type="Edm.Int32">76</d:speakerid>
        <d:firstname>Sara</d:firstname>
        <d:lastname>Chipps</d:lastname>
        <d:company m:null="true" />
        <d:url></d:url>
        <d:imageurl>http://devlink.net/Portals/0/Users/002/02/2/sarachipps.jpeg</d:imageurl>
        <d:bio>Sara is a developer living in NYC specializing in web applications with a focus on JavaScript. She's an irreverent blogger at GirlDeveloper.com, http://GirlDevelopIt.com co-founder, and a self descriped "Nerd Wranger." She likes speaking to and meeting with diverse groups from the Girl Scouts to straight up code junkies. Her goal is to inspire more females to see that being a developer is fun and glamorous.</d:bio>
        <d:twitter>sarajchipps</d:twitter>
      </m:properties>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>http://devlink.us/OData.svc/speakers(77)</id>
    <title type="text"></title>
    <updated>2011-07-07T14:05:35Z</updated>
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <link rel="edit" title="speaker" href="speakers(77)" />
    <link rel="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/related/sessions" type="application/atom+xml;type=feed" title="sessions" href="speakers(77)/sessions" />
    <category term="devlink2011Model.speaker" scheme="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/scheme" />
    <content type="application/xml">
      <m:properties>
        <d:speakerid m:type="Edm.Int32">77</d:speakerid>
        <d:firstname>David</d:firstname>
        <d:lastname>Smith</d:lastname>
        <d:company m:null="true" />
        <d:url>http://www.davidsilvasmith.com</d:url>
        <d:imageurl>http://devlink.net/Portals/0/Users/125/81/381/Gravity-Works_David-Silva-Smith-logo.jpg</d:imageurl>
        <d:bio>David Smith has been developing software for 17 years. He currently works at Gravity Works Design &amp; Development creating easy to use websites and mobile applications.</d:bio>
        <d:twitter>DavidSilvaSmith</d:twitter>
      </m:properties>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>http://devlink.us/OData.svc/speakers(78)</id>
    <title type="text"></title>
    <updated>2011-07-07T14:05:35Z</updated>
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <link rel="edit" title="speaker" href="speakers(78)" />
    <link rel="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/related/sessions" type="application/atom+xml;type=feed" title="sessions" href="speakers(78)/sessions" />
    <category term="devlink2011Model.speaker" scheme="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/scheme" />
    <content type="application/xml">
      <m:properties>
        <d:speakerid m:type="Edm.Int32">78</d:speakerid>
        <d:firstname>James</d:firstname>
        <d:lastname>Bender</d:lastname>
        <d:company m:null="true" />
        <d:url></d:url>
        <d:imageurl>http://devlink.net/Portals/0/Users/002/02/2/jamesbender.jpeg</d:imageurl>
        <d:bio>James is the Vice President of Technology at Improving Enterprises in Columbus, OH. James has been involved in software development and architecture for 16 years. He has worked as a developer and architect on everything from small, single-user applications to Enterprise-scale, multi-user systems. His specialties are .NET development and architecture, TDD, SOA, WCF, WF, cloud computing, and agile development methodologies. He is an experienced mentor and author. James is a Microsoft MVP. James is an active member of the development community. He is the current president of the Central Ohio .NET Developers Group (www.condg.org), is on the board of the Columbus Ohio Give Camp and is the senior editor of first-party content for nplus1.org, an educational website aimed toward architects and aspiring architects. James book "Professional Test Driven Development with C#: Developing Real World Applications with TDD" will be realesed in May 10th and is available for pre-order on Amazon now. James maintains a blog at www.jamescbender.com and his Twitter ID is JamesBender</d:bio>
        <d:twitter>JamesBender</d:twitter>
      </m:properties>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>http://devlink.us/OData.svc/speakers(79)</id>
    <title type="text"></title>
    <updated>2011-07-07T14:05:35Z</updated>
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <link rel="edit" title="speaker" href="speakers(79)" />
    <link rel="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/related/sessions" type="application/atom+xml;type=feed" title="sessions" href="speakers(79)/sessions" />
    <category term="devlink2011Model.speaker" scheme="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/scheme" />
    <content type="application/xml">
      <m:properties>
        <d:speakerid m:type="Edm.Int32">79</d:speakerid>
        <d:firstname>Joe</d:firstname>
        <d:lastname>Wirtley</d:lastname>
        <d:company m:null="true" />
        <d:url>http://WirtleyConsulting.com</d:url>
        <d:imageurl>http://devlink.net/Portals/0/Users/179/91/691/JoeWirtley.jpg</d:imageurl>
        <d:bio>Joe Wirtley is an independent consultant with over twenty years software development experience. He works as a .NET architect and developer on both smart client (WPF, WCF) and web (ASP.NET, Silverlight) applications. He is an active member of the developer community in the Cincinnati-Dayton, OH area and is a member of the Dayton .NET Developer Group board. He has presented at user groups and many community events, including CodeMash, devLink, CodeStock and Code PaLOUsa. You can check out his site at http://WirtleyConsulting.com or follow him on Twitter: @JoeWirtley.</d:bio>
        <d:twitter>JoeWirtley</d:twitter>
      </m:properties>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>http://devlink.us/OData.svc/speakers(80)</id>
    <title type="text"></title>
    <updated>2011-07-07T14:05:35Z</updated>
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <link rel="edit" title="speaker" href="speakers(80)" />
    <link rel="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/related/sessions" type="application/atom+xml;type=feed" title="sessions" href="speakers(80)/sessions" />
    <category term="devlink2011Model.speaker" scheme="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/scheme" />
    <content type="application/xml">
      <m:properties>
        <d:speakerid m:type="Edm.Int32">80</d:speakerid>
        <d:firstname>Kevin</d:firstname>
        <d:lastname>Griffin</d:lastname>
        <d:company m:null="true" />
        <d:url>http://www.kevgriffin.com</d:url>
        <d:imageurl>http://devlink.net/Portals/0/Users/039/07/807/DSC00808_2.jpg</d:imageurl>
        <d:bio>Kevin Griffin is a Developer Evangelist with ComponentOne. He's a Microsoft MVP, ASPInsider, and INETA mentor. Living in Chesapeake, VA, Kevin is the founder and leader of the Hampton Roads .NET Users Group. He can often be found speaking at or attending local user groups and code camps in the Mid Atlantic. Kevin enjoys working with new technology, and constantly works on being a better developer. You can often find Kevin on Twitter at @1kevgriff or via his website at http://www.kevgriffin.com.</d:bio>
        <d:twitter>1kevgriff</d:twitter>
      </m:properties>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>http://devlink.us/OData.svc/speakers(81)</id>
    <title type="text"></title>
    <updated>2011-07-07T14:05:35Z</updated>
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <link rel="edit" title="speaker" href="speakers(81)" />
    <link rel="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/related/sessions" type="application/atom+xml;type=feed" title="sessions" href="speakers(81)/sessions" />
    <category term="devlink2011Model.speaker" scheme="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/scheme" />
    <content type="application/xml">
      <m:properties>
        <d:speakerid m:type="Edm.Int32">81</d:speakerid>
        <d:firstname>David</d:firstname>
        <d:lastname>Hoerster</d:lastname>
        <d:company m:null="true" />
        <d:url></d:url>
        <d:imageurl m:null="true" />
        <d:bio>David Hoerster, a C# MVP, is a recovering corporate financial analyst and has been working with the Microsoft .NET Framework since the early 1.0 betas. He is the co-founder of BrainCredits (www.braincredits.com), a recent start-up that is hoping to change the way people learn on the web. David is the co-chair of the Pittsburgh .NET User's Group (PGHDOTNET), organizer of several recent Pittsburgh Code Camps and is also an occasional speaker at Pittsburgh and regional user group and code camp events. David can be found rarely blogging at http://geekswithblogs.net/DavidHoerster and also is an occasional Tweeter (@DavidHoerster).</d:bio>
        <d:twitter>DavidHoerster</d:twitter>
      </m:properties>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>http://devlink.us/OData.svc/speakers(82)</id>
    <title type="text"></title>
    <updated>2011-07-07T14:05:35Z</updated>
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <link rel="edit" title="speaker" href="speakers(82)" />
    <link rel="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/related/sessions" type="application/atom+xml;type=feed" title="sessions" href="speakers(82)/sessions" />
    <category term="devlink2011Model.speaker" scheme="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/scheme" />
    <content type="application/xml">
      <m:properties>
        <d:speakerid m:type="Edm.Int32">82</d:speakerid>
        <d:firstname>Seth</d:firstname>
        <d:lastname>Juarez</d:lastname>
        <d:company m:null="true" />
        <d:url></d:url>
        <d:imageurl>http://devlink.net/Portals/0/Users/012/48/1548/seth.jpg</d:imageurl>
        <d:bio>Seth Juarez has a Master's Degree in Computer Science and is also currently pursuing a PhD in the same. His field of research is in Artificial Intelligence specifically in the realm of Machine Learning. He is a Technical Evangelist for DevExpress where he specializes in data analysis in conjunction with their reporting toolset. When he is not working in that area, he devotes his time to an open source Machine Learning Library specifically for .NET that is intended to simplify the use of popular supervised and unsupervised learning models.</d:bio>
        <d:twitter>sethjuarez</d:twitter>
      </m:properties>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>http://devlink.us/OData.svc/speakers(83)</id>
    <title type="text"></title>
    <updated>2011-07-07T14:05:35Z</updated>
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <link rel="edit" title="speaker" href="speakers(83)" />
    <link rel="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/related/sessions" type="application/atom+xml;type=feed" title="sessions" href="speakers(83)/sessions" />
    <category term="devlink2011Model.speaker" scheme="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/scheme" />
    <content type="application/xml">
      <m:properties>
        <d:speakerid m:type="Edm.Int32">83</d:speakerid>
        <d:firstname>Robert</d:firstname>
        <d:lastname>Lathrop</d:lastname>
        <d:company m:null="true" />
        <d:url></d:url>
        <d:imageurl>http://devlink.net/Portals/0/Users/125/49/1149/22432_256501669801_766664801_3195636_149363_n.jpg</d:imageurl>
        <d:bio>Robert has over 12 years of software development experience across a wide range of technologies. He has successfully delivered software applications for embedded, Windows, and web platforms and has broad experience and in–depth knowledge of the .NET Framework, ASP.NET and the C# programming language. Robert is passionate about building decoupled and maintainable applications using practices such as Test Driven Development.</d:bio>
        <d:twitter>lathrop</d:twitter>
      </m:properties>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>http://devlink.us/OData.svc/speakers(84)</id>
    <title type="text"></title>
    <updated>2011-07-07T14:05:35Z</updated>
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <link rel="edit" title="speaker" href="speakers(84)" />
    <link rel="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/related/sessions" type="application/atom+xml;type=feed" title="sessions" href="speakers(84)/sessions" />
    <category term="devlink2011Model.speaker" scheme="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/scheme" />
    <content type="application/xml">
      <m:properties>
        <d:speakerid m:type="Edm.Int32">84</d:speakerid>
        <d:firstname>Steve</d:firstname>
        <d:lastname>Bodnar</d:lastname>
        <d:company m:null="true" />
        <d:url>http://www,geeksandgurus.com</d:url>
        <d:imageurl>http://devlink.net/Portals/0/Users/227/07/1507/sjb.jpg</d:imageurl>
        <d:bio>Stephen J. Bodnar is the President and Owner of Geeks and Gurus, Inc. which has been developing data-driven software applications for desktops, corporate networks and the Internet since 1999. Steve has been developing line-of-business applications for approximately 25 years and particularly enjoys learning new businesses and technologies as time goes on. Steve has spoken at user groups and conferences across the country and actively attends user groups, Code Camps and other conferences as much as possible. Steve currently lives in Williamsburg, VA with his wife and three sons. Geeks and Gurus (www.geeksandgurus.com) has offices in Detroit, MI and Williamsburg, VA.</d:bio>
        <d:twitter>SteveBodnar</d:twitter>
      </m:properties>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>http://devlink.us/OData.svc/speakers(85)</id>
    <title type="text"></title>
    <updated>2011-07-07T14:05:35Z</updated>
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <link rel="edit" title="speaker" href="speakers(85)" />
    <link rel="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/related/sessions" type="application/atom+xml;type=feed" title="sessions" href="speakers(85)/sessions" />
    <category term="devlink2011Model.speaker" scheme="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/scheme" />
    <content type="application/xml">
      <m:properties>
        <d:speakerid m:type="Edm.Int32">85</d:speakerid>
        <d:firstname>Nino</d:firstname>
        <d:lastname>Benvenuti</d:lastname>
        <d:company m:null="true" />
        <d:url></d:url>
        <d:imageurl m:null="true" />
        <d:bio>Nino Benvenuti works in the roles of Group Manager and Solution Architect for Avanade where he helps to lead Avanade's mobility capability in the Americas. While he is focused on creating mobility solutions for the enterprise, Nino also has significant experience designing and implementing cloud solutions leveraging Windows Azure. Nino is active in the Cincinnati .NET community as well as online Windows Phone communities.</d:bio>
        <d:twitter>ninob</d:twitter>
      </m:properties>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>http://devlink.us/OData.svc/speakers(86)</id>
    <title type="text"></title>
    <updated>2011-07-07T14:05:35Z</updated>
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <link rel="edit" title="speaker" href="speakers(86)" />
    <link rel="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/related/sessions" type="application/atom+xml;type=feed" title="sessions" href="speakers(86)/sessions" />
    <category term="devlink2011Model.speaker" scheme="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/scheme" />
    <content type="application/xml">
      <m:properties>
        <d:speakerid m:type="Edm.Int32">86</d:speakerid>
        <d:firstname>David</d:firstname>
        <d:lastname>Giard</d:lastname>
        <d:company m:null="true" />
        <d:url></d:url>
        <d:imageurl>http://devlink.net/Portals/0/Users/002/02/2/davidgiard.jpeg</d:imageurl>
        <d:bio>David Giard has been developing solutions using Microsoft technologies since 1993. He is a Microsoft MVP; an INETA mentor; and the President of the Great Lakes Area .Net User Group. David has presented at many of the conferences and user groups around the Midwest. He is a recovering certification addict and holds an MCTS, MCSD, MCSE, and MCDBA, as well as a BS and an MBA. He is the host and producer of the mildly popular online TV show Technology and Friends. You can read his latest thoughts at www.DavidGiard.com. David lives in Michigan with his two teenage sons.</d:bio>
        <d:twitter>DavidGiard</d:twitter>
      </m:properties>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>http://devlink.us/OData.svc/speakers(87)</id>
    <title type="text"></title>
    <updated>2011-07-07T14:05:35Z</updated>
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <link rel="edit" title="speaker" href="speakers(87)" />
    <link rel="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/related/sessions" type="application/atom+xml;type=feed" title="sessions" href="speakers(87)/sessions" />
    <category term="devlink2011Model.speaker" scheme="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/scheme" />
    <content type="application/xml">
      <m:properties>
        <d:speakerid m:type="Edm.Int32">87</d:speakerid>
        <d:firstname>Jim</d:firstname>
        <d:lastname>Christopher</d:lastname>
        <d:company m:null="true" />
        <d:url>http://www.beefycode.com</d:url>
        <d:imageurl>http://devlink.net/Portals/0/Users/198/78/1478/mug.jpg</d:imageurl>
        <d:bio>Jim Christopher has been developing software professionally for over 15 years, working on projects ranging from Windows to the Web, from device drivers to enterprise software solutions. His experience spans the scientific, defense, education, and gaming industries. He currently runs Code Owls LLC, providing software development services to local small businesses in Charlotte NC, promoting PowerShell as a platform for software tools, and maintains a technical blog at http://www.beefycode.com.</d:bio>
        <d:twitter>beefarino</d:twitter>
      </m:properties>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>http://devlink.us/OData.svc/speakers(90)</id>
    <title type="text"></title>
    <updated>2011-07-07T14:05:35Z</updated>
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <link rel="edit" title="speaker" href="speakers(90)" />
    <link rel="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/related/sessions" type="application/atom+xml;type=feed" title="sessions" href="speakers(90)/sessions" />
    <category term="devlink2011Model.speaker" scheme="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/scheme" />
    <content type="application/xml">
      <m:properties>
        <d:speakerid m:type="Edm.Int32">90</d:speakerid>
        <d:firstname>Michael</d:firstname>
        <d:lastname>Neel</d:lastname>
        <d:company m:null="true" />
        <d:url>http://www.vinull.com</d:url>
        <d:imageurl>http://devlink.net/Portals/0/Users/197/65/965/148972614_61d79d814d_d[1].jpg</d:imageurl>
        <d:bio>Software developer, currently .Net focused. Board member of ETNUG and organizes CodeStock, East Tennessee's annual developers conference. Previous Microsoft ASP.NET MVP and current ASPInsider. Co-Founder of FuncWorks, LLC and current projects include building and running GameMarx.com and XboxIndies.com. Proud father of three amazing daughters, Rachel, Hannah, and Jasmine. Loving husband to Cicelie who inflates and pops his ego as necessary. You can reach Michael at his blog, ViNull.com or on twitter as @ViNull.</d:bio>
        <d:twitter>ViNull</d:twitter>
      </m:properties>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>http://devlink.us/OData.svc/speakers(91)</id>
    <title type="text"></title>
    <updated>2011-07-07T14:05:35Z</updated>
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <link rel="edit" title="speaker" href="speakers(91)" />
    <link rel="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/related/sessions" type="application/atom+xml;type=feed" title="sessions" href="speakers(91)/sessions" />
    <category term="devlink2011Model.speaker" scheme="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/scheme" />
    <content type="application/xml">
      <m:properties>
        <d:speakerid m:type="Edm.Int32">91</d:speakerid>
        <d:firstname>Keith</d:firstname>
        <d:lastname>Elder</d:lastname>
        <d:company m:null="true" />
        <d:url>http://keithelder.net</d:url>
        <d:imageurl>http://devlink.net/Portals/0/Users/002/02/2/keithelder.jpeg</d:imageurl>
        <d:bio>Keith Elder is the co-host of the popular online technology podcast Deep Fried Bytes. He is also a Director of Software Engineering at Quicken Loans, the nation's largest online mortgage lender based in Detroit, MI and is the founder of the Hattiesburg, MS .Net User Group called Hub City NUG. Keith is an experienced technologist, systems administrator, software engineer, speaker, trainer and all around geek. As an experienced educator, trainer and speaker he has logged thousands of hours in front of the classroom teaching students of varying ages from the 6th grade to the college level. He has trained countless developers from various business sectors ranging from top auto manufactures, fortune 500 companies and Universities. As a Microsoft MVP he speaks throughout the United States at major technical conferences, Code Camps, and .Net User Groups. Keith's ability to explain complex topics with a friendly common sense southern attitude make him a highly regarded speaker at technical conferences. You can read more about Keith's interests, hobbies, rants and raves on his blog at http://keithelder.net/.</d:bio>
        <d:twitter>keithelder</d:twitter>
      </m:properties>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>http://devlink.us/OData.svc/speakers(92)</id>
    <title type="text"></title>
    <updated>2011-07-07T14:05:35Z</updated>
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <link rel="edit" title="speaker" href="speakers(92)" />
    <link rel="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/related/sessions" type="application/atom+xml;type=feed" title="sessions" href="speakers(92)/sessions" />
    <category term="devlink2011Model.speaker" scheme="http://schemas.microsoft.com/ado/2007/08/dataservices/scheme" />
    <content type="application/xml">
      <m:properties>
        <d:speakerid m:type="Edm.Int32">92</d:speakerid>
        <d:firstname>Ayende</d:firstname>
        <d:lastname>Rahien</d:lastname>
        <d:company m:null="true" />
        <d:url>http://ayende.com</d:url>
        <d:imageurl>http://devlink.net/Portals/0/Users/002/02/2/ayende.jpg</d:imageurl>
        <d:bio>Oren Eini (aka Ayende Rahien) is the author of Rhino Mocks, one of the most popular mocking frameworks on the .NET platform, and is also a leading figure in other well known open source projects including the Castle project and NHibernate. Ayende is an internationally known presenter and the author of the book "Building Domain Specific Languages with Boo"</d:bio>
        <d:twitter>ayende</d:twitter>
      </m:properties>
    </content>
  </entry>
</feed>